
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Nineteens, so there's going to be a brief testing period in Devon, that'll get released into patent prod so that that is being released, that's the core functionality that's needed to open up everything else and also unlock the delivery team, so they can manage essentially exclusively in the pipeline. And not have to do hybrid, you know, manual management that they need today that was a prerequisite to getting Jane's team engaged, so that is going forward into the higher environments. Now, so we put it in the release for that yesterday. 

Speaker 1  (00:33)
On the subservice, front, uh U. There's a bunch of work happening there as well. There's an initial set of changes that I've reviewed, and there's additional changes that are going in. 

Speaker 1  (00:45)
Some of the changes are dependent on other things. For example, the attribute glossary that we 're working through to identify what attributes should be available to self-service for optional claims. So we have another meeting at 4 o'clock for that today, and as we progress with that That'll open up that capability and the self-service module as well, so some of some of what the self-service is doing is dependent on other activities. 

Speaker 1  (01:09)
But the work is progressing to the point where I would say that we're on the backside of The downhill s**** to releasing an update to the lob module. 

Speaker 2  (01:24)
Okay, c***. Do you know of any specific target dates for the lv module? 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
Um, I I'd like to say that, but but I think this quarter, which is the end of July. So we're in July now that we be fully released and published. That would be Michael. 

Speaker 1  (01:50)
In St. Jane, I see that you're on what fully released. And published means that I'd like to have it to a state where we can actually open it up to people. 

Speaker 1  (01:59)
At least in Dev and potentially beyond for self-service, obviously that'll be predicated by some other work that we need to finance around attribute glossary and a few other things. But I'm i'm, I'm fairly confident that if we were able to put some focus into it, that we should have it in a in a viable state by then indebted Deb. The documentation isn't probably one of my biggest concerns, not just the glossary itself, but also making sure that we have, you know, adequate user documentation, and we also understand like if they're having problems where they go for support, you know, those types of things. 

Speaker 1  (02:34)
So, as long as we kind of are able to. Progress in those other work streams, then we should be able to release this 

Speaker 3  (02:42)
And who's and so who's on deck? Paraying up that documentation, or who should be in deck correctly, correct? 

Speaker 1  (02:49)
That's a great question, I think we'll have to collaborate a little bit on that what I've also been lining up Jane, which isn't, which isn't effectively mentioned here, but something that I wanted to broach is Similar to what we were talking to the API team about, I have the potential to lineup, I have a pretty senior developer on my side that is very familiar with, like the python and Java and other code libraries and was expressing some interest as we kind of went through this in creating some example libraries, or some example code for app teams that are using, like Java or no js or python, or whatever to do Integration, so so guidance for our developers, I also have a developer standards team that are lined app to be able to actually solicit sorry, socialize those changes, and actually train developers, and I've actually had them pending on that for vault integration for some time, and I don't know that we'll have that ready by the end of July, but I wanted to talk to you a little bit 

Speaker 1  (03:57)
more about how we should probably track some work to set some standards. And it's not just for self-service. It's also for app integration in general. 

Speaker 1  (04:07)
We get a lot of questions, we've been getting an escalating number of questions from teams that are like, well, how do I integrate with this properly, or we get integration requests from teams that are not clearly not integrating properly, and then that creates problems for roster in the integration process right and so we've talked about things like making sure that they're accounting for conditional access evaluation and other controls that we want. But there's also just the general, you know, what is the appropriate way in code to to integrate with venture ideas, a fed as an idp, right? 

Speaker 1  (04:44)
I don't know if you have code examples. And stuff or pinkfed and how you deal with that today, but I've seen that, you know, slowly growing, you know, Microsoft has some basic examples, but we kind of wanted to tedify them a little bit and provide some developer, kt. 

Speaker 3  (04:59)
The the SDK's that we rely on at the moment are provided by the APM team, but obviously those are specific to the custom. Yeah, custom APIs, we we typically direct people to industry standards for that type of thing just to allow them. 

Speaker 1  (05:19)
So that the industry standards are like all like when you Google this, it's all over the place. 

Speaker 3  (05:25)
Yeah, it's just we've kind of stayed away from being organed. Direct, in that only because it's a you know. 

Speaker 1  (05:37)
We did a changing target. 

Speaker 3  (05:39)
Exactly and teaching teaching development teams on how to do this kind of stuff is really not in our bellywork, right? I kind of stayed away from that we can. We can present Best you know, recommendations and best practices, and all that kind of stuff, but we didn't want to really get into the the So effort are the business of trying to teach teams to that level. 

Speaker 1  (06:04)
But the result of us not having or not working with our developer experience team to provide some general guidance is that we have people doing wonky stuff, right, like, I just got engaged for a request yesterday from a team that I actually pointed to pinkfed because they run into use an API, and we weren't ready to go with the enterid approach yet? Where they're They wanted to create their own jot token exchange between the provider and the The app client in the and the API, and they wanted us to Generate AA just a random grid to stick in a key bulb for them, so they could pull that grid to sign the jaw tokens that they're providing, because they had no intention of ever connecting to an idp, and they were just going to do a point-to-point, jot exchange with a job front. 

Speaker 1  (06:55)
They were self citing, right 

Speaker 3  (06:58)
Difference in architect in there anywhere like like 

Speaker 1  (07:00)
It was the architect I was asking you the question. So I was like, now fam, you can't do that. So in that particular case, I did actually go to the API, I pointed them to the API standards. 

Speaker 1  (07:11)
Right, and there's some general documentation about. Here's how you should do this with a you know, an offcoat flow. And here's here's your integration with pancut, but it actually raised the relevant point to me that those that that confluence from the API team is very hardcoded to pinkfed, and that's another thing we have to look at if they're going to open up venture. 

Speaker 1  (07:29)
ID. 

Speaker 3  (07:30)
Well, yeah, and I mean that they're again, they're hardcoded to the APIs API side of that equation. They're not. They don't exactly said last week, they don't really care about what happens on the client application side. 

Speaker 1  (07:43)
Yeah, I'm not necessarily saying that we should just go all in on. I am I am thinking for certain use cases it's relevant for us to offer some libraries and maybe even support them, maybe not use specifically, but from like the Ione, you know, developer side of the house working with our developer experience. Team, this is literally what they do, right, but I think in general, we should start with some guidance to at least point people to the vendor documentation, right? 

Speaker 1  (08:12)
You know, Microsoft has some good documentation for different flows on how to do this from a developer perspective, and it's probably worthwhile in our documentation to point that to that at the very least, as a reference to say, you know, as you shift over in Dan tried, right? Here's the code that you, you know, here's some code examples from Microsoft that tell you how to integrate for your for your code language, right? 

Speaker 3  (08:34)
Yeah, I don't. I do agree with that for sure. Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (08:36)
They will need that, and I think it's a necessary step from this program side that we at least do that as the bare minimum, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (08:43)
Yeah, and that's that's going to save us. At least some pain in the long run just to give that level of insight and recommendation. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (08:53)
Yeah, and I'm happy to take that I'm not quite sure where we want to track that I can. I mean, I can track a story for that in my subtask for that in my architecture ticket if you want, but at some point it's part of like us, our our strategy. For like the documentation pointers and the other stuff that we're uplifting, to point our integrating app teams to we should talk about, like, where do we service that And how is it referenced, right? 

Speaker 1  (09:21)
I'm happy to gather the material for you, but I think I'll need some help to figure out like, where do we where do where does that? Where does the ball start? I don't know if that's in the request process if that's in the supporting documentation, I don't know where our supporting documentation is going to be for this. 

Speaker 1  (09:37)
My presumption is that we need to do a bit of a documentation uplift from this program, because right now we have a very separate. Pink bet environment documentation and a very separate entry D documentation section, right? 

Speaker 3  (09:49)
Yeah, we have. We need a convo, like the equivalent of a combo confluence site for you know, sso federation, whatever we want agnostic, we want to term, we want to use And then that would be that, you know, that once stop 

Speaker 1  (10:06)
The catalyst 

Speaker 2  (10:07)
Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (10:10)
Andrew, do we have any related epic or anything that's related to like, you know, prepping for capabilities or etc, where we can add a story that talks about the documentation modification, we need to do as part of this migration. Or to prepare for this migration 

Speaker 2  (10:30)
Yeah, yeah, we have a few epics. We can Try to figure out which one toehye. 2 add 2, so I have So would this be on the this is on the cloud im side, or which team I guess owns this one. 

Speaker 1  (10:44)
Well, I guess combined like there's A There might be a few different stories that will end up having to create around, gathering the information, and then the central documentation. 

Speaker 2  (10:57)
Okay. Yeah, I have a gsdw off. I think maybe we can use this one49, and then there's some cloud I am epic, so Maybe a couple of stories, but yeah, Jeremy, let's Maybe we can start here, and then we can shift as required. 

Speaker 2  (11:16)
Ok, I'll drop this in the chat. 

Speaker 3  (11:21)
It would be good, we've got all the other work too Jeremy, to do around the The patterns and everything else, and if it is 

Speaker 1  (11:30)
Electric glossary etc, all has to go there, right? 

Speaker 3  (11:34)
Yeah, and I'm concerned that if it is that that architects coming forward, asking questions about something that's so far off everything else that we have in place, we probably need to get views from the architectural side of the world as well. That I mean, like, how can an architect come at this late stage? And say, oh yeah, we're going to build our own token exchange or whatever, yeah, like, oh 

Speaker 1  (12:03)
But that was the day before, that, I had someone else that came to me to talk about besetto tokens. Instead of jot tokens, which is also point-to-point token exchange But I didn't even know what the setup tokens were, I looked it up, and I was like. How have I been so involved in this for so long? 

Speaker 1  (12:20)
And I didn't even deal with episetto token even was 

Speaker 3  (12:24)
If that's something I gotta look up to I don't know Eric, do you know what that is? But I'm 

Speaker 4  (12:30)
I think it's a tomato sauce, isn't that 

Speaker 1  (12:34)
No, I'm going to I want to ping a leak in the chat quite interesting. As being more used in the industry now Their platform agnostic. I'll pick a link in the chat. 

Speaker 1  (12:48)
But there are basically like platform agnostic token exchange that fixed a lot of the problems with the like the jot token and jwe jws type tokens. Um, so it, but and it works with a whole bunch of various languages and stuff. But yeah, there's some interesting information there. 

Speaker 1  (13:10)
But I was shocked. I didn't even know it existed, to be honest. 

Speaker 3  (13:15)
Yeah, that's and for stuff like that, you know, it's good to know what the With the true purpose of it is out in the wild, because it may be doing stuff that we Don 't need, we Don' T need to have a house. You don't want to support You know what call collar? 

Speaker 1  (13:40)
Um U there's links from this page that was more for Jane and and and Eric, to reference, but uh, U. Yeah, it's a it's a whole thing, but, yeah, I mean, this kind of goes back to like dictating standards from the architecture side, so as we continue to work with, Jerry mangier Reilly on standards and stuff, you know, like it's really important that we get those republished, because Again, not having architecture, current architecture artifacts to point these architects, and these development teams, that too, is also very problematic for us and personally very problematic for me. 

Speaker 1  (14:14)
Because I get it. I'm getting these types of things on a regular basis. Especially as some of this stuff gets promoted by the cloud vendors and etc, right? 

Speaker 3  (14:26)
Yes 

Speaker 4  (14:28)
I was under the impression that you guys just didn't have these problems. On the enter side, every answer was M S.A. L. 

Speaker 1  (14:36)
I wish I wished 

Speaker 4  (14:38)
Apparently not. 

Speaker 2  (14:44)
Okay, anything else from your side Jeremy on this topic. 

Speaker 1  (14:50)
Uh, no um U. I think we're proceeding well, and the big thing that I wanted to call out was just that I think that we were just missing some stories around consolidating the documentation. Yeah, thank you, I Don' 

Speaker 2  (15:15)
I'm gonna assign this to you. But if you need help, let me know. All right, and this action, I have followed up a couple of times during the calls on when cloud I am, and A writer going to cleanup the epics, but I just sent a email to Murad, and I listed all the epics that need to be cleaned up. 

Speaker 2  (15:43)
So um U. Yeah, I think Moro's just been a way during the ones they refinement sessions is that they haven't 

Speaker 1  (15:52)
Yeah, I've been updating specific tickets. As I've been working with the team, but there hasn't been a cleanup on the other tickets. But today, yep, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (16:10)
Okay, so this is still pending. This one will be scheduled in the next sprint, so ETA. Probably another week or so. 

Speaker 2  (16:19)
And then Okay, so coming back to release management. I'm Jeremy, any any updates on the discussion with Alex and team for the broader The larger parrot issue for the So D rules. 

Speaker 1  (16:41)
I have been, we've had a few more sessions on that. I've been in a shocking twist that probably surprises no one I ended up driving most of those conversations and taking the pen. And we are proceeding With that, I think we have another session on modern day. 

Speaker 1  (17:09)
Um, yeah, I mean at the session on Monday for and I'm trying to get them to the point where I'll c***. It overlaps actually with the session that you set up on Monday at 4:30 manager. No, really for the call with rizwon for custom claims. 

Speaker 2  (17:33)
But. That 

Speaker 1  (17:35)
That session, we're just, we've been finalizing the so D controls and mitigating controls, and hoping to get it to a point where we can review it. So D and talk about a getting an agreement uplift, and at that point, I'm just going to ask to Get an exception to uplift our repos for Jane's team to have access. Like, we noted Andrew ray with the perception that that's changing, and that there's nominal agreements, we should be able to move forward with an exception for our stuff, ok? 

Speaker 1  (18:19)
Ok? Unfortunately, it's been a bit of a slow process, but I've been very much taking the lead to drive that forward. With our selfish goals in mind 

Speaker 3  (18:33)
Thank you. This option isn' That's appropriate in this regard. 

Speaker 2  (18:47)
Okay, so coming back to that deployment discussion so We talked about it briefly earlier today, and I'll just pull up the specific story that we documented this I already forgot where it's located. 

Speaker 2  (19:18)
And here we are. All right, Karina, that's why I included you in today's call so there is kind of some back-and-forth around. What's going to be the deployment process going forward for app registration and entrop? 

Speaker 2  (19:35)
And so I think there's some Some work that we can reference in terms of the auta and offset intake. But then there's some additional Requirements or decisions that need to be made around governance of and deployment process for app. Registration, and so these are some of the considerations that weighing in kind of being into the Q. 

Speaker 2  (19:58)
And you know what artifacts are required for each environment? What type of change Where will where will the approvals be stored? The access deployment caninance, slas? 

Speaker 2  (20:12)
Which aspects of the applying ourselves service? So these are some of the requirements that We're looking to the fine, huh? As I mentioned as soon as 

Speaker 3  (20:22)
It does go, Wayne, what does the first one? 

Speaker 5  (20:26)
I mean, the governance is more of That's more around. And the Tim stuff, right? Getting the reports out and all that other stuff 

Speaker 3  (20:37)
Oh, no, that. So that's not governance. That's metric. 

Speaker 5  (20:41)
Well, yeah, well. Proving over, I guess what we said, we're going to do right 

Speaker 3  (20:46)
Matt tricks, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (20:48)
I thought that one was around approvals, not 

Speaker 5  (20:53)
Well, separate approval. So there's different Well, there's difference there, there's governments of are. We are we fulfilling our controls that we've submitted, right That's what governance is, we got controls around the different applications that we need to mfa. 

Speaker 3  (21:13)
We can talk about that and we do so. The pools. Necessary approval should also be included in here, but I'm 

Speaker 5  (21:28)
All right, so these are all points. We've been discussing that we need to do and like I said, the challenge I have around them is This application onboarding is just not a single process. It's going to involve multiple processes. 

Speaker 2  (21:43)
Those streams. 

Speaker 3  (21:45)
Okay. 

Speaker 5  (21:47)
Like not? The application onboarding for you know, federation and ss O right, then the standard apps on boarding, and I see there's like a Southern portal, so I don't know how that's going to involve and how that plays into that. So that's that's where I'm struggling with this, it's, it's not one common float. 

Speaker 3  (22:12)
Okay, turn off. 

Speaker 5  (22:13)
And the challenge I have, and not knowing what all those flows are, it's going to be hard to fill in this information, right? 

Speaker 1  (22:22)
I don't think that's super hard to fill it in, but then again I know what all the answers are, so 

Speaker 5  (22:27)
Well, that's That may be the case, and that's what I'm saying, right They got every app's going to be, you know, federated ssl. Depending on what you know, service to service type functionality and other things like that. Right? 

Speaker 1  (22:46)
Yeah, there's there's a lot of integrations, there's service to service. Yeah, there's there's other things, right. I think for the scope of this project. 

Speaker 1  (22:55)
Yeah, I don't know if we're trying to revamp the entirety of everything, or if we're scoping this down to just, you know, salmon, oidc, integrations, chain. And taking the other work separately, I do think that we have to account for the larger picture. The I don't know that we could scope it down To suggest that because there's going to be stuff that overlaps right. 

Speaker 1  (23:18)
There'll be apps that need O idc and also oath, right? And yeah, and yeah. There'll be, you know, other types of apps. 

Speaker 3  (23:30)
Yeah, I think that's what Warren's concerned about at least partially what Wayne's concerned about, because, you know, there's so we've, we've We can enforce standards, sla, say for the sso stuff, right? But if we get an sso request or an odc grant type that also requires a you know. 

Speaker 1  (23:54)
Depressions or cloud access or whatever 

Speaker 3  (23:58)
Great, how do we enforce that, you know, how does that change the sla? Or does it? You know what I mean, like, that's, that's the kind of stuff that Those multiple processes we're referencing would impact all this 

Speaker 1  (24:12)
Yeah, but I think that like we understand what the use cases are a good drive through those. 

Speaker 3  (24:18)
Yeah, okay, so maybe it's just a maybe it's just a matter of foreign. Not like getting it and getting a discussion set app and working our way through the various use cases to make sure that we do have everything captured, and that we go well be in a better state to see where we stand with this state. 

Speaker 2  (24:38)
Yeah, and for everybody's awareness. Paul took a stab at doing an assessment or analysis Between alt. What they do today for antro Vs what pink fet does, based on his understanding and some recommendations are provided as well, so like, how changes are done requests? 

Speaker 2  (25:00)
A testing and artifact collection Etc. 

Speaker 5  (25:04)
Yeah, but all these were based on, like a sample or A That's the zo type functionality. 

Speaker 2  (25:20)
Okay, so there's that. So Wayne, you could have an initial draft. I guess for our meeting next week. 

Speaker 5  (25:32)
Well, I'm sure I can get people to come to the table and we'll take a shot for it. It's solved. Yeah, that's around the process stuff and the artifacts and the storing of approvals and ssl slas and all that other stuff, right? 

Speaker 5  (25:52)
I don't need sure I will try to book a meeting and get some people to get to the table and see what those processes look like. 

Speaker 2  (26:04)
All right, and then we don't have to pull on the line, but there is a bit of a discussion last week about the athen offset ServiceNow and take We had mentioned that this was pretty much done and on hold. For a while, but then Paul I guess Korea you met with Paul that kind of show him some of the process etc, and he thought that there was more work to do or that at least clarity was required on when the form would be used, and then we connected and you mentioned that there was no acci. Russian, I guess from that call. 

Speaker 2  (26:42)
So yeah, I was hoping that Paul would be on the line to To discuss, but he seemed to think that there was still more to do. 

Speaker 6  (26:52)
Um, yes, the call, uh U. That last week was mainly to walk through the basic and take process for basic app registration requests that don't need to make calls to APIs and Mr. 65 and Azure APIs, so I did a walkthrough of how to submit a sit and a sit intake, for instance, for new intake. 

Speaker 6  (27:19)
As well, as PC R requests, but I can follow-up further with Paul to see if there was anything outstanding that needed for further follow upon. Okay, it's a quick demo to walk through raising the intake request desserts, you know, so I know? 

Speaker 1  (27:41)
Yeah, I can't fall within. 

Speaker 2  (27:43)
It all seems to think that he was still going to provide feedback and that there was clarity required when the form would be used Vs not and clarity around the process. 

Speaker 6  (27:54)
I'm for right now there is some a task within the workflow, which is to do the app registration configuration and the deployment process. So I think there's still some outstanding details that need to be finalized on that. So here, comedy. 

Speaker 6  (28:13)
Yeah, in parallel, we're working to finalize those. And once we have confirmation on how the configuration will be done and deployments, etc, then then. I probably will have a more Ah, solid day for when we can enable it. 

Speaker 2  (28:38)
Sounds good. All right, move on to the rollout, so Token exchange. I think some good updates here. 

Speaker 2  (28:47)
Eric, you mentioned this morning that the apem application is moving to sit. I believe. 

Speaker 4  (29:00)
I still have death testing and do have to do, but then moving to set 

Speaker 2  (29:09)
Kate's open. Emission test bag and uh and I'm And then you have a couple of tickets, right? You mentioned this morning, you have a couple of tickets. 

Speaker 4  (29:30)
Yeah, there's, uh, as they are as requests that spending that will open up a firewall. For the testing 

Speaker 2  (29:55)
Okay, thanks. A. 

Speaker 2  (30:24)
I'm still living on Paul for timelines, for our byhea all up Okay, custom claims, Jeremy need good news. 

Speaker 1  (30:37)
Yeah, um U. The orchestra's progressing. I actually need to look at the tickets to make sure that we're doing good hygiene there. 

Speaker 1  (30:42)
But the The work is progressing, actually, I've been working with Warren on this today, we've got the data loaded, we've got a sample data set loaded in the database now, and we've Navigated tds, cd deployment process that we've actually got that all set up ash, has been working on the actual front-end code from the Azure function for the API, so I have to get an update from ash, but I know that they were working on that and making progress, and now that we have the data loaded in the database. Now ash can start to make, you know, sample calls against the data. 

Speaker 1  (31:16)
So we are, we're almost there. I think there's a few things that we'll have to to iterate on. But from like a sheer like, functionality perspective, I think we're almost there, I've been working on the related attribute glossary, that's going to identify what specific attributes we're going to need, which is going to help us in our Rahana, request? 

Speaker 1  (31:40)
So I'm just waiting to get some answers on that before I go to the rahona team. Because the first thing they ask for is what data we're looking for. Um, so we have another call at 4 o'clock today. 

Speaker 1  (31:54)
That you scheduled. We also have the call on Monday with riz, one that I might need to have you reschedule? Because it's conflicting with the so D call for the network side of this, but But yeah, from the actual, like custom clam, spider app itself, I'd say things are progressing quite well. 

Speaker 1  (32:16)
And we are getting close to a point where we can actually give like Jane, a demonstration of what it looks like or in Paul and etc. Um, U. So although I'd say things are progressing very well, okay, good day. 

Speaker 2  (32:40)
This is Okay, so we have the meeting today for the attributes. Discussion, and is this different, or is this? Is this the glossary 

Speaker 1  (32:49)
The glossary is the other one, which, you know, that is today. There's another thing today at 4, and I've been Suddenly, working in between the 40000 meetings that I have and every time slot to fill out the attribute Gloucester, you to facilitate a better conversation so I'll have some it won't be all done by 4 Hawk, but I'll have I'll have enough by 4 o'clock. That we'll be able to continue discussing chain. 

Speaker 2  (33:16)
Okay, I'm And what about the local testing with the API Q? Yeah? 

Speaker 1  (33:24)
So that's the part that is that we're finishing up with now. 

Speaker 2  (33:29)
Okay, so this is 

Speaker 1  (33:32)
I think that that's probably a bit of a misnomer that the we were developing the API. And then then local testing, so we're we're finished, we're, we're finishing development of the API itself, or at least the first iteration of it, and we're kind of testing as we go along, but But yeah, we'll be running through some more comprehensive tests. And then working with Paul to do like end-to-end simulations. 

Speaker 1  (34:01)
Okay, okay? The meeting was that we're on track to begin work with Paul at the beginning of the next sprint, we should be at the point where we can start also connecting with him to get his stuff set up like we discussed. 

Speaker 2  (34:19)
Meeting with rezwan, do you want to let me know? 

Speaker 1  (34:22)
Yeah, can we I'm guessing that I probably need to push the so D stuff forward and honestly, the we're not quite fully ready yet for the stuff with the rizon anyway, like we can kind of talk to many times but it's not, it's not as urgent as the sod stuff, so I'm okay to push it further out, we can find it. I'm off Tuesday Wednesday Thursday, but we can find it either a time on Friday or like the following Monday. 

Speaker 2  (34:47)
Yeah, I think Russian declined anyway for Monday. 

Speaker 1  (34:54)
That that solves the way that 

Speaker 2  (35:02)
Yeah, we check. No, he just yet, didn't have a response. Everybody else accepted, but yeah, I'll, I can push it. 

Speaker 1  (35:13)
Is Jane invited to that? I think so. Alright, let's make it sure I was gonna say Jane, and like I can handle it, but it might be useful to have you there simply to as from the business side that's also on in Gs D so you can tell riz one that it's important. 

Speaker 2  (35:32)
Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (35:33)
Or Syrians, that wasn't when it was 430 on Monday. 

Speaker 1  (35:36)
Yeah, yeah. I'm just gonna get moved. 

Speaker 2  (35:40)
Yeah, he didn't. Didn't respond, but I was like. 

Speaker 1  (35:45)
I think he's out of office. 

Speaker 3  (35:47)
And yeah, I'm gonna check 

Speaker 1  (35:50)
He's definitely out of office this week, and in Mary, having been working with Mary on something else, she told me that he's out of office for a bit, and she's been covering, but I don't think she's going to be able to cover this one on her own. 

Speaker 3  (36:08)
It should be back on the sixth. That's what it is out of office says. 

Speaker 2  (36:18)
You want to move it and you're away midweek. Anyway, so 

Speaker 1  (36:22)
Well, not midwinkleweight, it would have to be the end of the week, or the beginning of the next week because I'm off Tuesday Wednesday Thursday. 

Speaker 2  (36:31)
Okay, yeah, I can. I can reschedule? 

Speaker 1  (36:37)
When are you out, Jane? 

Speaker 3  (36:40)
Me, I'm out tomorrow. 

Speaker 1  (36:42)
Well, yeah, I feel like what are you? When are you deserting us for? A nicer continent. 

Speaker 3  (36:52)
End of August. Beginning. 

Speaker 1  (36:59)
I gotta. I gotta plan my vacation to so that when you run away, I can run away with you and then we can both not come back. 

Speaker 3  (37:08)
Yeah, Spain's looking nice right about now. 

Speaker 2  (37:16)
Okay. Anything else Jeremy, for custom claims. 

Speaker 1  (37:21)
Uh no, actually, I think out of the work seems that we're working on, I think this one has been progressing the cleanest, quite happy with words that 

Speaker 2  (37:33)
Hi, thank you, guy. Okay, mfa, on vdi. I don't think we have the stakeholders for this, although we need to do it. 

Speaker 1  (37:45)
It's mostly me driving. 

Speaker 2  (37:50)
I Don'. 

Speaker 1  (37:52)
Somebody's got to drive, so we met with Mike Fleming and his team Mike Fleming assigned a resource Jonathan's good with the test cases, so the action items first action item is good. Second action item is good. Uh, third executive. 

Speaker 1  (38:08)
I forgot to do what minise is doing. And A horse item, oh wait, I actually was going to give you a name for that. Actually I just got a name. 

Speaker 1  (38:22)
I remember who it was. We find Let me find A It was just that Like, I have a so yeah, ketchup, oh, uh Let me find the email thread where we were working with them and deloitte. Wayne, and I'll send that to you. 

Speaker 1  (38:51)
I forgot about that my apologies, but yeah. Mike is provisioning us some vdis, we gave them a web link to publish, and he was going to give us some information on that which I don't think he gave us the intake information unless he gave it to minise, and I just wasn't aware of it. And we've updated our test cases, we're basically ready to go. 

Speaker 1  (39:13)
We're just waiting for the vdis from Mike and many. She will start as testing minise, got all of the test accounts set up and staged, so we're basically ready to go, Mike just needs to give us the infrastructure. And we'll start testing Alright, I Don' I've also been continuing to work with the Hadfield program. 

Speaker 1  (39:36)
Jane and they're doing work right now to like try to base windows 365 and other stuff that's progressing slowly at some point, it's going to intersect with us, and we'll have to account for this right, I'm also talking to them about like, how they can use Onboarding to windows 365, and how they might be able to leverage the verification process that we're putting in for the service desk, but we're going to have to talk more about that. 

Speaker 3  (40:06)
Yeah, yeah. There's a lot that has to be talked about in that area. 

Speaker 2  (40:18)
Okay, so the app that we provide was that Azure Porter, or was that hash Corp? 

Speaker 1  (40:23)
A hash group vaul. Edmondy stood up that all set up and staged him. 

Speaker 2  (40:35)
So he requested access to the groups and he has it set up. Yep, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (40:43)
I think our stuff is completely good at this point, we're literally just waiting for Mike's team to publish that url in the citrix workspaces, or the citrix storefront, and also to give us the vis, and we're off to the races. 

Speaker 2  (41:02)
So you connected with Jonathan on this one 

Speaker 1  (41:05)
Alright. So yeah, he was in, he was in a couple of the meetings and and and good look at that. So I'm assuming he is good. 

Speaker 2  (41:13)
The splitting out the task cases in progress, right 

Speaker 1  (41:17)
Yeah, I gave it over to minash. He's working on that. Let me check and see if he's actually split it out. 

Speaker 1  (41:30)
I don't think he's actually splitting into a separate page yet, but he was working on updating. Let me see Actually, he hasn't made any updates to it yet. I think he might have taken it off to a staging page. 

Speaker 1  (41:48)
That's hidden, I think, and he just hasn't released it yet. I'll ask him, though I think he's I think he might be up-to-date. Let me check. 

Speaker 1  (41:57)
Wow. But yeah, he's he's, he's got that accent item. 

Speaker 2  (42:04)
Okay, sounds good. And we in any updates on the Sekiro, issue. 

Speaker 5  (42:13)
Well, the first I've been given for contact for that has been illegal sick, so I don't Jeremy. You mentioned hat, do you have any contacts? 

Speaker 1  (42:23)
Yeah, yeah, this is what I just said a minute ago, so cash out, but that buffetta Bethea is the guy that we were connecting with on clean rooms, Diego has a whole bunch of information on clean rooms, but let me find that email thread with them and I will I think it was hem and Bruno kormac, and I will I'll just bore that along to you, they've given us all kinds of info about their teams, and they had given us a split up of what the different teams do and stuff too. 

Speaker 5  (42:57)
Yeah, that was my impression that they were building that report they needed it, right? So the person I have is, is kind of a more of APM. 

Speaker 3  (43:06)
No, you were told you were meant sue Barker, Burton, yeah, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (43:11)
He, moreover, on managing it right. But But that's why my impression was they're building that list of clean rooms and basically with some requirements around them, which I think we need 

Speaker 2  (43:24)
Yeah, but just a reminder Wayne, that they're only building a list of physical locations, not users from my understanding. 

Speaker 5  (43:32)
No, they're not probably users, but I'm hoping they have information of who a td represents those locations, right? We need to understand if the identity provisioning prevention around them, and who those uses are right. 

Speaker 1  (43:45)
Yeah, it's definitely this dude, it's the guy that gotta be able to get to the answers. I Don' 

Speaker 5  (43:57)
Because they gotta be tied to an owner somewhere td. And if you have that, that might speed things along for me. 

Speaker 2  (44:11)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (44:12)
Let me find that. You know, let me get to the opinion of the name. 

Speaker 2  (44:17)
Cat qat. Gets move on. Okay, so the 5 of these 2 rollout and retail rollout. 

Speaker 2  (44:32)
Jeremy, I know that you've been working commercially, also with Anthony to continue building out. Use cases flows etc, given update. There 

Speaker 1  (44:45)
Anthony on this colleague, Anthony is on this call. Yeah, I've been working with Anthony, and we've been pulling those things together, Jane. 

Speaker 5  (44:57)
There's 

Speaker 3  (44:59)
Why are you laughing? 

Speaker 1  (45:01)
I'm laughing, because it's complicated. That's why so we've defined 4 possible options for user lifecycle, for if they lose or break their Fido key, which is probably the most complicated use case. And so we've been digging into four different options, I actually don't think that. 

Speaker 1  (45:22)
All 4 are viable, but we wanted to kind of flush them out to kind of give you kind of show the full context of what we've explored, and why we discounted them certain options. Honestly, at this point I'm not super happy with any of them, I think there's problems with all of the approaches. Um, like we're, we're almost at the point. 

Speaker 1  (45:45)
Anthony, I think one of our takeaways in the last call is, I think, we have another call no, not tomorrow. When's our next calling things Monday. 

Speaker 7  (45:55)
Since everybody's on vacation, we have it next Friday. Honestly. 

Speaker 1  (45:59)
Next Friday, okay, we're gonna start do the rib repeating this for the other use cases I can share what we have. So bar Jane, I think that I need to work with Anthony a bit and Anthony, I think one of the takeaways was that we wanted to take those steps. And you just kind of throw it into mermaid, or something to kind of get a visual flow that we can put in the confluence as well. 

Speaker 7  (46:18)
Yeah, I'll be aware we have a storyboard right now. Maybe we can share that if they want It's a reading, but you know it, it'll be 

Speaker 1  (46:25)
I like the storyboard is going to give Jane what she needs, though that wasn't what I was looking for it was the flows themselves right? 

Speaker 7  (46:31)
Yeah, the flows, we're going to work on it possibly mid next week. We'll have something to share okinaw. 

Speaker 1  (46:42)
And the point Jane was that the flows And the options help us with the design process to know a what we need to go to retail with, you know, B what gaps, we have and see some of the control things that we need to look for one of the other takeaways. Jane is that obviously we're missing control standards for this right. And as I'm digging into these use cases further, I am finding exactly what I thought I would find, which is places where we need to dictate some standards. 

Speaker 1  (47:15)
Yeah And so there are things that have come app like pretty standard things that like we need to account for in the am standard right. So something like if someone loses their key, we need to clear the off method from their Android account right. Because physical possession is King, so if you you're not a possession of your key, that's a very bad thing, all someone needs at that point is your pin, right, and so there's a there's probably a control standard that we need to dictate there that will that will influence how we set that, because we have the option to just leave the key there, and if they find it again, it would just be another method on their account, but that's really not That's really not appropriate. 

Speaker 1  (48:01)
Right? Which means that we have to build something in. So that way, if they go to register a new key, it clears the old one, right? 

Speaker 1  (48:09)
Right, so that's one extent, that's one very basic example. But there's several other ones that we've kind of run into that I've kind of flagged right to say, hey, we need to talk to WI am about, you know, whether or not there needs to be some sort of AA standard statement for this to kind of back up the control right or to kind of define the control. 

Speaker 3  (48:33)
Oh, that's good. If we can, if you recognize the spots, now we can confirm against, you know, we can look to what is available in industry and tie our standards back into both items, right? Because we've we're talking about standards, even today, those things that are just wonky that haven't been represented properly in standards, and we really do need to get Something else included in them, so this is good. 

Speaker 1  (48:57)
Yeah, actually then other use case, I was thinking about from a standard perspective as well. I actually went to look at the standards to see if there was anything that said, hey, you must use an idp, and the standard actually just excludes and pins, and I actually don't think that that's appropriate anymore. I actually think that we should have a control statement that we can back against to tell people that you can't just do point-to-point token exchange, you need to use a tdi idp, because I actually got that question from deloitte, who was running different deloitte, not our deloitte. 

Speaker 1  (49:31)
That was running that to say they're like, why can't you just do point-to-point? And I was like, well 

Speaker 3  (49:39)
Because why? 

Speaker 1  (49:40)
Yeah, like I can tell you technically why you shouldn't do that, but I don't have a good control standard to say this is why you shouldn't, right? Ok, yeah. That's separate from this, but and then, of course, I also had another request for somebody an architecture presenting a pattern that involved Pat tokens, and I died inside a little, and we have nothing for that, that was a takeaway from our architecture session, yeah, right. 

Speaker 1  (50:10)
But for this position, items are going It is generating a bunch of things that we have to account for from a design perspective and also from a control perspective, which is exactly why I wanted to go through this exercise, but it also very much helps us detail out the flows, so we can show these and have the conversations with the retailers generating a lot of the conversations we need to have with retail, about what they're going to have to do. And there's some pretty wild swings, and I expect that some of these, they are not gonna like at all, which might be the reason why we can't go with that option, right? 

Speaker 1  (50:42)
You know, like one of the options is that we have the managers, install the ub and roll app on their mobile phone, and then that's how they use it to register a Fido key for a user when a replacement is warranted, right? 

Speaker 3  (50:53)
I can help people screaming now. 

Speaker 1  (50:56)
There are significant problems with that, not just from a retail functionality perspective, but also the way that it works right now is that there's no way that we can ever tie the retail manager to just their people. So basically they would be picking their person out of a large queue, and they theoretically could pick anyone else and issue a token for anyone else that's in Q as well, which is not ideal. 

Speaker 3  (51:17)
I don't even think that that's available, that that's just available on Android. At the moment too, the last I heard from the ubico guys that wasn't available. 

Speaker 1  (51:27)
Yeah, but there is another option that might be more viable, but is more work for us, which is the SD case for that, aren't fully available. So if we want to talk on boarding portals that we can introduce verification. We actually could register the key from the onboarding portally using yes to case. 

Speaker 1  (51:49)
Wow, yeah? So there's a conversation we're going to have to have about onboarding portal, and I don't think that we really any detailed anything out from a program perspective yet, but there's definitely a use case here where I mentioned this to Jonathan yesterday that I think that We're going to have to have a serious conversation about how quickly we can move forward with a first iteration of the outboarding portal even before we have an identity grouping vendor established. Because we can make use of the current verification that we've been discussing with sale point and the service desk and we can leverage that 

Speaker 3  (52:31)
Yeah, I okay. So one of the one of the problems with that is that then that takes off the emphasis on trying to get the full on the idea. Maybe solution in place? 

Speaker 1  (52:43)
I don't think it takes off the emphasis because at the end of the day you've been so focused like the program's been so focused on a Bender, but the reality is that you need the portal more than you need the Bender. Fair, fairly noticeably. And so I don't think any of that's regrettable event 

Speaker 3  (53:02)
This is a big Big topics, ugly, yeah, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (53:08)
Is that accounted for like? 

Speaker 1  (53:10)
I don't want to get this Andrew, which is another reason why I'm bringing it upright, is that your ID verification workstream, I don't think is accounting for the 90% of work that needs to get done. You're mostly accounting for the idv vendor but that's just that's literally the smallest piece in the identity proofing work streamlined. 

Speaker 3  (53:29)
Right, but that's that poll workstream has been kind of set aside at the moment, we know, we have to do all that stuff. We know we have to build the portal we know, we have to do all the integrations for all that stuff, but the entire project has been pushed aside. You know, the entire completion of that 

Speaker 1  (53:44)
Some of the Rs are the Jane. This might help us if we decide that we need a portal to allow users to re-register and re-register. It might help us push this forward, right? 

Speaker 1  (53:57)
And we have options even without an IDB. Okay, and I think they're going to be forced into it. Either way, we won't have a choice. 

Speaker 1  (54:09)
Right, unless unless we again want to start putting significant pressure on the service desk where every time something happens, someone has called the service desk and the service desk has to manually verify them and then issue them a tap so they can get into security registration, which they can't do anyway even if they call the service. Desk, because they won't have a machine to get into bye. Bye 

Speaker 2  (54:29)
Okay, we're at time and do you have a complex? It's a good discussion. Let me know if we need to chat about this before next week's meeting, but just another quick update as well, is that I sort of argue in retail weekly touch point, Jeremiah could be, and then I think we need to start setting agendas for those calls one with the US retail one with Canadian retail, and they kind of they keep hammering me about timelines. 

Speaker 1  (54:57)
Honest, there is a bit 

Speaker 3  (54:59)
So yeah, like when Why, aside from just confirming what they may have to like, what is there? Why are they hammering you for timelines, on this. 

Speaker 1  (55:08)
They have their own findings chain on their software. But they're trying to get answers on 

Speaker 3  (55:15)
Great. But we have the we, you know, everything that we're doing, I've already told them right now, yeah? 

Speaker 1  (55:22)
But we can reiterate that with them, but you're absolutely right, right, it's really us driving not them so, but Andrew from an agenda perspective, well I've been working with Anthony, we've been identifying a bunch of questions that we have for retail, so we likely can use those to help drive some agenda items for both the US and Canadian retail calls. 

Speaker 5  (55:42)
Okay, that'll be helpful. And then 

Speaker 2  (55:45)
Did you get support from Ben Cassidy on the test cases, or is that yep? 

Speaker 1  (55:51)
So we did, I paused on it on here, so I don't have an update from Paul, but Ben did connect with us, and did He did acknowledge that he was on the hook to help us set up the desktops and stuff. So I think Paul was going to work with him, I don't know where that sits, but uh U. But he's engaged, okay, perfect. 

Speaker 2  (56:22)
Alright, I gotta run, but thanks, Jeremy, thanks. Team very positive updates. And then Jane, I think the msa no updates, just kind of continuing discussions 

Speaker 3  (56:34)
Yeah, they are the big meetings with the vendor are I'm about to start and we do have another touch point of vendor on Monday. I believe so. 

Speaker 4  (56:48)
That's perfect. All right, thanks, team, um U. 

Speaker 2  (56:51)
Enjoy your weekends. I think we still have a meeting at 4 but otherwise. Do you guys enjoy your weekends? 

Speaker 2  (56:56)
Thank you, bye, thank 

Speaker 3  (56:57)
Plenty of gear. 

Speaker 1  (57:13)
They want to check with the team. 

Speaker 2  (57:22)
Yeah, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (57:25)
But there's a meeting that's going to do so 
