
Speaker 1  (00:00)
I need to all right, say again, please. 

Speaker 2  (00:04)
Oh, air twice a little bit of firewall too. 

Speaker 3  (00:07)
It got open which happened yesterday, so obviously that now with Jeremy Bernard. 

Speaker 1  (00:13)
Verness, is there next up that comes up for you under this epic that you're not off? 

Speaker 3  (00:19)
I don't know, but the problem will be 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
We'll have 

Speaker 3  (00:23)
And we are the meeting on Tuesday about TV. Then if I then be updated. And I'm just waiting for Jeremy to give me some tickets, which he should do shortly. 

Speaker 1  (00:39)
Or this one with the custom claims provider, same thing, where if there is more work, Germany will be the one to tell you what it is. Yeah, ok O. And in that case, I don't think we need to talk about that one anymore other than refining to do Tell me about intra ID protection, Paul. 

Speaker 1  (01:01)
What's next? Thank you. Or has bottomless starts here? 

Speaker 1  (01:07)
Pat pryde comes along on chest. 

Speaker 2  (01:10)
Yeah, yeah, I won't. Who had just I will probably end up deploying it in prad, I will probably just spin up a delivery story for myself to do that and then close this, because they're all set with Pat, and then brought us just a copy of replacement. And I I've just been, you know, I'm Anyway, so that should be fine, and then that purview crossed 10 access changes, one that's not As far as I know, whoever I still need to ask them if they're ever planning on that, or if that kind of went into a black hole with this project and in it Sometimes things are in management, wrangling for 2 and then they pop back up. 

Speaker 2  (01:54)
So I'll just confirm whether that's dead or just suspended alt. And we might see it in Q4 or something. And then I don't think there's anything else but I don't know what happened. 

Speaker 1  (02:06)
Do you think that the well? I realized this is Not a question you might be able to reasonably answer, but do you know of anything else that they will need for intra ID for this epic? 

Speaker 2  (02:20)
I don't think so. There's I don't fix them. 

Speaker 1  (02:27)
And who was they? Is that chain and call? 

Speaker 2  (02:32)
No, no, that's as I did respond, or so, it's like, I mean, I can tell you that PM name and I felt like they normally plug you for anything. So uh U. Alexa, wait a minute, I would find people who are various leaders in the project so Raquel. 

Speaker 1  (03:01)
That's not going to end up 

Speaker 2  (03:03)
People are usually work for them. Work with on them. Are Now Raquel Edwards, Joseph harcell, had never been able to put out this last day in harassel yenko. 

Speaker 2  (03:20)
Aback rock rock, pale rock rock. 

Speaker 1  (03:24)
0 out of 3 ink bucket and 

Speaker 2  (03:32)
Trust up before. I think the usual folks really, so, but they have a rotating cast of characters mostly under response, or depending on the effort, it's just it's recent this the last this quarter and last quarter it's been reduced to this continuous access to valuation work, which is mostly Raquel and Joseph Owen Denise. Denise Billy. 

Speaker 1  (04:04)
None of these names meaning anything to me. 

Speaker 2  (04:07)
I don't think they bug you or microw. 

Speaker 1  (04:10)
No, they just, you know, which is an even, okay. So fair enough, this purview thing. Outstanding, we don't know. 

Speaker 1  (04:16)
Well, we certainly haven't done it. And to earlier point, we don't know if we need it or not. What about? 

Speaker 1  (04:22)
Number two, further investigation of risk remediation and continuous evaluation. Strict IP enforcement are these things that are bad? 

Speaker 2  (04:30)
Yeah, as far as I know, CA can strict IP enforcement as daddy U. And they have really totally changed tack on the theater, thank you The way that they we're about to finish there Risk blocking, they're, they're, they're their custom risk blocking group Goldberg machine that they decided to develop, which was so I don't know if they're going to want any augmentation. After that. 

Speaker 2  (05:00)
Now I love how they're talking about it, but that sounds kind of they're about to finish that, and then whether they'll call it and done done or whether they want done that. Something else, it's Actually, I probably need to put in some stories I don't think it's us, but our own, I Don' Art updated our own state with what we sought, the project was going to do, and then the project did something different. We need to make sure our stick is updated to account for what ep decided to do to address this, which is like it's kind of strange, I guess it's not that unexpected, but our Stig assumed that EV was going to do work X way and said they did work Y way, so technically, we're not in compliant with our own Stig, but the Stig was written with what this project was planning to do in mind, so that was a lot Yeah, so that is dead. 

Speaker 1  (05:54)
And risk blocking, we believe, is mostly done. And last, they decide to derail it again. 

Speaker 2  (06:03)
Or if they want additional functionality on top of what they're planning to do through their custom workflow, so well ugh. But they've been focused on that, because they 're stuck in MRA related to that that they' re trying to meet by July sometime, so what's the fire is out LLM? 

Speaker 1  (06:23)
You will ask, like, is there anything else? Or can we put a nail in that part as well? And then what about this xdr? 

Speaker 1  (06:29)
Or that rules? Continued consultation? Oh I hate that. 

Speaker 2  (06:35)
I know continuing yesterday. They have new fdr, back news cases here and there that occasionally take up meetings. I have a really child stories, because it's like it's quarterbacking between their security, their security engineering team and other people who need various access that we now tell to go to their security engineering team. 

Speaker 2  (06:58)
So I do need to do something to support them. Thank you But it doesn't sound like 

Speaker 1  (07:05)
Right? Like it's 

Speaker 2  (07:07)
Yeah, it's amazing. 

Speaker 1  (07:08)
They had tricks and baby cussings. 

Speaker 2  (07:11)
Yeah, and then I right. I needed it. Yeah, there's really actually for this I don't know anyway like I was saying it's continued consultation, but it hasn't risen to the level where I felt like a story is needed. 

Speaker 2  (07:26)
Because it's like A You know, a 1 hour, every 2 or three weeks, on some new edge case that they're looking to accommodate and mostly pointing at the right team to do it. There's once or twice, where we need to make a tenant change to support that. Which is where I might spin up a story, or I might just have give them instructions on what kind of delivery story to open? 

Speaker 2  (07:48)
So I it's in the list, but it's not a specific deliverable, which I know is your favorite kind 

Speaker 1  (07:54)
Yeah, I'd like to see us close this epic out if we can, then by the end of the quarter, just because then it's one less thing we have to worry about if, like, if we get the answer on purview as a no, and that there's no other changes to the blocking policy. Then, we can probably just do any rba consultations, as like lp requested, or something when they put them in. 

Speaker 2  (08:22)
I think that's reasonable. I will check with them if they If they anticipate anything coming up in Q4 once we deliver this little exort, you know, the access that this exord works on its to do if they're just going to be doing it. Done. 

Speaker 2  (08:38)
And maybe I attend a meeting or 2, but nothing worse than epic. 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
Yeah, in that case. Yeah, like let's close out the X or cancel the purview, close the epic and do anything else they want elsewhere as in thing. What's the word I'm looking for LOB requested nice round. 

Speaker 2  (08:56)
Sounds good. You're nice to clown. I mean, if we want to keep it open, because they pay for 50% of my time, right now. 

Speaker 2  (09:07)
Even though they don't take up much work. 

Speaker 1  (09:11)
Yeah, like I mean either or But I'd rather not have an open epic if there isn't one needed 

Speaker 2  (09:18)
Yeah, yeah, that's fair. I do want to say, I it's not that it's a you know, they've been paying for some time, which they have not really been using this quarter. And I don't know if they I actually don't know what the negotiation is for the next day next month. 

Speaker 1  (09:34)
And I want to close it halfway through, or just a few days into Q4, so that until then it's keeping it up. But let's see where that one goes, perhaps thank you. This one's horrible. 

Speaker 1  (09:52)
Are you working on any of this stuff? All I remember I wasn't like I had all this sense of magnifice for the ddi stuff. 

Speaker 2  (10:00)
So the ym application team on boarding, not the process design and training 

Speaker 1  (10:09)
Anyway, that is the one that I need to get cleaned out a little bit, but 

Speaker 2  (10:15)
Yeah, this was the one where it's I mean, there's, yeah, I was this is the mess, because it's, you know, there's one thing with me, and when it's time hunting, I'm not sure that I'm going to be doing the knowledge, transfer to the ym team, and then there's one with Wayne. Who's not on our team, and the stories aren't in our epic? And so I don't 

Speaker 1  (10:38)
Encouraged by you telling me that you're not sure that you're the one doing that knowledge transfer, because if that's the case we can push that to someone else and just pretend this or like, maybe I can show that this is not our problem. Well, yeah, that's where would that be? If it's not you Basically. 

Speaker 2  (10:58)
No, because it's actually us and transferring knowledge to them, but it's really I would say it's ",", it's really our delivery team, but Maybe they should get some help. I and it's like structuring, that is something where, you know, I would say it's mostly A Maybe maybe my knee I need to talk with Leh, Jane about the about it, right? That I have most likely to I've been debating, and they found out that it's actually optional or it's not and that well, they're all optional, but anyway, so I'm i'm 

Speaker 1  (11:41)
Potentially, you decide to be, I guess, maybe we'll talk about this a little bit more tomorrow. 

Speaker 2  (11:46)
Yeah, but I do, yeah, convert it to us, and maybe it's between me and they had Jane. We figure out how what the breakdown of that work has been look like, because they need to be onboard and there's a lot of stuff in flight that maybe should be done before that. It's it's, it's not right that the ym team isn't going to all transfer to themselves. 

Speaker 2  (12:09)
So to some extent it is on us an its to 

Speaker 1  (12:14)
Take a little of my mind me that these are ever got completed. The ones that were assigned to other neighborhood 

Speaker 2  (12:22)
I mean, uh M. And so the grant required permissions, sure, I think they self served that the developed recommendations. I you know, I have I keep having to remind myself what the heck that story is about. 

Speaker 2  (12:39)
Thank you. Oh, that's the big If you pay permissions, suspension, that has been, you know. That will that has not ended for years and will potentially end once Jeremy has some sort of Entirely new access model in place for edp. 

Speaker 2  (13:04)
I don't know, but it seems like he's hanging, they're hanging their hat on. Every invention of edp, separation of duties rules, so that's really a Jeremy thing. Or it's a thing that we can only do once the the Master plan has been revealed and approved. 

Speaker 2  (13:24)
Ah, so I don't, I don't I don't know whether we'll need to do anything once that's been approved. I don't know, develop recommendations. Sure we have recommendations. 

Speaker 2  (13:35)
They were developed, but we haven't actually, I guess I would say, maybe, yes, that's done once the, but the that doesn't mean that anyone can do anything. 

Speaker 1  (13:48)
There, it also means nothing to discuss what those recommendations are. 

Speaker 2  (13:53)
Yeah, I wonder if there's there might have been a story or 2, right? It wasn't mayhem that has been developed and recommendations. It wasn't Neha story, so 

Speaker 1  (14:03)
Well, there's no other stories under the septic either. So right 

Speaker 2  (14:07)
That maybe it's under modular and process of moment, this was kind of A 

Speaker 1  (14:13)
I didn't kind of buy ourselves until at least the end of the sprint to close this thing out. And you gotta really figure out. What does this mean because I mean this this, this, to me, sounds like an lob requested that we get around to when they say, okay, it's time to roll And all the rest of this 

Speaker 2  (14:35)
We could just move it into modular process improvements, because like once there, once all of the defects in the process, the service delivery facing process are done, then. They're tightening into training at 1 time, like we have to find what kind of accidents Train as well as 

Speaker 1  (14:52)
3 other albatrosses, 4, if you kind of the epic itself that are just hanging around her neck for s**** and giggles right now, so 

Speaker 2  (14:58)
Yeah, I don't. I don't really think this epic. I don't like, no, it's the worst, it's the worst. 

Speaker 2  (15:05)
Yeah, we'll come. And then Wayne can go take his developed requirements somewhere else. And like, my fellow do believe, and we were just talking, but I don't know where else, but that's the one like They can figure where it goes and Lincoln both arrested on professors improvements, which will not be done, and probably it probably won't finish this. 

Speaker 1  (15:31)
UB key service, initial onboarding, called it. Do you have any idea on where that is, you know? 

Speaker 4  (15:38)
Alright, so we have to complete the design. And right now we are documenting on the use case. Anthony is the lead on it. 

Speaker 4  (15:49)
So we have had a few sessions with Jeremy and a team and so yep, still in progress. 

Speaker 1  (16:02)
But do we have all of the stories we need? I'm only seeing Breathe here, thank you. Anthony, do you have any comments on that? 

Speaker 5  (16:15)
Hey, uh, uh, from what I've heard is we're not as yet documenting in Jira, okay, because we're going through design solution options, I guess right now. And really trying to understand what is possible and what is not, so I doubt anything is really documented in Jira, this is being held as an offshoot. And I think it'll stay this way till a few till we are certain that we can actually proceed. 

Speaker 2  (16:56)
All right, so there is no story tracking but design, right? 

Speaker 5  (17:00)
Yeah, there's no, there's no story tracking, as yet I had asked Jeremy, he said, let's keep this right now away from that. And so so we're just having our, we are just gathering the meeting notes and solution notes and whatever we can right now in conference. 

Speaker 2  (17:26)
But yeah, I think like like those that There's going to be a lot more Right? 

Speaker 5  (17:36)
There's definitely going to be a lot more. I'm quite sure. 

Speaker 2  (17:39)
Yeah, then there's like, that's just in the first use case that we dug into, right? 

Speaker 5  (17:44)
The ad alone is it's 

Speaker 2  (17:46)
It's like a politic around like I forgot my ubiquity that like out of walking through that in detail, there's like 2 entirely new things that need to be built stuff. So like there are no situation where, like there's no right. We couldn't know what the implementation story is until there's a design. 

Speaker 1  (18:07)
All right, so I think it's fair enough that this epic is not ending 2 days ago and that it doesn't sound like we know when this epic is ending, so I'm going to flag it with this comment. And that 

Speaker 2  (18:16)
And it wasn't, I was going to say, we can't even I don't know if different epic is better, but that's sorry for 

Speaker 1  (18:26)
I think it will mean a different approach anyway. Because it's been absolutely safer. 

Speaker 2  (18:29)
6 months, were you updating? Were you making that comment on certificate authentic? 

Speaker 1  (18:33)
No, no, no, no, no, no, sorry. Yeah, no I made it on this. 

Speaker 2  (18:38)
I Don'. 

Speaker 1  (18:40)
One I made it on like is, yeah, no, definitely on this one. 

Speaker 2  (18:47)
The reason I was asking is that all the stuff that we're identifying Anthony and the design session, those feel like it's kind of their own epic, right? And I don't even know what initial onboarding, like, maybe we need to define what initial onboarding constitute, because they're like the stuff we're discussing, and the design meanings, it's more like those are, like 3 or 4 new components. Potentially, and then like implementation, so maybe maybe they don't, maybe they're not, maybe this initial unborning. 

Speaker 2  (19:17)
I don't know if that is actually blocked by this, or if we're just talking about a bunch of new work that hasn't even been. That doesn't even have epics yet. 

Speaker 5  (19:28)
Because right now, I don't think Jeremy wants to capture them as epics, but we'll bring it up, we'll bring it up definitely in the next meeting. You know, we are not having one till next Friday now. So so we'll bring it up and we will if Jeremy says. 

Speaker 5  (19:50)
Let's let's gather this as an epic. Yeah, we could, but there's really no implementation that's going to happen in the near future. 

Speaker 1  (20:03)
I've moved on already to this modules and delivery, one that is where Paul way too much in here to get done in like a sprint and a 1 yeah 

Speaker 2  (20:14)
I am luley. I mean, there is some progress a lot of those, actually, I don't. They're not A few of those marginal healments, I think, may have gone into progress in the last few days, and they haven't updated the stories. 

Speaker 2  (20:28)
However, yeah, it's not I mean, it's way too. It's all, it's a lot more work than we will be able to complete in 2. Sprints, though, I think there'll be, you know, they're moving pretty fast now that they're dedicated to it, but I think it is actually somewhat 

Speaker 1  (20:44)
That is encouraging. Do something if we have all of the stories we need for the most part 

Speaker 2  (20:50)
Or like, I was, oh wait, no I was saying that Andrew, there's a defect that was identified this morning, so we're adding with some of the stuff that was implemented. So there's some additional stories around that. I'm trying to think If everything Jeremy has been talking about is reflected here, much of it is. 

Speaker 2  (21:11)
He is And I think that Michael spun up a story for her. I don't know, I am trying, I'm trying to track all of the hours of discussion we've been having on this and making sure much of it is reflected. 

Speaker 1  (21:37)
Much of it is not the worst place to be so like over the next because we've got another like, basically 2 and a 1 weeks to figure out what We need to do with the seed there that we're extending it to like What's 5 months for or 6 months from March into September? Or possibly, we're shutting it down and creating a new one for Q4, with all of the stories we need there. 

Speaker 2  (22:03)
Yeah, so I would say that the delivery of probably by the end of the quarter I think we will have delivered the non lov facing enhancements. Or at least the low-hanging the high priority out of those and that's what the overall project is tracking as a dependency for some of the mra work Vs the lob features, I guess there are also time left the mra work, but that's like X. That's that that's like a make, go faster Vs it gets started. 

Speaker 2  (22:36)
Situations, so I think that's It may make sense to make some sort of a break and create spin them off into an epic that's more focused around the lob or just extend this one I don't know what makes more sense, but I agree, I like almost all of the work. Thank you, thank you. Sort of go ahead. 

Speaker 2  (22:55)
I think almost all the work is tracked, minus, you know, things we run into along the way of implementing the stuff that 

Speaker 1  (23:03)
First of all, we kind of tell everything, but if we got it, if we've got everything we know off listed here, and we can split it up into 2 epics 1 of which is the foundational stuff that is almost completed. And another, which is the ov support work that can be a separate ethic. For that would be a nicer way to look at it. 

Speaker 2  (23:28)
And then we can move the actually do nullus, transfer to the pingpen team on how to use F from the other finger into this one, and then I don't know, do something with t That little they had Wayne and me epic. 

Speaker 1  (23:48)
Coloradin, if there's anything else needed here. 

Speaker 4  (23:53)
No, I think this one's pretty much done. So the nti I for the hardware is supposedly simpler, as you can see on the template, so it's all done. 

Speaker 1  (24:03)
So the NP I is completed. Yeah And I is there like an artifact that suggested that this like we can like good, or did I just mark this is done. 

Speaker 4  (24:16)
I mean. What we need and the artifacts are those tasks really right, so those are all completed. That's your proof all right? 

Speaker 1  (24:28)
And it's tough. I mean, I Don' At some niche tenant security, you don't have it, and you have one Andrea, I have one in the world. 

Speaker 2  (24:46)
I'm probably getting close at this point. 

Speaker 1  (24:50)
Alright, I can then affirm more from my niche. We'll talk to him when he's back to see what his ideas are for that. Tasky, that one's all vanished as far as I know, or any uh, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (25:02)
Alright, Ellen's kind of suspended the nation at the moment. 

Speaker 1  (25:06)
Naria, also, that did we flag it already, and almost certainly we have Yes, yes. Ubiky, integral nation. 

Speaker 2  (25:22)
I have confirmed I confirmed with Jeremy that we should design before bill before we plan before writing out engineering tasks for this, they should have a design. 

Speaker 1  (25:36)
When do you think that design will happen? Because it's not going to be tomorrow, it's not going to be on Wednesday. I'm assuming 

Speaker 2  (25:47)
I mean, it's, I would, I would have Optimistically, I'll say a month from now. 

Speaker 1  (25:57)
Um, what's now today's July 2nd or like Wednesday, August 5th. Which would be the start on and it would be the 12 okay, let's say the 29 yeah, which is the start of the quarter. 

Speaker 2  (26:11)
Once they start next quarter, we're starting to start 

Speaker 1  (26:12)
Out of the next corner is possible. 

Speaker 2  (26:14)
And so if you know, depending on those outcomes of the meetings that we're having Anthony, that that's what drives much of this, I would say, and then maybe a right That's once that's done. We could call if we want to call the architecture, sort of "-un", part of service onboarding, right? Right? 

Speaker 2  (26:35)
Or if we want to say that the architecture work is kind of tied to service onboarding, then the integration follows from that, so anything that that identifies, and we need to build widgets service in order to let people, you know, who lost their ubiquises. I am back up or whatever. Then that could be fallen to the ubik, integration, epic. 

Speaker 2  (26:54)
Because right now, it doesn't include like the stuff that we talked about incorporating there, though, some of that will be stuff. We ask other teams to do so, you know, however, that works. Maybe it wouldn't be tracked in this episode. 

Speaker 1  (27:07)
All of her. Thank you. I already does anyone know what the dates are for actually doing this ied, or getting a design that we can move ahead with. 

Speaker 2  (27:32)
I have no idea if the iap relates. The design 

Speaker 4  (27:38)
Then, I dropped it down, I think it follows the design right so once the design is completed, that's what navel has had been asking that right? 

Speaker 2  (27:50)
Not for ubiquity, ubiquity is different. Okay okay, yeah, I don't know yes, server yeah. Yeah, I happy. 

Speaker 2  (28:00)
For ubiki. I pay for what I'm not sure. So I mean, it's going to, right, I guess I guess to project slightly right, there's going to be ServiceNow stuff we're going to ask about, and there's going to be services that we stand up in as you're that surface APIs and all that stuff. 

Speaker 2  (28:24)
So maybe it's the iap for that. But it's not, uh U. 

Speaker 1  (28:36)
For others, is that a question about the aiab process in gender or specific to this? No, this is this is an iap that has been submitted and has gone nowhere from there. And the epic is to complete whatever is needed for the iap technique. 

Speaker 2  (28:53)
But yeah, I'm confused what we would have asked for myapp consider, and we don't know what we need. So I think. 

Speaker 1  (29:01)
It was one of those things that we got in proactively under the expectation that we would know what we needed sooner rather than later, which has obviously not happened. 

Speaker 1  (29:20)
Clothes, not when we talked about it. Okay, um, U. I think you already talked about to insecure. 

Speaker 1  (29:26)
Vasculature, uvg's phone Let's look at Ntia, silver build. I'm assuming that lunch going to need a little bit Is this really sad? Are you working on it at all? 

Speaker 2  (29:52)
Sam's not going to work on it, so I guess it's me but I'm not. I'm only working on a couple of items for Interestingly? 

Speaker 1  (30:03)
But Sam is never working on it, you son, I don't think so, I'm coming up. 

Speaker 2  (30:11)
So, but I'm also like, we do have the infrastructure architect engaged, but he raised some questions around like, can we really use that fibes for this that are in the design? But I open the console with the F5 team, maybe I forgot to flag it as A Does not showing up on your board this board. 

Speaker 1  (30:31)
What did you fly attack? 

Speaker 2  (30:33)
Ah, let me find that. 

Speaker 2  (30:48)
Maybe I imagined that I opened a console. 

Speaker 1  (30:53)
You have a ticket, the last story on this epic is yours right? The active directory attribute. 

Speaker 2  (31:01)
That's what I just opened up because one of the other discovery analysis we did. I did on something, you know, opened up a we needed to make sure a potential issue with user resolution in the cloud. So I opened a story for myself to investigate that. 

Speaker 2  (31:20)
But I am, oh I found the story I opened. And I So consult with network infra, architect 

Speaker 1  (31:30)
Give me a number. 

Speaker 2  (31:33)
219221922, why did I forget to do 

Speaker 1  (31:38)
Far related, I am That's weird, oh, it's a task that's why tell us to show up on our math. That's why it shouldn't be it to 

Speaker 2  (31:48)
Because it was a consult. I wasn't sure 

Speaker 1  (31:51)
Yeah, I can go either way, but are you giving them something at the end of it like? Is it taking time from you? 

Speaker 2  (31:59)
Well, I submitted time I submitted an intake And I am waiting for engagement I anticipated taking a couple hours of meetings potentially, but I do not know. Also, it is I just submitted it so I could track hey, I submitted it. 

Speaker 1  (32:16)
Hey, I'm going to submit it. 

Speaker 2  (32:18)
Wayne aging for That's waiting for someone on the other side to hand shake, and then we can start having discussions on it, and it could be short, right? It could be a yes, a no or A. We need more information about what you're asking. 

Speaker 1  (32:33)
I'm not gonna refresh the board because that takes like a good couple of minutes, but the next time we look at it, that story will also show up here, but yeah, so definitely sounds like July 21st does not happen in there. But I don't know like to me, I feel like these things might be not very large in terms of effort, but huge in terms of duration. If we're looking to get new servers built. 

Speaker 2  (32:59)
Yeah Well, I don't know I've never. I've never had any servers built-in TV. Oh, I'm actually not super sure for timing, how long to expect. 

Speaker 2  (33:11)
But I would expect quickly, you know, probably not quick. And then we need load balancers, actually, that was where I was. I probably should add stories around load balances, or just update the Deb server bill to be deaf infrastructure bill and inclusive of servers. 

Speaker 1  (33:25)
I would not, I would put that as a separate story for the load balancers, because let's go to be out of our control and pretty much going to take 

Speaker 2  (33:36)
Yeah, that was where I because I haven't had it for a build. Here, I was a little bit, I think I had assumed that the infrastructure architect, the iaa was maybe going to do a little bit more than I. 

Speaker 1  (33:51)
What's the I aint? 

Speaker 2  (33:53)
Uh, that's uh, U. Ella, I just mentioned his name Nabil, no, huh. 

Speaker 4  (34:01)
Yeah, yester. 

Speaker 2  (34:02)
Yeah, I got it. I think there's there's, it's I'm unsure how many of the requests for like patent prod. He'll actually submit, or if he's just going to send us a design document and we go and fill out all the requests, which is where I'm thinking it is now Vs like a is a design person, not a concierge, so that's it may end up all being on us to request the stuff. 

Speaker 2  (34:25)
Once he's drawn up a little by Grammy. 

Speaker 1  (34:28)
That probably more likely, I would imagine 

Speaker 2  (34:32)
But that's, that's a anyway, that's Yeah, I should reassign the stuff to me. I think for that, and then I just need to I guess maybe maybe the bill refers to us doing the app can fake work which I will need to do. But we need to maybe maybe the requests, right? 

Speaker 2  (34:54)
That requests and management of infrastructure of the infrastructure creation isn't reflected in a sector. Go ahead, let me break some notes for myself. And like, I'll add And to enrich this epic with stories around, you know, that we need to go fetch the infrastructure and connectivity parts, in addition to just Going on to the app servers and building the app, which is really quite easy. 

Speaker 2  (35:26)
I mean, it would take me a day to finish the production servers or less if I could get into them. 

Speaker 1  (35:32)
Drop in all the stories you think you need, and then more likely than not, I think we'll probably split this into why it could build into a second quarter, or maybe we'll write another epic for whatever's remaining. But yeah, if you can get that sun thought over the next couple of weeks, Paul, thank you Okay, thank you. So what are we doing on eye? 

Speaker 1  (35:59)
Salepoint, is that a thing now? Do we know when we're supposed to do that? It doesn't look like it. 

Speaker 2  (36:11)
I mean, that's I think. Most of that work is on the salepoint side. So Jeremy's mostly been just having given them feedback. 

Speaker 2  (36:23)
I haven't given them a little bit of feedback, but it's been one of those like 30 minute meetings, occasionally type things. A situation where there's been dedicated work from us. Mostly consultation ones. 

Speaker 2  (36:39)
So we may have to, you know, deploy some of the access or something for them in the lab, but I haven't had to do anything. Other than answer questions Because we're doing everything we're at. 

Speaker 1  (36:52)
Trying to run him out of time, or I looked at only 1 left on it. So it would stand the reason if we're doing it, except you 4 or Maybe urge. 

Speaker 2  (37:02)
Well, they've made a reasonable amount of progress per the, you know, occasional comments I get on it, but I don't know what it's going to be done. And it's mostly the salepoint team is implementing something right to replace our appestation process. So we just need to make sure that The thing at the access they need and that their product meets the needs. 

Speaker 2  (37:28)
For our antestation, we feed 

Speaker 1  (37:36)
I'm assuming this is coming along, but I'm going to ask questions on both 

Speaker 2  (37:40)
So that oneI just converted from AI converted from a delivery story so that alt And then that's fabric capacity, when I'm The person responded last week on it. I need to look at it, but The AI itself posted API gateway thing. I do need to I was going to do that this spring because they're looking for it. 

Speaker 2  (38:04)
And we got a bunch of teams to opine that it's appropriate to do in Dev. 

Speaker 1  (38:09)
That was my okay, so those are both on your board upshore. You will come across them when you check there. So Nothing else, alright, anything else we wanna Bring up, though, we haven't seen that. 

Speaker 2  (38:25)
On the board, connect 

Speaker 1  (38:30)
Collar, then any concerns. 

Speaker 4  (38:32)
No, no I saw there was a story about pcam form. F2NPS. Yes, yeah, so this may not be needed because the new process according to the new process pcams, are not required. 

Speaker 4  (38:47)
So the Tara for F2 nps has already been completed. I think we can mark this story again. 

Speaker 1  (38:54)
I mean, yeah, if you can drop some comments in the work that is done. That would be great. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (38:58)
Yeah, we'll do that. 

Speaker 1  (39:00)
Good stuff, bags, books. All right, I'm going to end the call. In that case, enjoy the rest of your day. 

Speaker 1  (39:10)
I think you're right. 
