
Speaker 1  (00:01)
What is this for story which is? Oh, this is this is the stuff that you're painting about. 

Speaker 2  (00:08)
Yeah, I apologize. I thought it was 1 o'clock, but it seems that it got moved and I'm 

Speaker 1  (00:13)
Because I was looking for the 1 o'clock because we talked about a clock, but I couldn't find anything in my 1 o'clock, and I was in the definitive grindo, but that's okay, yes, yes. 

Speaker 2  (00:23)
Yeah, so Daniel, I was still in the then about the plan that we had to actually you know, link your system with our system and get that initial mail routing going right. This is that we need to log into the 2 places and to get that configured. So yeah, I don't know where to stand so then when do we do this? 

Speaker 2  (00:47)
First, do we do it on the messaging side part? And then we move to the lp. Or 

Speaker 3  (00:51)
We want to do on whatever system is doing. The initial sending first. 

Speaker 4  (00:56)
Okay, so that will be Daniel seizing X. 

Speaker 1  (01:01)
Okay, so so so let's think this so then again? We welcom. Uh, okay. 

Speaker 1  (01:12)
So we're talking about outbound images here, right? Thank you Okay, so our bound emails right now. They're coming from They're coming from on Prem. 

Speaker 1  (01:31)
And they will have the next half after that will have to be dlp, is that correct? That's the order of things. So let's first confirm how this should work and then I'm going to rely this on you. 

Speaker 1  (01:53)
So from our own prim. Edge devices right, we need to reach proof point DL. P. 

Speaker 1  (02:04)
I'm assuming is that the way the first step in and then from the DLP deliver it to the seg. And then outdoor however, it's gonna be or how 

Speaker 3  (02:18)
It's that our final delivery architecture 

Speaker 1  (02:23)
Well, so I'm asking, what's the How should we do it? I think that that's how we should be done. But again, I'm just asking for from for your opinion if this makes sense. 

Speaker 1  (02:38)
Thank you, go Or how should How should we do it? So an email coming an open email coming from on prep? What's the next Stephen, step up. 

Speaker 3  (02:54)
Yeah, we're here for DLP purposes. So What is going to be doing that dlp, scanning? 

Speaker 1  (03:10)
Yeah, so this point is okin, ok. 

Speaker 3  (03:13)
And Horace, which cluster is that Oh, I see novenger joint novembra. Daniel is asking a question on their internal architecture. And what the outbound mail flow should be for dlp. 

Speaker 5  (03:32)
Okay. So Daniel, the the first hot before the internet, from From internal from td, she goes to the dop pod and then the dop pawed after it's it's rather than reeling it bad. Yeah, we'll go out to the internet, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (03:51)
I mean, when you go on the internet in the same way? Yeah, okay, gay, wait, so that's so that's what I thought do I just wanted to confirm that that's how it's gonna it should be. Yeah, I' Alright, ok, okay. 

Speaker 1  (04:10)
So let's, so let's think about this right now. So, um, U. That means that we cannot do anything just yet. 

Speaker 1  (04:22)
Oh, let's no we can, because so the next hub out for us right now, for the UAE that it did not come, is we moved. We put the mixed record to proof point, so that's how the message gets there. But I think I can set up a smart hose directly to the One of the pieces of the dlp. 

Speaker 1  (04:45)
And if we can try that way. Poor outbound, right from on prep to the DLP. Okinawa. 

Speaker 1  (04:54)
Alexath's 

Speaker 5  (04:55)
Yeah, but it wasn't a concern, though Daniel, he does. He won't only do it for select traffic or 

Speaker 1  (05:01)
No, no, there's no concern we're trying to try and right now to integrate the dlp into the current outbound, that's the purpose of this right, so so so Howard and myself for trying to figure out how to integrate a dld piece into the mail flow right now for output. So right now, the output that I have it configured independent of the dlp, is that our ontime devices, the next hop out for a specific domain that we're using, right now that we move on to provide for testing purposes, which is the uap, that is up, is proofpoint sec, right? 

Speaker 1  (05:40)
Because we change the mixed record. So right now, the emails from the own private, it bypassing the dlp, and it's coming straight to to us right. So right now we want to repoint that to send the traffic through the dlp. 

Speaker 1  (06:03)
Right and then and then the deal B to create, I'm assuming some type of a routing pack. To us, I don't know about that piece that's still not 

Speaker 5  (06:12)
Yeah, we could walk through that. Yeah, we will send Alabama out to send it to the what you call the seg, the podcast. 

Speaker 1  (06:20)
All right, I don't know who wants to call it, but yeah. It's okay. So first thing, first, can I Use, is there any restrictions on the dlp side on which IPS can be can receive emails from 

Speaker 4  (06:44)
Wouldn't it be a host name? 

Speaker 5  (06:47)
So yeah, so you want to restrict like sources, and for allow relay, yes, we can which restrict who get allowed relay from, and there's a joker, there's a setting for that, I think we already said that for the seg, now we're really going to restrict the lay on the seg to be just the 2 pot IP addresses for the dlp pod, but yes, no, no no. 

Speaker 1  (07:09)
I I'm let's start from the beginning right? Let's start from on trend to dlp part first. 

Speaker 5  (07:16)
Yeah, what right? Why don't you share the pile interface, and we can show you where 

Speaker 1  (07:22)
Yeah, so Howard, that's on your side. Thank you. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (07:26)
Do you want to see the point of faith from the deal to decide? 

Speaker 5  (07:28)
Yeah, the deal keypod. Yeah, we'll show you we'll show walking up through the cent. 

Speaker 2  (07:34)
Sure, can I say, let me cheer my screen? 

Speaker 4  (07:38)
I'm sharing how I work. I'm ready for I'll go go get a fight. This this interface, or this interface 

Speaker 5  (07:46)
Yeah, the classic. Yeah, the old school. One 

Speaker 4  (07:53)
Oh, shoot, uh. 

Speaker 5  (08:04)
Yeah, okay, all right, so we're on the right tab there on their system. So there's yeah, you kind of got to mail routes, we'll get to there that that's to, that's where we'll send it to where I'll send all traffic to the 

Speaker 4  (08:21)
The sack to the seque. 

Speaker 5  (08:22)
Yeah, yeah, that's the that's the second step. Let's go to a LA relay to directly answer Daniel's last question, right? Run underneath mill routes. 

Speaker 4  (08:33)
After a bandwag 

Speaker 5  (08:35)
Yeah, expand elbow milk. Yeah, and I really this is where Daniel was saying, so we're gonna put in those IP addresses, and you'll probably the same IP addresses you probably have on the seg, and to this this setting. 

Speaker 4  (08:49)
Danny, do you mind provided that? 

Speaker 1  (08:53)
That's probably I wouldn't remember sitting down but I just was sitting. I just checked with it right I Don' thanks again. Checking right now. 

Speaker 1  (09:08)
This is on the old interfaces. 

Speaker 1  (10:17)
I cannot plug into that, but our parts anymore. But not the 

Speaker 2  (10:23)
We had this image today, and we had to dry, like a 4 or 5 × 2 be able to get it was. We are 

Speaker 4  (10:33)
That firewall problem. Yeah, can you get to it or you can't unlog it or 

Speaker 1  (10:40)
I cannot log in. I can get to it. 

Speaker 4  (10:42)
Oh, okay? Yeah, no, no, no, we were having problems getting to it. 

Speaker 1  (10:46)
I can get to it. It's just the pasture doesn't work, okay, hold on, just check, thank you. 

Speaker 5  (10:55)
Okay, maybe as he's getting to that, maybe we'll just skip the other step above, and then we'll come back to this screen. Can you go to mail routes? Okay, so we're gonna add a default mail route. 

Speaker 5  (11:10)
Click on, add And it will put a dot That means anything. Thank you. And then what we can do then, is put in the I don't put this in chat since I have it in front of me the 2 host names for the seg. 

Speaker 5  (11:30)
What Dan refers to the seg, and that's the perimeter there. 

Speaker 3  (11:34)
And also, make sure you select a record only. I'm 

Speaker 5  (11:39)
I'm putting I guess in 1 second to chat. Don't put the commander, thank you. This is yes. 

Speaker 5  (11:58)
I'm brother, I put in the chattel piece. She hadn't seen it. 

Speaker 4  (12:02)
No, I'm working on it. I'm just sharing one specific screen, because I'm working on a on an individual screen, and so I don't want other messages to come up. Kayleigh. 

Speaker 4  (12:19)
So, is separated by a uh. 

Speaker 5  (12:24)
Yeah, melian, yep, and you haven't ordered. We could do low balanced. I'm glad and that the on the other yeah, he has seemed to be fine. 

Speaker 5  (12:37)
The last app delivery type is that's ordered right now. 

Speaker 4  (12:41)
No, let me move my stuff right, didn't see that. 

Speaker 5  (12:46)
A little balance. 

Speaker 4  (12:48)
And it's just a good second, anxious move in India. Oh, balance, okay? And it's okay. 

Speaker 4  (12:56)
So was it was a priority. Here is equal, it's equal, then it will be an equal priority. 

Speaker 5  (13:02)
That's right, no, we have a global wealth balancers in front of it too, like so through DNS we will distribute the traffic between the two. Pardon piedres's for the sake, and that's it the same as change. Um, U there might be a scenario that's more of a Daniel question later on, like some customers, will let the we'll send allows some inbound mail so we can if we want to change the route for specific traffic. 

Speaker 5  (13:32)
If save the change here. 

Speaker 4  (13:34)
Help me help me see it. Cause I don't see it. 

Speaker 5  (13:37)
Patient, oh yeah, you gotta get used to this interface. Let me get the marker here. 

Speaker 4  (13:40)
There it is, I see it. Yeah. 

Speaker 5  (13:42)
So yeah, so we'll do things later on like, if we need to route things like we talked about Like echo works. If one of the actions says, read or route to Echo Works, yeah, it's safe enough right now, thanks to him. Yeah, I mean that's it. 

Speaker 5  (13:58)
So for right now, for simplicity, all traffic ISIS going to that sense that is going to be relayed through the seg. Now we just need to specify, yeah, this is it, and then if there's any other use case that comes up where we need to divert the traffic to New Destination, we would just we get spected here. Specify this by domain. 

Speaker 4  (14:23)
Yeah, it makes sense. I used to do email. 

Speaker 5  (14:26)
Yeah, so yes, this is easy, I guess I think the far is, they'll allow relays. So we don't, Daniel doesn't want us to get on an open relay list, so we're going to restrict it, and one thing in the future. Once Daniel finds it is that we can also restrict a tear. 

Speaker 1  (14:45)
We cannot. We cannot. I try with the ivory. 

Speaker 1  (14:48)
We cannot log into the product meeting 

Speaker 5  (14:51)
Okay, let me treat if I can log in and I can grab you those IP addresses. 

Speaker 1  (14:55)
And then we get no, but it's more than that. Can you reset a password or something like that? Because maybe the count it's locked, because if we both cannot get in She come Jed, was able to get with his regular account to the pod, but not to the pod podermin account. 

Speaker 1  (15:11)
I'm 

Speaker 5  (15:13)
Airpod admit I will. That's a case I can't reset it, that you would have to log a case support, it has to do. It's restricted. 

Speaker 5  (15:24)
By what favorite return, you can't get into that one either. 

Speaker 1  (15:28)
Sorry I can get online. I can get to the new interface, but it's useless, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (15:32)
Yeah, you need this one for this setting. Okay, I can get you this the loud relay I Don' 

Speaker 5  (17:08)
I have the 2 IP addresses which if I could put a chat So you don't I'm going to say I'm Xi. 

Speaker 5  (17:26)
That's one. And the second 

Speaker 2  (17:51)
So now what you guys call the device behind this IPS, and then you guys mentioned that the 2 above that they're called seg. And what is the name for this 2 IPS, no, certain devices. 

Speaker 1  (18:03)
And so this device is Howard, our diasmg devices that are sending email to email. 

Speaker 4  (18:09)
Oh, that was your own grandmo. 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
Right? These are the own prim devices described, so these are the netted IPS of the path devices in the smg devices in Pat. 

Speaker 2  (18:23)
Oh, okay, makes sense then. 

Speaker 1  (18:25)
Yeah, so this is what's gonna send emails to you, right? Yeah? 

Speaker 5  (18:30)
And I said, save the change. So 

Speaker 1  (18:36)
So now what I need is what's the pot? Oh, it's 2 or 2KC trick here, so it's 00 okay, 82 0 2, because that's what they need to change an S. And G. 

Speaker 1  (18:48)
I'm 2 start sending emails, okay? 

Speaker 5  (18:59)
Okay, yeah, so that one other thing Daniel, you have to go on this seg and add the 2 dealp, pause to the lla relay list. So it's changed right here we need to add Those still are really listless. 

Speaker 1  (19:15)
The story we track 

Speaker 5  (19:18)
You need to add the new deal peapot to the allow reader lists 

Speaker 1  (19:22)
Okay, do we have okay? Do I have do I have the IPS? 

Speaker 5  (19:26)
I get that for you. 

Speaker 1  (19:27)
Okay. Yeah, I do know you can get that. 

Speaker 5  (19:30)
I'll put in the chattel yeah. 

Speaker 1  (19:32)
I know, but the problem is that I cannot log into the stupid 

Speaker 5  (19:36)
Eventually, in a seg. 

Speaker 1  (19:38)
Yet where the sake is the problem 

Speaker 5  (19:41)
On Eric. 

Speaker 1  (19:43)
Okay, hold that jet. Are you able to connect to the 82 0 1 at all with using your account. 

Speaker 6  (19:51)
Yeah, I can connect with my account. Okay. It says I can't manage anybody just hat up if you're thinking I can reset a password or something. 

Speaker 4  (20:01)
No, no, no, no. 

Speaker 1  (20:03)
But can you go into the system and outbound and allow relay? Okay, all that you should be able to go there. I sit down. 

Speaker 6  (20:14)
Settings? 

Speaker 1  (20:17)
You know, a system outbound mail. 

Speaker 2  (20:21)
The affinity you want to say the sailings, and then I'll be like, you get to check the supreme. 

Speaker 1  (20:26)
Ok, so allow relay, and then in there you're gonna need to need to add 2IP addresses. 

Speaker 5  (20:32)
Or the hotel we put the 2 host names that I have there in the chat. Yeah yeah 

Speaker 1  (20:39)
Yes, I guess yeah, if you if you yeah, yeah, yeah, i' 

Speaker 6  (20:44)
You know, let me see all right. 

Speaker 4  (20:47)
Sorry, that one word. Did you just say something trick? 

Speaker 2  (20:50)
No, let's say if we wanted to set the changes. And then I'll 

Speaker 4  (20:53)
Maybe ji did already okay. I did a very 2 domains, something safe because these are safe. 

Speaker 1  (21:02)
Yeah, so Jed, take those mxa and mxb and just put them in the allow relay. 

Speaker 6  (21:12)
Thank you like I like saying, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (21:15)
And just because of apparently, I'll put the I put the 2 IP addresses there. 

Speaker 1  (21:20)
Okay, yeah, I saw them, yeah. Jet, did you change the UAE? That did that come to go? 

Speaker 1  (21:31)
2 hours seg, anywhere else, or you left it for just those 2 domains. I am right. 

Speaker 6  (21:41)
Believe it, I changed, oh uh oh. 

Speaker 1  (21:44)
Look, I can't, and that's it, okay, okay. So so he's just, but I'll look and like, okay, so we're gonna do the same thing for testy purposes, right? So, Howard, what we did on our site, because as I said, we just moved one single domain UAE, that did that M right, what we did is we are piping, the traffic for specific outbound domains and redirected it to the seg right now, right, we're going to do the same thing for but instead of regenerating the reset, we're going to read it to the dlp, so that I'm going to make that change for those 2 domains. 

Speaker 1  (22:29)
Ah, was it here like an oculus.com. 

Speaker 2  (22:35)
That's right. So they should allow to test their emails from their policies again to those accounts that we have. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (22:43)
Correct, so, just to life that life that come and out of that cap, we can add more domains if you guys want to use Chima or whatever right? Yeah, let's yeah. 

Speaker 2  (22:56)
If you could add email, I can give you a specific email address. You don't have to open a completely Gmail. 

Speaker 1  (23:01)
Yeah, no, no, no. Yeah, we can do no, no, no, no. We can't do it, so it's okay, we can just open it this testing. 

Speaker 1  (23:06)
Okay. So your butt, it's 8202, right? 

Speaker 2  (23:12)
Hey, 2 or 2, yes, yes. 

Speaker 1  (23:15)
I'm changing right now. Now the other problem that we're going to run into is The S PF record, it's not set up yet for utter cap. There's already a requested there because of that, and because you don't have bacon, the BM is going to fail. 

Speaker 1  (23:35)
Okay, the request is already in, but I don't know how long it's going to take for the 5 world to do their stuff, but at the minimum we should see the traffic going from going through the dlp, and then reaching our pad and then failing there. 

Speaker 4  (23:53)
Yeah, the email doesn't have to reach the destination, the email that they doesn't really matter, which is need to get that email, apply policy. And if it gets rejected at the destination, that's okay. 

Speaker 1  (24:04)
So I did the change on our side. I can send an email right now if you want And we should be able to track it on the dlp. 

Speaker 2  (24:18)
All right, so that's the greatest name 

Speaker 4  (24:23)
So which I guess navindra, which platform do we use here? 

Speaker 5  (24:29)
I think for you, since you're not gonna love the classic. This is the modern interface. Yeah, nurse smart search search at the top around her dashboard. 

Speaker 5  (24:38)
Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (24:40)
Okay, just set the opin. 

Speaker 5  (24:42)
Yeah, just just be mindful. It takes like maybe up to 5 minutes for things to show up here, just click on the search. You'll click on search. 

Speaker 5  (24:48)
That's for just click on 

Speaker 1  (24:50)
Just as such, yeah, you don't need to enter anything. 

Speaker 5  (24:53)
Yeah, so The first time you see it, you'll see all this knowledge from stuff that is like our N to end monitoring service. So that's normal. Once obviously, once you have rural traffic going through, it's gonna drown that out, but don't be alarmed see that stuff in there. 

Speaker 4  (25:09)
Is this your own moneyer? 

Speaker 5  (25:11)
No, I was a third party and a service, not all in different. Yeah, we have our own monitoring that we have in our knock, and we also solve with knowledge for 

Speaker 2  (25:24)
I sell out. Yeah, well, we wait, Daniel, and yet, I gave you access to this portal, I don't know if you guys saw the notification, I know the Thing that I did, I actually restricted our group from seeing the mail firewall. I'm all the stuff, so you guys are the only ones that had the visibility, right? 

Speaker 2  (25:46)
Now, and a couple of us that we have for that moment, right? But everybody else in our team also had the possibility anymore, so not to worry about from the front 

Speaker 2  (26:07)
I mean, if Fernando, maybe you want to put a filter out there, there isn't 

Speaker 4  (26:11)
Yeah, I already found it. It's hard to 

Speaker 5  (26:13)
And you can click on trace. Mta logs. The empty logs, yeah, click said original. 

Speaker 5  (26:23)
I think that's easier for charade, they'll be like a rail blender. 

Speaker 4  (26:30)
Nothing's coming up, yeah? I had to take it takes a while to replicate that 

Speaker 5  (26:39)
Close it up and track 

Speaker 5  (26:56)
Oh? Yeah, so bring our testing like this will be useful when you want to. You know, test a negative scenario like it did not have an actual rule. 

Speaker 5  (27:09)
Or something didn't, the match were all and he wanted he want to make sure why he would he would use the smart search, so you definitely are going to use this tool pretty often video. Yeah, I don't. What says, really denied. 

Speaker 5  (27:26)
No, no, no, really? It was pretty, yeah. So reeling tonight. 

Speaker 3  (27:36)
I'm bird lined from the top too. 

Speaker 4  (27:38)
Yeah, yeah, I saw I was just looking at 

Speaker 5  (27:42)
Yeah, just know, like there's like this 2, we have 2 lines in our for the mta. 12 herself filter sends into to the mta. But this is the one that matters. 

Speaker 5  (27:55)
Yeah, really denies, so we gotta check the settings jet. Are you able to share? This one is make sure they allow relay settings. 

Speaker 5  (28:07)
We're correct. 

Speaker 4  (28:09)
Do you do a pep? Next up is rejecting us. 

Speaker 5  (28:14)
Yeah, yeah. But for the most part, yeah, the SM G to dlp is working. 

Speaker 4  (28:21)
Yeah, we're getting in by embonina from there. Des boxes. Doing whatever he needs to do is try to replay it here. 

Speaker 6  (28:30)
I don't, I'm sorry, can you stop sharing so I can share 

Speaker 4  (28:34)
Oh, sure done. 

Speaker 5  (28:48)
Oklahoma. I'm out of relay. Thank you. 

Speaker 6  (28:56)
Yeah, let me just say 

Speaker 5  (28:58)
Yeah, that's hard to level. It. 

Speaker 6  (28:59)
I had back again, just to make sure it gets refreshed. All that Yeah, so there, yeah, they're there, so I'm not sure it might take a few minutes. 

Speaker 1  (29:14)
Okay, so this is weird, I was able right now. I'm able to look into the pod. We're in air. 

Speaker 1  (29:22)
Yeah, like I didn't do any changes, but Driver and I know I'm back crazy, because that's why I asked the s*** to go into it, right I said maybe I'm crazy, but okay, so I have access right now. If 

Speaker 5  (29:38)
Can you add the 2IP address? 

Speaker 1  (29:42)
Yes, they're really there, you mean no, but those are the IP addresses, no, those 

Speaker 5  (29:49)
Yeah, I want you to add the ones in that chat. 

Speaker 1  (29:52)
How about you? Look for When you say that? Yeah, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (29:56)
Because those are the IP addresses or those 2 IP addresses are the ones on the smg, right? Which we don't need 

Speaker 5  (30:04)
California yesterday. Can you ask them? He adds from, yeah, so I this doesn't Adam first and then we can remove that some cheese so yeah. 

Speaker 5  (30:13)
Yeah, yeah, that's that. 

Speaker 1  (30:20)
Yo just remove the smg, please, if you don't mind, because that's 

Speaker 6  (30:24)
We'll leave it for now. We can move it later. It's not a big deal, right? 

Speaker 6  (30:28)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (30:28)
I just yeah. 

Speaker 6  (30:43)
Okay, it looks like it's saved, it just maybe clusters, pedestrians. 

Speaker 5  (30:47)
Let's just go as my search. Let's see, we can use classics since we're hero and just look at the ala. I'm Search. 

Speaker 1  (30:59)
The cluster is still yellow. 

Speaker 5  (31:00)
That's why we're just in smart searches until sick. Yeah, click search, show me that much traffic, so it should be in the top 20 results. 

Speaker 1  (31:09)
Top list. I left. 

Speaker 6  (31:14)
Top left. 

Speaker 1  (31:15)
Bring her left left, give him on the right, oh. 

Speaker 5  (31:22)
Yeah, that's not enough. Yeah, there's something incomplete, so yeah, click on any of those top 2 yeah. Expand that. 

Speaker 5  (31:35)
Yeah, so we added the ipa, so it should work now. Yeah dot 30. 

Speaker 1  (31:47)
Okay, that. 

Speaker 6  (31:58)
Let's see how quick this is. 

Speaker 1  (32:01)
He was taken a minute or so, but it's much faster than the airwave. 

Speaker 4  (32:10)
The magic yesterday, 30-30 minutes. Oh, you guys should be happy with the fact that it's an in 5 minutes. 

Speaker 1  (32:19)
No, it's not even 5 minutes. 

Speaker 4  (32:22)
Okay, yeah, I' 

Speaker 3  (32:25)
Mark search, it's any tie between 1 and 2 minutes. Because there's a cool job that actually parses the raw text logs and then pushes that into an SQL database. 

Speaker 1  (32:37)
Yeah, that's typically then what we did. And what we saw like. It's about the 1 minute like thing, right? 

Speaker 6  (32:47)
The new Ford, the Not knowledge, fund already there Then, you set it up, I'm just wondering why these email 

Speaker 5  (32:55)
On the archbred is supposed to be there, after I guess that's our third party monitoring service. 

Speaker 3  (33:01)
Look, those are heartbeat emails to and from our off centers. 

Speaker 6  (33:16)
Right there on Thursday, Daniels incomplay still 

Speaker 1  (33:19)
I think a cash flow isn't really? There's still real. Est. 

Speaker 1  (33:25)
So let's say, so, it's coming from 67 to 31, is that in our list. 

Speaker 6  (33:33)
Now Hoy one, they're here, no 67 2 3 1 1 51 1 30. Yep, that's the the first IP. So you weep, wee. 

Speaker 6  (33:44)
You got a good go there. Just make sure it's stuff very first I keep here. Yeah, try Monday more, because now it's screened, so 

Speaker 1  (34:01)
No okay, yeah, I' 

Speaker 6  (34:04)
Just for Kix, yeah, I know I Don' 

Speaker 4  (34:15)
That's that no I guess you need to send the email the ecosystem with 500, so it's not a free trade. Right? 

Speaker 6  (34:26)
Yeah, I know he just, didn't, yeah, oh, and he wanted to do it. I'm 

Speaker 4  (34:34)
I accept. No, that's a that's a detached action. 

Speaker 6  (35:04)
This is an incomplete stuff. 

Speaker 3  (35:11)
Yeah, I'd seen the scent mail configurations take a little bit longer lately, I actually haven't asked him to product engineering why that is 

Speaker 1  (35:22)
And so the thing is, this is just the timing 

Speaker 3  (35:25)
It may be that that's my initial guess I can actually look on one of the agents and see what that what's going on there. I Don' Well, I'll need a minute or 2 to get to that, though. 

Speaker 3  (35:50)
Which agent did this go to? 6XX feet. 

Speaker 3  (36:12)
Oh, I have to use cyberark to get there. It's going to be another minute I Don' 

Speaker 1  (36:21)
Yeah, we're not only ones we're not paint. 

Speaker 3  (36:26)
We have to do it for ssh, and basically I have to go to a different url to get a token, and then sign in with It's like some dollar ubiquity, you know, you have to 

Speaker 1  (36:44)
Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (36:46)
And then it actually allows you in 

Speaker 3  (37:03)
It's new as well. So a lot of people aren't used to it. 

Speaker 1  (37:07)
And I can leave Nick Meyer, nickname. 

Speaker 3  (37:12)
Yeah, so I type in a very long ssh string, and then it gives me A Don't tiny url or a QR Code that I can scan. 

Speaker 6  (37:29)
Earlier, you You gave me the MXA looking at this. It seems the ultras MX0, D. Should we not put this in as well, just in case or 

Speaker 1  (37:46)
But it's weird, why does he say makes this? Because that should be a different IP. 

Speaker 5  (37:51)
Alright, it's a reverse DN sport, and he's right. It should be 

Speaker 3  (37:56)
Because of the global load balances, you may see either IP address associated with either ftbn, the wholesale okinaw. 

Speaker 1  (38:05)
Yeah, but if you have the IP do we need to add both 

Speaker 3  (38:08)
No, I mean, it's the other piece of match. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (38:15)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (38:57)
You have meet us another image just in case 

Speaker 3  (39:01)
Yeah, feel free while I'm checking this. 

Speaker 1  (39:05)
Maybe it's maybe it's that it's, it's I'm Do you know what I want someone to check or see? What's what do I see on this saying? I feel like yeah, i' 

Speaker 1  (39:51)
Yeah, so even on our side on the seg, I see the same thing they see the email coming home is that what Chipotle was looking at? Oh, yeah? I don't know if that's what chip was looking. 

Speaker 1  (40:04)
I'm sorry, thank you. Thank you. You're not looking at the same thing. 

Speaker 1  (40:09)
What do we see on the DLP side? Yeah, I' No, incidental, being sensitive as play. I'm assuming so Yeah 

Speaker 1  (40:41)
Yeah, the folks included 

Speaker 5  (40:44)
Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (40:58)
That is this. 

Speaker 1  (41:35)
Now isn't this something that you have? Because remember you, I was creating this this era coming 

Speaker 4  (41:43)
There's no user or no So let me just if you look at the user, it says the user, if I'm getting user on. So the user unknown 

Speaker 3  (41:58)
I wonder if we have recipient verification somewhere. 

Speaker 4  (42:04)
So I'm getting enough. I'm getting the knife with obviously the same error message. 

Speaker 1  (42:12)
Can you send the screen to the 

Speaker 4  (42:15)
He of course. I'm trying, I don't 

Speaker 2  (42:29)
That thing did need to stop sharing this 

Speaker 4  (42:32)
I just told this chef, I aint no worse, but it needs to stop. So This, this is what's drawing, my eye right now is like user unknown. The circumstances denying exactly. 

Speaker 4  (42:50)
But why is it giving me the denying? That's my question, right? 

Speaker 5  (42:57)
Yeah Accountable to the user's list 

Speaker 1  (43:05)
It doesn't matter just because if you look at the email validation, sorry. I changed the policy to be continued contin. 

Speaker 6  (43:17)
Okay, cancel qanc, so if you change that arrangement. 

Speaker 1  (43:21)
So, it doesn't matter what the it's on yesterday. 

Speaker 3  (43:27)
Yeah, it's called that there for just a second. Can you scroll all the way down to the bottom? Now, please Perfect, Thanksgiving, okay. 

Speaker 3  (43:54)
Yeah, I don't know if it's caught up with this or not. Okay? I'm going to welcome you to the advent console. 

Speaker 6  (44:09)
The emails are being sent out as Pat. -, td, unless we change the primary app, do we have to specify something about in the 

Speaker 3  (44:21)
No, if you're on the allowing the table, it doesn't 

Speaker 6  (44:37)
There's the relays. 

Speaker 1  (44:38)
And so I always have locks. 

Speaker 3  (44:43)
Yes, they would show the same thing, though. Give me a jest minute, still looking into this unpacking logs here. 

Speaker 4  (46:04)
Do on a navigindraw or a Navendra, do I need to be specific here? Or can I just do asterix that domain.com. 

Speaker 3  (46:14)
You can, you can do partial, so you don't even need the ad symbol. You can just put in The Domain. 

Speaker 5  (46:34)
Yeah, the DLP side's fine, is it's why The allowed relay is not being Applied on the seg 

Speaker 3  (46:46)
Yeah, I'm looking right now. 

Speaker 4  (47:03)
So the seconds are close, close relay until you allow the specific IPS. Right, so 

Speaker 3  (47:12)
The only thing it allows is Itself essentially, so if it generates its own email and allows that to go outbound, thank you. Yeah, so now that I'm finally on the agent, I am not seeing it replicate cleanly. Let me Yeah, something's up with. 

Speaker 3  (47:36)
Uh, the The replication on the send male side of things, I am just going to push a command and tell this system to To pull the latest pfake file down. 

Speaker 1  (49:03)
I have Arthur, I have one word waiting, I was just trying to see if I can see your Cause you said that to give you permission to your staff, I don't see your part at all. Did you just set it up for the for you have to set it up for Daniel lacria at stash, indign. 

Speaker 2  (49:28)
Let me take a quick look and see what it did. 

Speaker 1  (49:31)
Yeah, I like Because I should be able to see your dream fight management. Thank you back. That thing was sitting in it. 

Speaker 7  (49:48)
So I did just want to call out there's about 6 minutes left in the meeting, and I don't know what's left to be done Dan, but I believe you do have a hard stop at the top of the hour. Is that right? I do yes, okay. 

Speaker 7  (50:00)
So I just wanted to let everyone know so we can plan appropriate. 

Speaker 1  (50:06)
Well, I see what you did. You know, here's my wrong developers. Use Daniel that we have D3 that grew at pet that didn't come 

Speaker 2  (50:15)
So that's why. 

Speaker 6  (50:18)
Doctor I'm like you. 

Speaker 1  (50:21)
Oh, you don't need it. You're fine, I got you A 

Speaker 2  (50:26)
Let's ej, for a planet, read the cardinal. 

Speaker 1  (50:30)
Jep is fine. Yeah, jet is fine, so he should be fine. He's just me who 

Speaker 2  (50:37)
You know what I got that from right launching, I was going to do a cap, but I was searching for a coming in any lab that that's what I saw, like, okay, most likely to switch up. 

Speaker 1  (50:46)
I didn't Yeah, I don't even know that that that's that evaluaters exist. Yeah 

Speaker 3  (50:53)
Ok, yes, so I do have to drop. I have refreshed forced to refresh on the send mail config, it's still sitting on On the the back end script that runs this so I'm just wondering if it's waiting for something to update, but if you could try this in about an hour that would be fantastic. I do need to drop though, to take a quick bio and prep for my next call. 

Speaker 1  (51:22)
Okay, so if this is not going to work in the next, let's say about half an hour, right? We can schedule something to get from a nickname. Sounds good. 

Speaker 1  (51:32)
Thank 

Speaker 7  (51:35)
Yeah, if you can just replay all let me know, and then I can look to get some time on Dan's calendar or right now. It looks like 1030 to 11:30 AM is open, so I'm gonna go ahead and put a hole on there. Just so we don't lose the slot. 

Speaker 7  (51:57)
Okay, let us know how it works out. 

Speaker 1  (52:00)
Yep, we will. 

Speaker 7  (52:00)
Hey, thank you everyone for your time today. Thank you guys, thank you, okay, bye, bye sticker. 

Speaker 1  (52:20)
Thank you. 
