
Speaker 1  (00:01)
We're gathering like, there's nothing of officials started yet. 

Speaker 2  (00:08)
You mean on the meeting today? Yes 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, I just came in a minute late. That's all 

Speaker 2  (00:13)
Okay, yes, I believe we are still waiting for people, and I was just entering an ad hoc. 

Speaker 1  (00:18)
All right, perfect, thank you. 

Speaker 2  (00:21)
Of 

Speaker 1  (00:22)
I was, I'm following up from last week's session, I think was held Wednesday instead of Thursday, but in any event, there was some action on him. Some last week team we can wait for everyone to join. If Daniel's here, jet or Dave Reese. 

Speaker 1  (00:38)
Anyone want to stand up and just let us know when you're ready. 

Speaker 3  (00:45)
I think, give it a few more minutes, see if Daniel Schulz. 

Speaker 1  (00:52)
When I was bringing the cookies, all right? Yeah, we had some leftover action items. I see a couple of them, but Daniels pretty sure. 

Speaker 1  (01:03)
Or maybe it's dance. They just write this dance. I don't know if it's Dan or Daniel. 

Speaker 3  (01:12)
What are the action items? 

Speaker 1  (01:14)
Test new message generation bug with multiple approaches. Provide screenshots of test results to the team. Send cloud threat response app registration documentation. 

Speaker 1  (01:26)
Is that you Dan, or is that Dan internal? 

Speaker 2  (01:30)
I have already it pointed them out on all the C Tr documentation. 

Speaker 1  (01:35)
Alright. And then jet continue reviewing remaining rules. Investigative second banner is caused by exchange transport rule and to tag along with that jet. 

Speaker 1  (01:45)
If it's you or Daniel, I just said to summary, to just to kind of get some visibility into the rules we've reviewed. And what we have left so think of it like a percentage tracker, if that makes sense. 

Speaker 3  (02:01)
I do have a few questions still, that's new, I believe right. I sent an email to Dan previously about removing headers. I think maybe it'll be easier to just clarify here. 

Speaker 1  (02:16)
Yeah, and if you wanted to wait a second, we certainly can I just Sharon, though, those are where we left off the other day, and I want to make sure from your perspective, the team's perspective that is where we can pick up today. I'm And that's it, when you're ready, take it away and I'd ask again, team, be considerate, and let's try to wrap up at 5 minutes to the hour, if it's possible if something pressing, obviously let's continue, but just kind of wrap on a clear point where we end. Something and we have a couple minutes left in the hour to break to the next call. 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
That was one of the open items we're trying to I want to do a better job at managing for all of you. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (02:57)
That's good to hear. 

Speaker 1  (02:59)
Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (03:04)
Go ahead, please, Jack. 

Speaker 3  (03:06)
Actually Let's get a few of the questions hardware wise, I know we got some of the devices. Do you know exactly how many nicks are on the device? 

Speaker 2  (03:19)
I go offhand. 

Speaker 3  (03:21)
Okay, can we find out because I really need to figure out whether we're going to be doing any type of fault tolerance, you know how I sent an email about inbound outbound, and possibly, if there's 4 nicks, we'll do Baltimore for each one okay. I said, no or no wonder he actually wants us to know as well. 

Speaker 2  (03:45)
Yeah, sorry, I think the vendor is going to have to answer that, because he's the one who actually sold the hardware to you folks. I will reach out to him on teams right now. 

Speaker 3  (03:54)
Ok, that'll be great. And How will we remove all receive headers from for outbound email? Only, that's the only thing I'm concerned about. 

Speaker 3  (04:08)
So that we pretty much Hide our naming conventions, I ps internal IPS and things like that. 

Speaker 2  (04:18)
But I don't recommend doing it because it can cause downstream problems, but you can do a delete header action, and you would want to limit that to allow relay. 

Speaker 3  (04:34)
Allow relay. 

Speaker 2  (04:36)
So in the policy route section, you would be restrict processing to the following policy routes set that to allow relay, which is for the most part. Your outbound email. And then Do remove header options? 

Speaker 2  (04:52)
There just keep in mind. Well, you'll probably also want to disable that for default inbound, so you'll have a double policy route condition. I will bring up my test lab and grab a screenshot for you in just a minute. 

Speaker 3  (05:09)
I thought, if you want a I'm sharing my screen right now we can walk through it kind of because I found it was Gonna be something like this right where default? Don't process default outbound, but which but you're saying in the rair ring? 

Speaker 2  (05:27)
The top one you are, they make to allow relay, and then you want to keep that. In addition to do a not process for default inbound. 

Speaker 3  (05:35)
Okay. All right, and then paulsy wrote upbound. 

Speaker 2  (05:44)
No, in this case, I would just do um U. Message size greater than one bite. And that way it applies to all emails belonging to those to the policy routes you have indicated up above, so in other words, any message bigger than one bite that's on, allow relay and not default inbound, we're going to perform the following actions, and then definitely copy The header and name, if it's not one of the headers listed under operations. 

Speaker 3  (06:15)
Can't give me one suck. Matches such message Audi no, no, no I want message size and total rain. 

Speaker 2  (06:31)
If you want to do message size It may be message body size either. It is message size right there and then greater than one bite. 

Speaker 3  (06:44)
On bite, okay? Alright. So 

Speaker 2  (06:49)
To delete the policy ride equals outbound condition. Alright. The condition 

Speaker 3  (06:57)
Addition, oh, correct. Time 

Speaker 2  (07:03)
There you go. 

Speaker 3  (07:05)
Okay, continue. 

Speaker 2  (07:07)
And then the operation go ahead and edit this. Yeah 

Speaker 3  (07:10)
Yeah, I was wondering about the distancing, right? Unless I'm because it seems to want to value right. 

Speaker 2  (07:19)
You can be as a value blank and it should apply to all headers of that header name. 

Speaker 3  (07:25)
Okay. 

Speaker 4  (07:32)
Sorry, Jonah, a little bit, so so then do we need to do this for each individual header? They're going to remove 

Speaker 3  (07:38)
No, no, no, it's all the received headers right at this point B. Yeah So this looks right? Right? 

Speaker 2  (07:50)
At first glance, yes, I definitely would recommend testing it. I am actually looking for those header names right now as well. 

Speaker 3  (08:01)
Okay, I'm just gonna save it for an optimal. And if you don't mind, I want if you can step through the ortp profile settings. 

Speaker 2  (08:24)
Yeah, so that header should just be received, so we should be good there again. I'd recommend testing. I absolutely understand the approach and the issue trying to resolve again. 

Speaker 2  (08:38)
I don't recommend removing the received headers just to try to obscure your internal network settings. 

Speaker 3  (08:48)
Okay, well, we did have it done previously, so I just wanted to make sure that we can do it what issues have you seen so far like maybe male routing looping? 

Speaker 4  (09:03)
I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (09:04)
Deterrors on outbound email. Yes 

Speaker 4  (09:07)
Yes, wouldn't that break some of the rfcs? Yes 

Speaker 2  (09:14)
It may also conflict with receiving side filtering. Thank 

Speaker 4  (09:25)
I'm pretty sure the jet that there's some rfcs out there that rely on 

Speaker 3  (09:28)
We've been doing it for the longest time, unfortunately 

Speaker 2  (09:32)
It doesn't mean that you are complying with smtp. Protocol standards understand 

Speaker 3  (09:38)
Okay? So 

Speaker 4  (09:40)
Okay, so you know, let's for now, let's let's make sure that we can do it and I think that it's the test that we want to do and let's raise this with Joe. 

Speaker 3  (09:52)
Joe, whether he wants to keep it or not. 

Speaker 4  (09:55)
Water is yeah. I' If he was to keep it or not, because it does from what I remember vaguely, it does break some of the rfcs. Yeah, I' 

Speaker 3  (10:06)
Okay? So In a general, smtp profile hosts would normally be local, correct or local sorry. 

Speaker 2  (10:18)
Exceed profiles S and TP profiles are typically used for sending email out from this system or routing to one of those profiles, and the host would indicate in the case of sending an email out what you want the sending system to be. So when we specify host local host, we are saying generate the email on this system. 

Speaker 3  (10:43)
Is it okay? Does it matter the delivery type? 

Speaker 2  (10:51)
Do you mean the puffer cue type? 

Speaker 3  (10:53)
Do you see the mask screen? I don't see your pop-up window. Oh, you don't, I'm sharing? 

Speaker 2  (11:00)
You're sharing the browser only, and when you add it and new window, it did not allow that to be shared. Okay, Guinea, so when you get a pop-up, if you are sharing the browser, only we don't see the pop-up. 

Speaker 4  (11:12)
All right. If 

Speaker 3  (11:17)
You can just stop sharing and then share again. 

Speaker 4  (11:28)
If you're using chromejet at the top of the new window, you have an option to share this 

Speaker 3  (11:38)
Okay. 

Speaker 4  (11:39)
On the new pop-up 

Speaker 3  (11:43)
Yeah, I don't see it. But maybe it's because I stopped sharing all that 

Speaker 4  (11:49)
Yeah, you have to share. 

Speaker 3  (11:51)
Is sure okay? So now That's Thank you, I'm 

Speaker 4  (11:59)
So if you click on something that the jury to pop-up on the new pop-up, you should have An option to share that pop-up 

Speaker 3  (12:09)
I don't see it. It's okay, I'll share the whole screen. Give me a sec. 

Speaker 4  (12:17)
Okay, this next s*****, shi. 

Speaker 3  (12:19)
I'm sure I'm Okay, you see the pop-up here, let me move it over. Maybe that'll be better. So it says delivery type, and it is a balanced ordered 

Speaker 2  (12:37)
You wanna do a load balanced? So from multiple proposed systems, it will balance it across the agents, okay. 

Speaker 3  (12:45)
The main reason is because when we're going to be doing some auto replies, right? And this is why we're looking into configuring multiple smtp profiles. So I would put something on the lines of the front field as this right There's a different sender. 

Speaker 2  (13:02)
You can put the Frome address as anything you want. 

Speaker 3  (13:05)
All right, okay. And then display name so on and so forth each. Although does it really matter? 

Speaker 3  (13:13)
Yes, it should be matching The Domain of the sender. 

Speaker 2  (13:17)
Typically, yes, okay. 

Speaker 3  (13:22)
I put this one the S and TP addressed. 

Speaker 2  (13:25)
You don't, you don't need to fill that out if this is going to be used for sending only that I can stay in blank because that would be, if you were changing the recipient with a profile. 

Speaker 3  (13:37)
Okay, okay, okay, that's pretty much all I needed for this one. We tested the auto replies, but because the system But we're receiving system by now is rejecting because of the mark. So We can't quite complete it yet, but I do see in the tracking logs that a reply has been set and just being rejected at this point in time, not shiny. 

Speaker 3  (14:06)
And I think that was It for me. 

Speaker 4  (14:15)
40 other estimates, but it 

Speaker 3  (14:23)
Yeah, I think we're good for now. 

Speaker 2  (14:29)
Other issues that people want to bring up 

Speaker 3  (14:33)
Oh, that Daniel. It came a little late, but Then, it's going to reach out to. I've got his name already. 

Speaker 3  (14:47)
To see what is actually on the physical boxes that were sent I see. Still there, I think he dropped. Oh, I think he dropped or something else, maybe okay? 

Speaker 3  (15:01)
Okay? 

Speaker 1  (15:02)
All right, was that the question was a dual Dix, or 

Speaker 3  (15:07)
Well, I don't wonder how many actual nicks it has because anyone 

Speaker 2  (15:11)
I would get that there's, you know, at least 3 physical ports outside of that. I Don 't know what the the specs are. 

Speaker 3  (15:21)
Okay, do people tend to use the fault warrants with it? Or 

Speaker 2  (15:27)
I have not heard of organizations doing that. Generally, if people are concerned about network connectivity, they have alerts on the switch side. 

Speaker 3  (15:40)
Well, sometimes I don't know how often, but sometimes they replace switches. So if we have a vol tolerance or redundancy, then, you know, we won't have any issues with them, bringing down a switch. 

Speaker 2  (15:55)
Of course, and whatever hardware vendor we're shipping out appliances, as I would be very surprised if we didn't have some kind of Nick pairing capabilities. Okay, and most organizations will set it up, so that you have a paired set of nicks and one goes to one switch infrastructure, and one goes to a different switch infrastructure, and that way if one switch goes down, it's still processing, just fine. 

Speaker 3  (16:24)
Is it worthwhile to separate the like in an inbound and outbound physical Nick set up or 

Speaker 2  (16:32)
So I don't think so, but that's up to you for inbound and outbound email. I don't really see a benefit for it for inbound and outbound TCP traffic. In general, you would want to refer to a networking expert for that. 

Speaker 3  (16:46)
Okay, no, no, because of the previous. Hardware, it was a little bit easier to distinguish between inbound and outbound with the 2 knicks. So I'm just wondering how this one's going to work in that sense, right? 

Speaker 2  (17:01)
It depends entirely on how you have defined inbound in outbound, one of the concepts that I have come across is that there really is no inbound and outbound in email. Directionality depends entirely on, if you are routing via mx record, or if you are a routing via a static cable entry on proof point, for example, inbound will let you set a static cable entry to say. All right, for emails to td.com. 

Speaker 2  (17:32)
Route it to TD - com.mail.protection.outlook.com, and then for everything else you would be routing via the MX record, so I try to get away from directionality and go by instead domains essentially. 

Speaker 3  (17:58)
Okay, thank you Oh, there was one more thing because I think the, you know, I think you were helping us doing the dlp relay part right? Because the outbound email was a Pat - td.com. I did end up adding the not. 

Speaker 3  (18:23)
That tomato means to the To the embarrass, ok. And that seems to have done it, because there seems to have been a rule. In place? 

Speaker 3  (18:37)
What was that rule? 

Speaker 2  (18:40)
And Jill and just as an FYI going into the Zoom chat is The specific grid on hardware specs from our internal article. It looks like all of them have 2RJ451 gigabyte ports built into the appliance itself, and then 4RJ451 gigabyte ports on pci cards. And with eye drack, which is the Dell appliance management system, you would be able to set up Nick pairing with those 

Speaker 3  (19:17)
Okay, so there's in total, 6, yes, Daniel, actually, Daniel was thinking there was 6, so, but we needed, okay, sounds good. 

Speaker 3  (19:40)
Give me 1 second. 

Speaker 2  (19:42)
Yeah, of course. 

Speaker 5  (20:16)
I want you to prevent the issues like that pleased. Why do you think that's 

Speaker 3  (20:25)
We need to do it to do a search I think the question I have is, does that to allow really does the In bad? But where I'll have to be there, descending domain 

Speaker 2  (20:50)
Now allow relay is based on the fqdn of the server or IP address of the sending system. You don't have to have an inbound mail. Table entry for an allowed relay entry to be present. 

Speaker 3  (21:03)
I did see a rule that triggered as well in a second search. Maybe 

Speaker 3  (21:35)
So okay, let me share once again if you don't mind, please So the reason why I thought you might have needed this was, and then after adding this I see this. My domain_from Ah, yes, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (21:59)
That's for inbound S PF D came in demarc, checking specifically email fraud defense, that's so that we can identify domains that are pointing to be" -un", your domains. The purpose of that is, for inbound, male, you may want to have separate policies. In fact, you almost certainly will want to have a separate policies for general domains i.e., the internet Yahoo, Microsoft, whoever and for your organizations, domains, and this is so that you can get more aggressive with your own inbound email. 

Speaker 3  (22:36)
So in theory, I could just delete this, and we should still be able to, we won't have any issues. 

Speaker 2  (22:42)
Keep in mind deleting those is going to 

Speaker 3  (22:45)
No, just this one, because this is the one I added. 

Speaker 2  (22:49)
Okay, the mydomains from is being built off of this table right just as an FYI. D. 

Speaker 4  (23:00)
But what was the problem with this s***? 

Speaker 3  (23:01)
No, no, no I just wonder if I actually had to. At the the The inbound or not because you know how we were having issues with the allow relay Yeah, so I added this so maybe it's a coincidence because after I added this this thing to work. So maybe it was a timing thing rather than me. 

Speaker 3  (23:24)
Adding this. 

Speaker 4  (23:26)
So just remove it. Yeah, let's just remove it. 

Speaker 3  (23:28)
And all women just see. Yeah 

Speaker 4  (23:32)
I can tell let's test again. Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (23:36)
Okay, I'm pretty much good now at this point. If you have any questions, oh, the next, I don't think you were here, but there's 6 knicks, okay? When they get you onboard and for on A 

Speaker 4  (23:54)
And that does, there's a special portfolio, right? 

Speaker 2  (24:00)
I drag it, it's de. 

Speaker 4  (24:02)
Ah, I drank, okay, sorry. Yes, yeah, so that's so so there's different. Okay. 

Speaker 4  (24:07)
And I remember that you mentioned this before the there's no dedication management board any and any of those interface, they can be used for management. Correct? And they can be teamed, right? 

Speaker 2  (24:22)
They should be able to through eye drag okinaw. Yeah, I' 

Speaker 4  (24:31)
So Judd, I think that we should be good from that perspective, because if we use we only realistically need 4 nicks, right? 

Speaker 3  (24:40)
I mean, maybe even 2, unless you want to change the routing, in some way right? For if we still want to bounce out about, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (24:52)
I'm thinking that that's going to make it cleaner. All right, to make it so to have in bound and outbound deliveries, like for delivery via a different interface. 

Speaker 3  (25:04)
I don't know, I think it might work slightly better and might be easier in terms of a network routing, where they have to gnat. 

Speaker 4  (25:15)
Yes, yeah, there's that way they can keep it clean, and that we can just make it obvious, which one is the outbound, and which one is the inbound? Yeah, yeah, okay. You have 2 more minutes and I have to jump together meeting just so open. 

Speaker 3  (25:33)
Yeah, I'm not sure if we have much else right now. 

Speaker 4  (25:40)
Did we get all the answers that we needed? Are we still waiting anything from then if we have him here? 

Speaker 3  (25:45)
No, he stepped me through the deleting the receipt. Headers, I'm gonna try that out a little bit later as well, so I think we're good I've gone through most of the rules already, and we pretty much have A We've done A I guess an example of it tests an example of it already. Yeah, and some of the other ones we just need to retest again because of the the IPS. 

Speaker 3  (26:18)
I mean, the teammark settings. 

Speaker 4  (26:21)
Yeah, so I'm having a chance tonight to to. To add some changes and the S PF for W etc, right? So I'll change. 

Speaker 4  (26:33)
I'll check it tonight, but by tomorrow we should be able to we should be propagated, we should be able to test it. 

Speaker 3  (26:40)
Yeah, sounds good. 

Speaker 4  (26:42)
Awesome, didn't yeah? So I don't have anything else if anybody on the line, they have other things that they would like to talk about. Both me and jet were good, we have to jump into ADR meeting. 

Speaker 4  (26:58)
So if anybody wants to talk about something else, please go ahead, if not, we can give everybody some time back. 

Speaker 6  (27:08)
I've got a question that just wanted to bring up, it doesn't have to be solved here, we don't have to I Don' Review it. I don't think we're prepared for it, but from a governance side after we get, you know, across, finished line with this, and it becomes production material, is there a way for You need to do like a configurative monitoring to API access for what proof point has in place in the cloud. Yeah, we said something we can do. 

Speaker 2  (27:40)
We have a cloud API, and you can look for specific events within your CM to see if things are changing. 

Speaker 6  (27:51)
So it wouldn't be looking for events. We want to queer that configured 

Speaker 2  (27:56)
Yeah, events should be logged. When can take changes are made? 

Speaker 1  (28:01)
Yeah, like an audit trailer. You might be saying, right? 

Speaker 6  (28:05)
So like, like, for example, I'll just take something at random, say we, you know, we have to have demarcan forced, right? It's a that's a control we have. We would want to say, you know, for this control, we're going to query this part of the config. 

Speaker 6  (28:22)
And proof point cloud, is it currently enabled? Actively enabled. 

Speaker 2  (28:33)
I don't think we have any way of querying like what are the real-time settings, but any changes to configurations would be logged via the API, and you could track that 

Speaker 6  (28:46)
Okay, yeah, so that would still I assume, flow down to spawn today. So I guess would be, is there like a is there an export from the Confederate? We would get like a file that contains all of the configuration. 

Speaker 6  (29:01)
No, so you don't have an exporter that can fig, and we can't query the config that they're actively running config through an API, so the only way to do it would be in the dashboard taking screenshots. 

Speaker 2  (29:15)
No, the the log API will notify if there are any changes to the confederation. 

Speaker 1  (29:20)
No, he's if he would say, preconditioned, Dan, like as of today, not a Chad. 

Speaker 6  (29:25)
I have to, so I have to collect evidence to reflect that to config that we expect to be there is present, okay. And so like from a governance perspective, we're going to say, deanmark has to be enabled, enforced actively. 

Speaker 2  (29:42)
Is this something that needs to be ongoing and repeated? 

Speaker 1  (29:46)
Yes, yes, yeah, they get audited today as someone by third parties or something that it's enforced right or something like that. 

Speaker 6  (29:52)
I'm going to be audited from my second line, and then potentially on some, you know, unknown schedule, the regulators may come in and do something, you know, so we have to be prepared for that, and we have to present evidence to support that the requirements that we have from a security perspective are enabled, and how we're affecting those 

Speaker 2  (30:15)
There may be one of the APIs where you can query specific settings. I'll look into that I know we have it with our S ER product, for example, you can do get requests and query specific settings. 

Speaker 6  (30:33)
Yeah, so I don't, if there's an API dock, that kind of goes in detail of what's available in there, I'll take a look at it. But it sounds to me like maybe this guy's gonna come up before, but it is something in the fintech industry. That ISIS expected. 

Speaker 2  (30:52)
In the Zoom chat is the log API article and then the PDF file down towards the bottom of that goes over all of the different things that are possible via that log API. Hi, I'm Alex, looking to see if one of our active control APIs would have information of what you're looking for. 

Speaker 6  (31:13)
And just curious like how how challenging would it be to have a feature that that could, you know, provide some export of what the config is like X? 

Speaker 2  (31:24)
That would have to be an RFE that's that's not something I can answer from a product standpoint. 

Speaker 6  (31:30)
Okay, is there a is there a way to do like a softening query on that with before we go formal? 

Speaker 2  (31:37)
I could ask, but the product team is going to say. Have the customer submit an rfa. 

Speaker 6  (31:43)
Okay, all right, fair enough, we'll do that. Ok, but that was my question sounded like somebody else had something they wanted to bring up to. 

Speaker 1  (31:54)
I had a tiny one, but it's not pressing it kind of tags along with yourself. Sir, is Dan you think anything like these type of Query's like, about, this might be something you could find in a community form. 

Speaker 2  (32:09)
Absolutely. The log APIs is in the communities, and that's the article I just pasted. 

Speaker 1  (32:15)
All right, because I was thinking Joel, if you know, if you wanted to go soft query, just to kind of out of curiosity, I could do some searches too if I have time later, but just I would encourage you to go out into the proof point community and maybe say, are there are there other institutions doing similar things. And sometimes you find the answers out there 

Speaker 6  (32:37)
Yeah, II just, you know, there are no hard feelings here, but I just assume that you guys did a lot of work with the banks and this has come up and it's not, we could find somebody in the industry that you're using, that's using proofpoint that you work with maybe. It's 

Speaker 1  (32:53)
Yeah, not to just beat this in the ground, but when I worked in another industry similar to yours, we used a vendor that we got a tool from that had to go kind of do a third party that had to do it for Anyway, when I worked in compliance, I can appreciate what you're faced in any events. The only question I jet I sent you on Daniel an email a little while ago of If it isn't clear enough, feel free to respond via email, if you have any questions, I'm just trying to get caught up to where what I miss for a couple weeks and just want to just sync with yourself. 

Speaker 1  (33:28)
Daniel, and Dave just to make sure I have everything Karen okay. Jeb might have already left cause he had to go to another meeting, but just in case yeah, I' 

Speaker 7  (33:41)
Oh, I think there are all 3 of them are gone. It's meeting 

Speaker 1  (33:45)
I need, yeah, they had a Golf. 

Speaker 7  (33:46)
Yeah, it's because we're having some internal Let's say issues with our with the placement of those physical devices in our data center. And that's basically we need those to move forward, which is why they dropped. 

Speaker 1  (34:07)
I understand it, isn' yeah, i' 

Speaker 7  (34:13)
But I think we're good Any other questions? I can give you back all that time. Today I have your tylee took up. 

Speaker 3  (34:25)
Thank you, alright. 

Speaker 2  (34:29)
Thanks, thank you, bye. 
