
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Some time ago, but now it's I'm a little bit more motivated to get that going sooner than later. 

Speaker 2  (00:09)
Hopefully, it's still because nothing to do I do prove quite, oh I do not know that. 

Speaker 1  (00:16)
Just I'm just getting, I'm just getting all that's, that's all just age. Okay, okay, happy before. Yeah, thanks man. 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
Thank you. So our digit, last week you mentioned you wanted to just throw some updates my way, and then pour, do you want to go from top to bottom like we did last week. What approach do you think you want to take today? 

Speaker 2  (00:46)
It doesn't bother, I think you prefer top to bottom, just to make sure we don't miss anything, but last week we actually dubbed missing a little part from The palace section, maybe we want to do it backwards. This is time just to make sure none of 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
Well, sure, whatever. Remember where it works? So it wouldn't go up. 

Speaker 1  (01:03)
Yeah, that way. Yeah, you're right. If it go backwards that way, we have more time to make sure we didn't miss anything correct? 

Speaker 1  (01:10)
Okay, okay. So we so we have a handover section here, which starts in August through October. 

Speaker 2  (01:19)
Yeah, Leslie was there. I don't think it's going to be told because we probably look October September, something like Around the time, so that looks fine. We change it. 

Speaker 2  (01:30)
After airport. Engaging deployment when you have here, ocos. Sorry. 

Speaker 2  (01:40)
Hey, you deploy, man. So trying to see what they have this July. No, that's not gonna happen in July. 

Speaker 2  (01:47)
I would say it's changing from September to December. You gotta keep in mind right for us. To be able to deploy the air game, we gotta deploy the air to the very least. 

Speaker 2  (02:00)
We need to have so far. 

Speaker 1  (02:04)
Final group, yeah, I took this originally from from from your Ok, from your spreadsheet some time ago, so 

Speaker 2  (02:13)
But we'll go. 

Speaker 3  (02:15)
Howard would in this setup and testing PR testing right now. 

Speaker 2  (02:19)
Cerebral testing will be, yeah, I would say it's sour, yeah, yeah, so that's yeah, you can leave it as you like, that's fine. Oh, yeah, okay, so we can change the spot. The empire set it up from probably September. 

Speaker 1  (02:36)
I think yeah, so I think that's what we said, right? And your sheet originally was the pilot All the pilots here okay. 

Speaker 2  (02:51)
Yes, please. 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
Okay, so I changed that to September. Make it the first eh, yeah? 

Speaker 2  (02:57)
Past and refers to through September 12th. Yeah, September. Yes, he was 2 months to do that. 

Speaker 1  (03:04)
So to mid-october, or the end of 

Speaker 2  (03:08)
Ahead of October, we will probably dump sooner than that. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (03:12)
So this this gap here, August, the month of August, or is this going to go set up in testing? 2 to August strength, correct? Yeah, got right, okay. 

Speaker 1  (03:26)
Okay, so that will make it August. Just put 20 eighths. 

Speaker 2  (03:30)
You can probably split it from may until August because we started the testing in May. Well, it's a boundary Oklahoma. 

Speaker 1  (03:40)
Let's reflect. May down fifth or fourth. Something like that. 

Speaker 1  (03:45)
Whatever 

Speaker 2  (03:46)
Yeah, something like that. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (03:47)
Okay, and then over here It wasn't to the farm. Not to know. And that's how it all begins. 

Speaker 1  (04:01)
Okay, so then the August September October And then here, this would The face phase 12 and 3. 

Speaker 2  (04:12)
Yeah, those will be a little bit more delay. Remember we supposed to be production ready by November? I don't think we're going to deploy phase one at least onto mid January. 

Speaker 1  (04:28)
Okay. Mid January, correct, okay, so we just go up, put the third 

Speaker 2  (04:38)
Yeah, remember they said messaging right? So we are. We're supposed to be production ready for messaging by November. 

Speaker 2  (04:45)
What messaging still have to do more work on their side? To be a 100% 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Okay, so jurors, not allowing me do this right now, but so if we say January here, then this would be probably March. You think, or 

Speaker 2  (05:00)
No, the 3 faces would be between January and March. The 2 other Okay, so that's just never finished everything by March. Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (05:09)
Oh, yes. I'll throw March 26th. And then this then I can change this now. 

Speaker 1  (05:14)
So this would be, I think, you said mid, January 

Speaker 4  (05:18)
So how, from a from a pilot perspective, how much how many endpoints are you thinking? I mean, a couple 100 

Speaker 2  (05:26)
Probably everybody on the broader or Robert Brown. Yeah, we will probably throw a couple of annual businesses there. We will probably throw A couple of interviews have said, we will probably throw ideas some of the ideas, guys, right? 

Speaker 2  (05:47)
Well, it's going to be more than a 100 That part with control, like a 1000 different endpoints. 

Speaker 1  (05:55)
Look, Joan, make that comment in here about a 1000 

Speaker 2  (05:58)
No, no right now. 

Speaker 1  (06:00)
Not right now, not too much commitment. And so they and the end date, Howard would behingch No, no I meant for the phase one. 

Speaker 2  (06:12)
Phase one I mean phase one takes about a week right, so each phase is about a week, so phase one, let's say next week, we can start phase one and by Friday should be done, then the following week. We schedule the next show and everything so in total it's going to be like a 3 or four weeks of changes right? Okay that that extra amount of time from, you know, from a very to March is just in case we run into we are situation right, but we should be able to figure that out during the pilot, ok. 

Speaker 2  (06:45)
Okay. We might be able to do this sooner as well. 

Speaker 4  (06:51)
So are you thinking packaging and deliver to secm right? 

Speaker 2  (06:56)
Yes, that's the way well, we don't know, still today, we could do scm, we could do life update, but scm would be the first one, the Hugh. Yeah, we'll figure it out. Well let you know. 

Speaker 4  (07:13)
Engage another theme from employing a moment 

Speaker 2  (07:17)
Yeah, we are ready. Not all guys. Hope we work with them already. 

Speaker 2  (07:21)
So 

Speaker 4  (07:22)
Okay, bad. If 

Speaker 1  (07:23)
So any of these phases like we said the end of March, but it kind of puts us into early tip. Here with that for now. 

Speaker 2  (07:33)
Yes, we're good for now. We can adjust today. We still haven't 

Speaker 1  (07:36)
Goyah, ya. Okay, so we're sorry. 

Speaker 2  (07:43)
Look at the diploma, as the last thing we want to do right, like, we want to have all the piece of weather. When you push the engine to those guys, it's because, hey, we're ready, we're going to come. Yesterda. 

Speaker 2  (08:01)
I'm sorry, I Don' 

Speaker 1  (08:04)
Pablo omarti's in progress. 

Speaker 2  (08:11)
Hi apology. 

Speaker 1  (08:13)
Your dogs are hungry again. 

Speaker 2  (08:15)
Yeah, I know one of them we're having is that every time one of I we took, we take one of them each week to what you call this team, the dock salon. 

Speaker 1  (08:28)
So Michael excited. 

Speaker 2  (08:30)
No, my girlfriend calls to the house. I can pick them up, so they just get excited to see her next. 

Speaker 1  (08:38)
Yeah, they're doing doggy things. Yeah, okay, yeah. Scanner infrastructure. 

Speaker 2  (08:46)
It's kind of infrastructure. I do have a goal. I'm not too sure of a dish one Um, I think we what we're waiting here for this to be to move forward. 

Speaker 2  (08:58)
Right? I chat I was still working on the placement. Do we know where we want to put them or 

Speaker 5  (09:04)
Yeah, I have two different engagements with the IP, like in engine architecture. I need to put those tickets 

Speaker 2  (09:15)
Yeah, so we can move these 2 in progress. 

Speaker 1  (09:22)
And when did it start? 

Speaker 2  (09:24)
Probably like a month ago, Chad. Keep on in there something like that. Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (09:32)
Okay, we touched on that. We start talking about it a month ago, but we only got access to the platform last week. 

Speaker 5  (09:42)
Okay, this is TSP RE scanner. 

Speaker 1  (09:48)
Infrastructure, I'm 

Speaker 5  (09:53)
And I'm posting the tickets if you want to have any comets, because it's probably good to track 

Speaker 1  (09:59)
Yeah, and and what kind of I don't think it would apply to any of these stories. So I think we talked about this last week and uh Do I need another story in here? 

Speaker 2  (10:10)
So let me see what you have on the ESPN, the ESPN, you have a scanner infrastructure, you should have We have policies. You should have also, uh, uh uh. It's kind of bossy's eyes. 

Speaker 2  (10:27)
Do you have integrations? 

Speaker 1  (10:31)
Okay, scanner policies scanner integration. 

Speaker 2  (10:35)
Because the group of integration that, you know, this codes that we 'Ve been getting pulled for we mail that the train to integrate with cyber art, right? 

Speaker 1  (10:44)
It's all right, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (10:45)
Okay, that's okay, that's. By the way, there's also gotta be integrations with assured because we need to be able to scan Trip on online lyr. I have so having an interpersonal section, and then a couple of stories like 147 Aragon, and the only one for chip on in line will make sure that that will ensure that we can track those items. 

Speaker 1  (11:09)
Ok, so you set cyber And the other one was was Azure, would you say? 

Speaker 2  (11:15)
Cyber arc chair pon online and yes, there's also need to be AD integration. Sorry, there's 3 other there you go. Okay, so I need to run for a SIM. 

Speaker 2  (11:28)
Okay, I love the shirt about that. I think we can pull the juice as based on the integration base of what I was reading, I don't believe the support of the skin part of thing but I might be wrong, oh okay okay yeah. Yes, we need integration with the S pluck. 

Speaker 2  (11:51)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (11:52)
Oh, okay, splunk, got Okay, so that's so that's 4 of them, so I got sober sharepoint 80 and splunk. 

Speaker 2  (11:59)
Yeah, there's one more, and this is applicable for everyone, right? We need to integrate this at the end. Don't worry. 

Speaker 2  (12:06)
Actually, don't even add it to a project. We have to integrate this with with something called AMHL. Which is kind of when the AMH is now used to be the former guy, the name What's in the mother feed that we pulled somewhere? 

Speaker 2  (12:25)
Yes, thank you, okay. 

Speaker 1  (12:30)
I love you, okay, so I don't need to do anything with that as far as the story goes or anything like that, correct? 

Speaker 2  (12:36)
No, it is. I mean, I'm striking this from somewhere else okinaw. Okay, we get an email asking us to do it, so I'll just ignoring that email for now, literally Okay, you mean it's parked? 

Speaker 2  (12:55)
Sarah, that's the other word. 

Speaker 1  (12:59)
Okay, so Chad, the 2 links you sent me here are those are those are they part of what we just talked about? As far as those are scanner policies is that correct, or is that 

Speaker 5  (13:12)
Yeah, see the club, the containerized scanner placement. That one is the 466 task you have there on prime scanner using doctor container. 

Speaker 1  (13:24)
Okay, we're 66 equals container scanner. Okay? 

Speaker 5  (13:31)
And then the other one is the 465. Cloud scanner, which is like, set eyes or side cardbo. 

Speaker 1  (13:40)
Is your slide car? Okay, thank you that helps 

Speaker 5  (13:44)
If someone's engaged on both of those may need to push them along touch if we want to have like, if we're ready to have that conversation to have, you know, you Do next steps? 

Speaker 2  (13:56)
Yeah, I'm and so ready, Chad, I've been trying to figure this out for the last 3 days yesterday and late until prelate, and Fernand and I have been working on this container, the whole morning, right? We train to visit our lab to make this happen because obviously we don't know what we're doing from the debt side right. So if we could have those conversations so we can start getting some guidance from how we want to shift this. 

Speaker 2  (14:21)
That would be great because as if right now, we're running into issues left and right and We can just, we just, we don't have formal infrastructure, right? So yeah, so 

Speaker 3  (14:31)
When we got the container up and running, at least right, so 

Speaker 5  (14:35)
Yeah, on Dr. Dogger on a server, right? 

Speaker 3  (14:37)
And we're running independent doctor on us. 

Speaker 5  (14:40)
Yeah, I think I think that's the only choice but we still have to probably do an exception to get that like approved for patent product, but I think that's the right, that's probably we're going to end up, but that'll cover the Docker's side. Not like the container scanner, then the more I think the other one is the share point scanner, like if they, if the only option is to use the sidecar, that we still have to sort that one out. So 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
Yeah, you know what worries me about that, I sit up a chat, I look at the documentation, and it seems that they want to have the ability to run or run compute devices, basic computers and not too sure how that's going to fly with E. But I 

Speaker 5  (15:21)
Yeah, so check out the ticket I posted, because I tried to summarize that, and the person I engaged in massud, he engaged in another team to ask them for cloud engineering. So cloud engineering and infrastructure architecture both there, to help answer the question, even if the answer is going to be no, at least we get the answer. All right, so one step at a time 

Speaker 2  (15:47)
Yeah, what's rain there like a wow, really do you wanna manage? I will compute the storage and then the send us another file to say, hey, this is how much money do you will be spending to be charged and decide what the charges are going to look like in your invoice, like, wow, no that's not going to work 

Speaker 5  (16:05)
It's interesting, because on the other hand if we deployed a vm, we'd be paying anyway. So so in a way they're being more efficient, but on the other side like that's not like we don't work that way, right? We don't, we don't want you to play things on our side, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (16:17)
Exactly, exactly, alright, well, we'll throw it out, but yes, if we can have those conversations like who do we need to initiate that like in charities that sometimes we can engage with that, we need the pms or just grab the name of the person I'm booking call or other works. 

Speaker 5  (16:34)
Let me reach out to a sewer. Let me just touch base with them and then try to get a call schedule probably next week. That's okay. 

Speaker 5  (16:41)
And if I need PM help out, reach out to you environment date, but I think it should be okay. Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
So I think they ate, this is we're penning. Information from from scale, correct for policy stigs. 

Speaker 2  (17:02)
Yeah, that's my understanding is this is part of the csp at some point they're going to go back and say yes, these are concerns, or in order for you to move to production, you need to answer all these different questionable proofs that you can do XYZ as part of and they will decide this thing that's my understanding. 

Speaker 1  (17:24)
This one we added last week, which was The functional capabilities and gaps Okay, so I think in here added. I think this is some of the yeah, this is some of the male Or Gat spreadsheets and so forth. Right? 

Speaker 1  (17:44)
So there's some attachments within the Then, the applicant. 

Speaker 2  (17:49)
Okay, so you can set this as a startup because we're starting identifying gaps on this. I would say, assign it to me. Allocate resources and list change the resources. 

Speaker 2  (18:08)
Yes, as anatomy. Yeah, we 're here, yeah. And can you look at resources? 

Speaker 2  (18:14)
So no I'll figure it out, don't worry. 

Speaker 3  (18:23)
Are you talking about Technical limitations are actual gaps. 

Speaker 2  (18:30)
So this this is gonna allow for both right capability, limitation gaps, anything that is mission for us right, so this will account for that API. That situation is the 

Speaker 3  (18:42)
The one API key for all scanners. 

Speaker 1  (19:06)
Okay, so this this story is basically the activities right? So they Okay. Yeah, I think you're going to be at your, you're going to track these requirements over here. 

Speaker 1  (19:24)
I think I believe 

Speaker 2  (19:26)
Yes, maybe I haven't wanted to check things making certain stories. I might just do that. I just need to see what the interactions they have, which at the end towards the end of the call, I'll ask for something that's likely to have a commitment, but I want to, let's pull on in that 

Speaker 1  (19:46)
Yeah, okay, alright, so I'll finish these updates later. Ok, so that sounds good. Okay, then the cyber arc business here isn' 

Speaker 2  (20:02)
That's, that's been progress right. You have to sign that to I think the second jury is like it' No, it's not something that's Yeah, so jury, so why you are y'all? 

Speaker 1  (20:22)
Yeah, which which which area is it? Yeah, first one okay. This was team intake requests, but we did that, right? 

Speaker 1  (20:33)
That's that's that's done. Is there something missing? What's in? 

Speaker 2  (20:41)
Yeah, it's still mixed with a sentiment. You know what assigned to mail? It may not be such a boat, but then you're gonna have to chick, you aren't 

Speaker 1  (20:53)
Yeah, well. Oh, yeah? Yeah, yeah, okay. 

Speaker 1  (21:01)
Yeah, it's in my notes here. There it is. I got it right now. 

Speaker 1  (21:14)
I'm just going to come up on the trip, which Rick's going to come up. Let's have a look at the look 

Speaker 2  (21:22)
Look at that side, I will say, I signed multiple segments now, because they're being very reactive, tasting soda and setting up calls, screening to others around it. Yeah And I would say, I said, all of them asked this time. 

Speaker 1  (21:41)
Odra, I'll start it okay. I'll do that. Okay, I'll just make a note and we'll do that offline. 

Speaker 1  (21:51)
Or 400X. I know you guys like to watch me if this is this. Executive buttons, but 

Speaker 2  (21:59)
Don't trust me, I'd rather be doing something else. But 

Speaker 1  (22:04)
Okay, no problem. Okay, next going up? Yeah? 

Speaker 1  (22:12)
Yeah. A proof point agent wireless setup. 

Speaker 2  (22:18)
That is in progress down any changes in The Times that 

Speaker 6  (22:23)
Yeah, we said last time that This is going to be pretty advanced because we need hard evidence of each I'll interfere, so that's I'm going to reveal itself. When the more and more we get into testing and if we hit snags Where we see that there's actual interference, we would have to record it 

Speaker 2  (22:46)
Yeah, so we maybe what we want to do then is park this onto the top. I actually know the system, the essential, the pilot, right? Maybe during the pilot, when we're going to be able to identify all these issues, right? 

Speaker 2  (23:06)
You feel nice, absolutely, okay. Okay, well, thank you 

Speaker 6  (23:14)
Remember the immutable backup requirement? 

Speaker 2  (23:18)
Yes, or so? 

Speaker 6  (23:19)
It's the DP sac. I'm assuming that would be But we have to figure out the whole storage thing, whether The clowns are going to be here or not, is that pending, that 

Speaker 2  (23:37)
Components that requires the type of syrup, right? So we'll be on this talk somewhere from sematic, Queen. That's the only theme that I have about immigration. 

Speaker 2  (23:51)
Sorry, let's go drag us it up so I don't know that should be on the move, but I don't know if we have more and let's go and now we don't The idea that's okay. 

Speaker 1  (24:06)
All right. Yeah, I got I got more here. Yeah, of course. 

Speaker 1  (24:11)
I'm sorry, see if I can. It changes a little bit, sometimes gets a little wanky. It's don't get everywhere. 

Speaker 2  (24:20)
Yeah, I don't think they actually have any type of tracking or any type of 5 yet that they only had a conversation about, you know, the racy. And so for so that's where we are. What about these, these 2 stories here? 

Speaker 2  (24:46)
So in progress, so skilled progress, we'll say probably the chimp date. 

Speaker 1  (24:58)
So they so that this Python script, conservative alp. Okay, so this can be canceled for the correctional C. 

Speaker 7  (25:08)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (25:08)
We were modified with something 

Speaker 7  (25:10)
Yeah, I mean, if you wrote 

Speaker 2  (25:13)
That's 

Speaker 1  (25:13)
Yeah, I'll just put breeze. 

Speaker 5  (25:20)
Okay, Howard, I'm about to send out an invite from Monday for the utter. A sidecar, okay, just an fy, if you want to afford it to someone from proof point in case they want to, you know, in case you want someone there to answer questions, if any come up. 

Speaker 2  (25:37)
Sounds good. Alex sent her over to Harris and again, maybe 

Speaker 5  (25:44)
No, I could. I couldn't 

Speaker 3  (25:46)
A group, how I go just overwhelmingly, I guess. 

Speaker 1  (25:52)
So if you want me, do you want me to taste change the tape for death deployment and testing 

Speaker 2  (25:58)
Deployment. 10 days and day, 2 next week. Okay, thank you 

Speaker 1  (26:04)
Ok, OK so we'll say the 17th. I Don'. At the point. 

Speaker 1  (26:15)
So this is what I have to change as well, obviously. Just make that the 18th. 

Speaker 2  (26:26)
Actually, I think PAN is to wait a little bit more a little bit, because that's That has to be part of the therapy sign and approval, so we don't know where we're going to get approved. So 

Speaker 1  (26:45)
Okay, I'll be home gone okay, so I Don' 

Speaker 2  (26:51)
Okay, I guess it's 

Speaker 1  (26:55)
Sorry, attitude. 

Speaker 3  (27:00)
Bad attitude, bad attitu. 

Speaker 1  (27:01)
Alright, so anything else under EDM. Okay, moving. Dop policy trackers set up Policy migration, that's in progress. 

Speaker 1  (27:17)
That's been okay, not sure, no shift. 

Speaker 2  (27:20)
Assignments in here Fernando. Pick a name, smile. 

Speaker 1  (27:28)
Bill Fernando came up, so okay. And I'll just mark, I'll just put Fernando for both. Okay, this one here all depends on the single sign on. 

Speaker 1  (27:42)
So There's nothing there, then this one here. I think yeah, I added some stories. Oh, yeah? 

Speaker 1  (27:49)
I brought this out. I think to to death have fraud, right? So we had, we had so for a person, no, it's okay for a single sign on this. 

Speaker 1  (28:03)
Originally, we had dp sac, then I added stories for deep DPS PM. From last week and I you know, same idea right? Just repeat Come on, man just again, okay. 

Speaker 1  (28:17)
And deep beep be suck is in progress. D. P. 

Speaker 1  (28:21)
BPS PM. Is what's happening on not start? Okay, is there? 

Speaker 1  (28:28)
Did you have any planned dates at this point or British marketing says? 

Speaker 2  (28:32)
Yeah, yes, yet, but I can't wait. But I can tell you that what we need for We beside also addresses. PPP, itm, it's the same platform. 

Speaker 2  (28:43)
I think you have to be okay with the same story. Alright, Bob yeah. 

Speaker 1  (28:48)
Okay. So I'll just remove this over here and then okay. 

Speaker 2  (28:51)
Yes, okay. So yeah, okay, thanks good catch. I got it to do. 

Speaker 5  (28:55)
Advocate, hey, Howard from that call was Trevor he's really it's UN, he's unusually interested in the the So I am, like the world mapping tainty group, I don't. I don't know if you want a task for that here to track that. But it's, he's been following up, saying with examples of what he expects. 

Speaker 2  (29:21)
And that's what it is like, right? 

Speaker 5  (29:24)
Yeah, technically it's going to be for all, I think, I think he's just starting with dp sec. It kind of goes to end with the sso stuff like it's 

Speaker 2  (29:35)
OKOK okay, so Yeah, on the desk, so maybe we can add another story. Migrant roll mapping for cesp for the city chicken where I am taking sorry, I can remember which team is part of. 

Speaker 5  (29:52)
Yeah, he's doing the ymci for the csp review, thank you So I guess this could be that. 

Speaker 1  (30:02)
That's you, I think I was the name of Trevor or some 

Speaker 2  (30:15)
I pulled the name from the chat from that surely, sir. Thank you And that applies to, for all the malcods. 

Speaker 1  (30:28)
So so yeah, okay. So for stories, basically, all right. Yes, or one story with 4 miles 

Speaker 2  (30:37)
Let me have a cool story. 

Speaker 1  (30:39)
For students, okay, no forget Yeah, no problem. If you do that, okay, anything else in this section? I Don' 

Speaker 2  (30:57)
I Don'. 

Speaker 1  (30:58)
Okay, and then for D psych, I think we have some activity and progress this one's coming up today. Agent deployment options. 

Speaker 2  (31:09)
This is something that I shouldn't get, that you can depleting options that that part needs to be adjusted or employment, but I would say, change aid, also for maybe putting two weeks out, I think, Fernando to the intelligence challenges back into Today I am consort source. We hit a robot there. 

Speaker 3  (31:31)
I need to submit ACO. I gotta figure out what that is. 

Speaker 2  (31:37)
He wants to change the air. We're caught really potent. Wow, okinaw do you have a detail for now? 

Speaker 2  (31:45)
I can help you yeah, yeah, we'll talk, we'll talk, we'll talk about it better. Draft sounds good. Yeah, I 

Speaker 3  (31:53)
I got a reply today, so we're going to do that. For par, that was for Pat, not for pattern. 

Speaker 1  (32:00)
Yeah, forgotten, yeah, yeah. So so for for for prode I guess we'll do. We'll start that Sometime in July, is that correct? 

Speaker 1  (32:11)
Yeah? So I always say, I don't know if there's some holidays in here. They ate maybe. 

Speaker 2  (32:20)
That's yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (32:22)
Okay, and that would probably be another Probably the end of July, correct? Yeah, I was like, that's okay. Okay, did you want me to change the description in any of these 

Speaker 2  (32:36)
I think you may just in remote agent deployment options. Yeah, okinaw. 

Speaker 1  (32:42)
For all of them, right? All of this, okay Okay, sitting down here. Yes, yes, yeah, okay, okay. 

Speaker 1  (33:07)
And then we have app, and so this relates to blob. 

Speaker 3  (33:17)
By the way, do we add an sso for dspm? Dpml? I know I didn't see it. 

Speaker 3  (33:25)
Maybe I missed it. Yeah, we do DM. L. 

Speaker 3  (33:35)
Oh, for email. 

Speaker 2  (33:36)
Yeah, 468. Yeah, yeah, right. Yeah, yeah, okay, yes, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (33:48)
I'm going to remove this part. The supper pick. 

Speaker 2  (33:53)
Yeah, I mean 

Speaker 3  (33:54)
If we want to get in debt improv on the epm out, yeah, I forget, never mind, okay. 

Speaker 1  (34:02)
Okay, okay, so in here seems to be A few stories. Okay, that's the that's our Peter discussions, manly. Any updates in here that 

Speaker 2  (34:32)
I'm going to think of 

Speaker 1  (34:44)
And this one. 

Speaker 2  (34:50)
This is a game of so it'll be integration. The paint does the same one that we had towards the bottom, so don't be intro. All right, I said, I wish one had you pointed out. 

Speaker 2  (35:00)
Sorry, matth. 

Speaker 1  (35:00)
Oh, no, sir, no, it's okay, I'm i'm up here. Our customer of pop stories, I think that that's that's those ongoing conversations, isn't it? Yeah? 

Speaker 1  (35:09)
Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (35:12)
So what's the next step of this, what are we doing? Do you want me to sit app and go with you and add that so we can go with the options and see how we want to present that to broad view with the work. 

Speaker 4  (35:24)
Yeah, I think we should do that. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (35:26)
Ok, let me set up the Q. 

Speaker 4  (35:28)
You know what, you know, what, all that My lady still is taking the moment. We dropped and the question about pci data that came up. 

Speaker 2  (35:36)
Yeah, that was a big chunk for 

Speaker 4  (35:40)
I don't even know that there was a restriction like that, but 

Speaker 2  (35:44)
Yeah 

Speaker 4  (35:46)
On journal talking about no, yes. 

Speaker 2  (35:49)
Yeah, that's the same thing I was gonna add to like. And we're just spanning out we're talking about upstairs. And then in 2 seconds, everything just goes. 

Speaker 4  (35:56)
My routine, the sacrifice I went silent. 

Speaker 1  (36:01)
Yeah, somebody busted the balloon. 

Speaker 2  (36:03)
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that plan is my crushness, alright? 

Speaker 6  (36:08)
Yeah, so on that is there are blood thing, while it's still being resolved, that's kind of where I was talking about with the immutable backup, like that's going to be in the club, but it's still going to be tds. So is it because it's in the cloud that it doesn't, it's not required, or is it required if it's still part of tds, even though it's in the cloud. 

Speaker 2  (36:33)
Yeah, it's not required because my understanding is that the data that gets sent there. It gets backed up automatically right okay. It doesn't get the leader unless you actually ask him to happen. 

Speaker 2  (36:47)
And even when digital, there's still an application of a 70 years after that, so technically, data could be living in our infrastructure for 14 years after the decision. I really have something like that. Yeah, that's when I was told so that's why they don't require the stuff. 

Speaker 2  (37:03)
There's A I remember playing the condition for the mutability is that it's to actually get you back online. Quicker. This has just made the data. 

Speaker 2  (37:13)
I need some data that doesn't affect application, okay? Sorry. That was not a sake of precision, where we had, I'm sorry 

Speaker 1  (37:28)
Okay, so I guess what we'll need is for now. Maybe I'll put AA note in here like Actually, yeah, okay. It's still under investigation or something like that. 

Speaker 1  (37:39)
Okay, so the training we're gonna push, I think there's some discussion that this is This is going to vote. Or it's kind of add hot training as well. But how do you want to approach that hard? 

Speaker 2  (37:53)
I'm Let me talk to you. Okay, wait, wait, you have these training the bandaries, we'll be talking about training, but hey, we are A couple of months down the road, and we stole those don't have it to train, and we just go, and we're research 

Speaker 3  (38:08)
You haven't really followed up. Where I think maybe we can follow-up with? I don't know navindra or Greg. 

Speaker 3  (38:18)
I think Craig is the one Greg odor I think, yes And the account manager or the yeah, the account manager So then I picked that up, follow-up with him in reverse, too. That was for in class train. 

Speaker 2  (38:34)
All right, glass online, put the band of Yahoo yep, exactly 

Speaker 3  (38:43)
That's 

Speaker 1  (38:45)
Don't go and change the state to you, Fernando or urpe. 

Speaker 3  (38:47)
We're just not learning, okay? 

Speaker 1  (38:50)
Yeah, I know some guys. Yeah, exactly. Because we're There's a good team, okay. 

Speaker 1  (38:57)
So all right, so what I'll do is I'm going to, I'm going to move this somewhere down our list here so that we have the scale the blob and the apps kind of all kind of all together. Look at this. This kind of Kind of looks like a bump in her in our road. 

Speaker 1  (39:15)
Okay, so this one scale challenge, I think this is all those csps that were submitted that leaf, correct. Yes, what happened? 

Speaker 2  (39:25)
What happens with that? There's an outdoor 

Speaker 1  (39:30)
Napoleon queer. 

Speaker 5  (39:32)
You can't, we can't technically go to powder Brod fully until those are done, so at some point they're going to become a big deal. Yeah I don't I'm David, there's a lot of stuff you need, so I'm sure some of it's going on right now, right? Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (39:50)
They're asking Phuchka, if they're looking A cg to do a promise are completed once we have those faiths and then it's going to be just yeah, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (40:05)
So these start dates, they're obviously not valid. Go ahead and eat them black for now. 

Speaker 2  (40:28)
Okay, yeah, I'm can we say that if you still need to do I think they should be moved to doing progress. We got this really status, right? Because we're worried on the airport. 

Speaker 2  (40:40)
Illegal parts that are going to lead to that as a foreign effor. 

Speaker 1  (40:45)
Okay, so I'll mark 33, sorry 435 down to 4. 

Speaker 2  (40:52)
39 in progress, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (40:55)
Okay, no prom and 

Speaker 1  (40:57)
I'll put them in anybody's name. 

Speaker 2  (41:02)
Um, who's the person that's been living there? The skill 

Speaker 4  (41:10)
I mean, usually I find I wanted the ones, but 

Speaker 2  (41:16)
Thank you. Yeah, let's put on The Island. If he's the one that opened most of the teeth and everything right? 

Speaker 2  (41:23)
So I'm 

Speaker 1  (41:24)
Yeah, okay. All right, we'll do that. It's 2:08 Y5 okay, so and oh boy, of these guys here. 

Speaker 1  (41:34)
These ntis, I don't think we want it, but So 

Speaker 2  (41:39)
So they are starting, you just went to the ticket for the fg ii. I 

Speaker 1  (41:43)
Yeah, so it generates all these all these stories, right? And task, so this is auto generated. Yeah, I think I think this may need a separate session, like just to review. 

Speaker 1  (42:00)
What's in here? Like, obviously, well, we got some intake. But well, this is a duplicate because we already have a cyber intake request. 

Speaker 1  (42:18)
Um, U. Okay, I'm not sure what the approach from this one. 

Speaker 2  (42:27)
Let's let's put them in progress because we're working towards that just hand the ticket. Yeah, we'll put us in progress. And then we provide an updates, and if this is applicable or not right, but alaba. 

Speaker 2  (42:38)
I can tell you that these kind of tied up to some of the L2 and 1 records, for example, CMD intake request, I have those rights right? Right, because they were part of my when I submitted the L1 request I had to submit cmd records so that we did add to the system right. So I got those I have those captures so I can give it to you right or I can update them right okay. 

Speaker 2  (43:04)
Some of these might not be appealable, but 

Speaker 1  (43:08)
Right, okay? Yeah, and like we had the cyberark intake, we did that whatever last week or something, okay. Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (43:18)
The issue I just throw them to me in the chat, I can make those updates, so no problem this one I could probably find, but I do have it, it's down, it's in the it's in another story. Okay, so it's just a matter of going through this. And maybe next week when we review, we can You're going to have a look at this again. 

Speaker 2  (43:34)
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 1  (43:37)
Sounds good. Okay. So they so the only thing in the nta that I that I have now is I just put those L2 records that you did Howard, for each mouth. 

Speaker 2  (43:49)
Yeah, then why PPI TM is completed? 

Speaker 1  (43:58)
Itm, which is this one I try to put them in order. So that's done okay. 

Speaker 2  (44:06)
I don't know why the other one wants to tell the progress, but okay. 

Speaker 1  (44:11)
I just mark that it's done this quickly. All right, so anyway, I put the reference number in there is there. Is there a link to check the records or anything like that? 

Speaker 2  (44:25)
Yes, there is. Let me give it to you, give it a decidedly closer. L2 actually had it for a skull L2 Of course, to prove And it's polished, so here it is. 

Speaker 1  (45:00)
Thank you for Why not make those updates? Okay, architecture design. Briefly. 

Speaker 1  (45:15)
I got hope I'll make that update. Chad. I'll make it annoyed that comment that you have your that you have, you're And not published pending scale process And zatara, I marked as done And one more, I'm not sure if this is a book applicable unless you have something else before I move on. 

Speaker 5  (45:43)
Yeah, can you add one more task and the architecture area, or I'm sure that model Yeah, yeah, so a threat model is in school. Based on the criteria for material I've already started it, it's about halfway, and the CSP T might well eventually ask for it too, so 

Speaker 2  (46:02)
Just give me 5 minutes up. 

Speaker 1  (46:04)
And it just comes up craz. 

Speaker 5  (46:10)
Ad high level, it can just say threat model. You say that book. 

Speaker 1  (46:14)
Okay, gotcha. And this is, you can't This one here Anthony, who you had said an email to Dave, and I regards to If you're looking for some epics or stories, is this is this a popcorn to this? 

Speaker 7  (46:41)
Yeah, I believe this is. I was wondering if this is covered anywhere or is it? Is it not part in scope? 

Speaker 7  (46:49)
Kind of thing I remember this was discussed a while ago. No, we're just wondering if anybody's covering this I think Dave told me about it a long time ago. When we summoned me, this happened somewhere in me bye by Which went correct the R UAR UF configuration dearest. 

Speaker 7  (47:12)
Remember, you told me there was some, there was going to be some weekly network meetings. And they needed to this involved Dimitri, or somebody in it. 

Speaker 4  (47:25)
We wanted a consult to talk about how Robotic plant, this is for the demarc. 

Speaker 7  (47:32)
Correct, because I don't think this is D. L. P. 

Speaker 7  (47:36)
This is not DLP this is dmark 

Speaker 2  (47:40)
Something, yeah, this is related to the email the email party, so you probably don't care to the emerging team ingratify this right 

Speaker 1  (47:50)
Okay, okay? So okay. 

Speaker 7  (47:53)
Yeah, because I don't think yeah, this, I don't think this comes under Harvard. This most probably comes under the Philip web, I guess. 

Speaker 1  (47:59)
Oh, I sense odysse. 

Speaker 7  (48:01)
Maybe maybe I should loop in Donna into this. I guess maybe this is Donna. 

Speaker 1  (48:08)
Yeah, dawn out of the yeah. Perfect, right, so I think I'll make I'll make these updates in the background. I'll have to remember my notes are backwards from bottom to top and And I think that's, I think that's about it. 

Speaker 1  (48:28)
Anything else, guys? 

Speaker 2  (48:32)
All right. Um, oh I Don' I actually guess I do. I think we need to try to prove we probably need to have More session, weekly, I hope that we could just do ethical calls, and I don't think that's working right now, we probably need to have weekly calls with them and make sure we get the right support. 

Speaker 2  (49:00)
The ritual I'm asking this is because I've been trying to exchange a call with a group, and it's scheduled this pretty busy, right? So I Don' 

Speaker 4  (49:09)
This one something fixed on their color and every week then 

Speaker 1  (49:13)
Okay, ok, ok, okay. 

Speaker 2  (49:14)
It's like me like sing. It seems that I agree with assigned to a whole bunch of costumes tomorrow waits on his calendar right? So and then and Getting a resource to help us when we are available seems to be challenging. 

Speaker 2  (49:28)
So maybe we need to have something fixed on the calendar. So regardless of what happens, we know we're going to have that call, rather than kidding it bye. Bye So we can actually And our left esteem, or somebody else 

Speaker 4  (49:45)
Perfect, thank you, yes. 

Speaker 2  (49:53)
Fernando, anything that we need the project team support to get some of this stuff going. Did you can recall qe? 

Speaker 3  (50:04)
I think the call will definitely help at least. We have one with the with the data, the dop team, and I think we definitely need one with the other with the other folks. With the DSP M. 

Speaker 5  (50:19)
Side of the house. 

Speaker 3  (50:22)
Yeah, at least at least once a week. I know. We already have 2 But with the endpoint team On a Wednesday, we can I think we have it about Tuesdays and Fridays. 

Speaker 3  (50:36)
If you want a windside, we can play that yeah. 

Speaker 2  (50:42)
And one of the big challenges that we can have, babe, and Myron is the APIs situation in the spn. They only had to, they have a section where it makes you believe that we can use multiple abi keys, but it's essentially just one single abi key right? So that could be a single point of failure because in order for them. 

Speaker 2  (51:05)
Yeah, you notice for you. This scanners, you need to provide the API key and secret, right? And if somebody goes and modifies that or clicks on the bottom by mistakes. 

Speaker 2  (51:18)
Guess what? Every single scanner will stop working. 

Speaker 3  (51:21)
Right, cause the kid gets regenerated, and the old key stuffs work. We test it that 

Speaker 4  (51:31)
Hey, zelensky, is that 

Speaker 2  (51:33)
I mentioned it yesterday. 

Speaker 3  (51:36)
We need to raise it to John and Joseph, because this is not that that's Not acceptable from the security Sir, I would say Coming from semantic, we have the ability to create multiple keys. For a sad solution and assign specific roles or where in the And through the API, Queen 

Speaker 4  (52:00)
Which data storage that we're going to be in Thai? 

Speaker 2  (52:04)
Tapping into so one key 

Speaker 3  (52:07)
For all scanners, that's just that doesn't know nomin. 

Speaker 2  (52:11)
Thank you for everything. They're just a scanned, right. Even they sabotage integration with me to run on the desk and key and if jury goes and messed up, because I'm pretty sure this is going to need it to change something, right if it goes and change it, that's going to mess up everything. 

Speaker 2  (52:24)
Else that we have done 

Speaker 3  (52:26)
Is that correct the same for for 

Speaker 2  (52:30)
We'll talk about it right guys. Okay? Yeah, so it's like the amount of the rain type of thing when rain covers, everything else, right? 

Speaker 5  (52:41)
He even Evans, even if that wasn't accidentally changed even on a scheduled change that would be hard to deal with, because you'd have to go around and update all the downstream systems at the same time or however, with that new Keynes. Yes 

Speaker 2  (52:58)
It's painful. 

Speaker 3  (53:01)
Even though I think Turkey is only for initial deployment right of the scanners, at least 

Speaker 2  (53:09)
Every time you're from the campaigner, you have to provide those those parameters. 

Speaker 5  (53:15)
This is all related to DSP. I'm still right, the scanning, so yeah. Paul is more and more important. 

Speaker 5  (53:21)
It sounds like he's 

Speaker 3  (53:28)
And the title says API ts So you can only generate one at a time. 

Speaker 1  (53:37)
Did you want me to add something in here? As A 

Speaker 2  (53:41)
No, no, no. So good, I think it wouldn't be up to that person called limitation. Don't worry. 

Speaker 2  (53:55)
I don't think that. We are good at finding issues. 

Speaker 1  (53:59)
Well, I'm sure that it's not to know that. That's a constant, yeah? 

Speaker 2  (54:07)
Ok, alright is yes chest, but you need any system from performing anything that you that used to wait in front of. Anything that we can bring during the call tomorrow. 

Speaker 5  (54:17)
You know, I think we're on the same page, right? I don't have any new questions. It's just the stuff we already know to deal with sidecar, and all that ok, perfect. 

Speaker 2  (54:29)
Alright, I think we made it on time then. 

Speaker 1  (54:31)
Yeah, yeah, thanks very well, very cool. Alright. We'll have a wonderful rest of the day, hence thanksg. 

Speaker 2  (54:38)
Hi us. Well, thank you and say guys, bye, thanks. 
