
Speaker 1  (00:00)
80 arms from Eaton, Texas barbecue. 

Speaker 2  (00:07)
Yeah 

Speaker 3  (00:07)
So now it's so 

Speaker 2  (00:09)
It was a bit good at this stage of the And the best guys out there on the day went so Okay. I'm too f***** too so far. Canada is today Brazil today tonight I'm still betting on the Netherlands. 

Speaker 2  (00:31)
All right. Let's see 

Speaker 4  (00:33)
Hey guys. 

Speaker 2  (00:37)
Yeah, okay, yeah. Hey, I don't Hello, yeah? Knock in, so we wanted to continue admire, and I'd love to continue their arms. 

Speaker 4  (00:49)
Yeah, so just to give you some insights, we met kids Neil, and we'll be taking those data attention questions separately, because we need to do some cleanup in those records. But today, since we have an idea, what exactly we are going to do so, we can continue filling the Di so that we don't have those, you know yeah, some delays from those filling of the Di and whatnot need. Please keep me honest if you agree with that. 

Speaker 1  (01:14)
Yep, that's good. 

Speaker 4  (01:16)
Buffett. So who will be sharing this screen since Myron is no longer here, so 

Speaker 2  (01:28)
Ladies and gentlemen, who's feeling it and you need someone to fill it in. 

Speaker 4  (01:33)
Yes, somebody has to fill in. 

Speaker 2  (01:37)
Okay. All right, weird, it's my my I need one's economy. Oh, yeah? 

Speaker 2  (01:52)
Here it is. Alright, you guys are seeing my screen up. Yep, yes, all right. 

Speaker 2  (02:03)
I didn't want to call it aw. 

Speaker 4  (02:05)
Yeah, so I think David, you won't be able to do it until you add your name. So if you go up, you would have to do initiatively, delegates as ad me, then only would be able to do it delegates. Yeah, here come down, where Howard name, is there okay yeah. 

Speaker 4  (02:23)
Or if I can save it, save and And would you mind enlarging your screen a bit? 

Speaker 2  (02:30)
It's all pressure. Am I? I mean, get my do a screw here. 

Speaker 2  (02:41)
Oh no, I'm glad the wrong direction. Much better. 

Speaker 4  (02:48)
Yes, perfect. Let's go down. Okay, so let's fill the questions, because again, those deliverables purpose still needs to be revisited, I think, that's what I told Myron that purpose has to be called out clearly. 

Speaker 4  (03:05)
So if you are tracking through your project ID, or something it has to call it, why are we doing this initiative? Right, so the purpose should be updated. And then the deliverables also 

Speaker 2  (03:19)
We are the deliverable bus. 

Speaker 4  (03:21)
Yeah, yeah, I'm coming upcoming trash delivery booths on the left side. 

Speaker 2  (03:28)
Instead of planning prayer chance, we're not delivering insurances, we're doing one or alt. Yeah, well, this, this is correct. Yeah, it is correct. 

Speaker 2  (03:39)
These are the components you're doing. 

Speaker 3  (03:43)
Okay, we have, it's just for it, and why we have email that 

Speaker 2  (03:52)
Good morning, there, madam. I think Wendy P epi. Keep me on, is there anything else? 

Speaker 3  (04:02)
No, we don't need to wrap. We don't need to just, you can keep endpoint. I was yeah, SAS, just picking point and uh I came at the end that said I have to get you left that one, get you, that email are this one nominal. 

Speaker 3  (04:23)
Okay, what about and structural checks? 

Speaker 4  (04:29)
And purpose also, is it's not 

Speaker 2  (04:41)
You see, because we wanted to do this da as a giant 20 shikina, saying we shouldn't do that anymore. 

Speaker 4  (04:50)
Together, we assign emailing, no, actually, we have different leaders here right different business, so it would be two different data owners. We are referring to sure, so sure 

Speaker 1  (05:01)
They're saying, basically break it up, because it's gonna be a deep. There's gonna be a DIA for Peter's role, and then a DIA for my world, which is well 

Speaker 2  (05:11)
So daily protection, strategic replacement. So that's what we're doing is this good enough here as the purpose 

Speaker 4  (05:20)
Not exactly right, this is not no. Yeah? 

Speaker 3  (05:24)
We have emails. 

Speaker 2  (05:25)
Oh, no I saw that I saw that as Herbert first. 

Speaker 3  (05:28)
Do you guys support you guy? 

Speaker 4  (05:30)
So I decided to drop dip, but that's, do we have a feature or something which where we can use this change summary, or a project summary, where we can copy paste 

Speaker 2  (05:39)
That's what was here that's in the future. Yeah, that's exactly what you see in 20 years here I'm deleting most of it now. So I think because we're standing to our feature feature for one feature for both deliver both work streams, right? 

Speaker 4  (05:54)
But it still does not call out, right? Why are we moving to cloud from onprem? It just talk about the strategic solution which we are doing, but it does not telling us that white has been driving you to do this initiative, right? 

Speaker 2  (06:08)
Oh, I swear you're coming from what's up, but what if so? 

Speaker 1  (06:11)
This new vent is a nice initiative is to essentially replace the proof point ITM on prim solution with proof point SAS. 

Speaker 3  (06:26)
Eric, I was here that you can just there just, you know, basically delete it and keep it simple migrating on primed solution of insider track management program to the cloud version because it has better support, it has more functionality, better functionality, so it's 

Speaker 4  (06:43)
So Dave, you can keep that of which you've had. It controls, you just keep it, but add additional things, also like the one pitch. Yeah, I don't delete everything. 

Speaker 2  (06:57)
I'll be glad it didn't get rid of this piece and implement ITM. Oh, black, I. Tm. 

Speaker 2  (07:23)
So Russia, as the replacement for the day. On prim. And it's the same Move my dad. 

Speaker 2  (07:37)
We have ITM thank you. This is this, is this Okay, so ala, you are saying no, that in terms of not a lot. 

Speaker 1  (07:56)
Yeah, for the 

Speaker 2  (07:58)
Got it. While we're the benefits. Yeah, yes, yeah. 

Speaker 3  (08:06)
The Trump from tooling perspective, it does some more functional. Yeah, I wouldn't, I wouldn't basically put it here. 

Speaker 2  (08:15)
She Kay RK with this 

Speaker 1  (08:16)
This, yeah, this that's plenty to cover the gist of what the purpose is for that initiative. 

Speaker 3  (08:22)
Yeah 

Speaker 4  (08:23)
And then after solution, just put mall code, because we need to call her that which application code we are talking about. So after solution after solution, where you put in the purpose itself? No, no, not here in the form. 

Speaker 4  (08:37)
No, no, just this is not the maricode, right? It's speed point, so just take that off PPI TN okay below after where you have the toward the bottom of this column solution where you have it enter yeah, malcod. 

Speaker 2  (08:57)
Oh, this nice speed of it, that's one. 

Speaker 4  (09:00)
That's correct, perfect on the right side. Please change the owning defined business area, it's not global security and defense, it's financial crimes and operations. 

Speaker 2  (09:13)
And on so crimes I prevent you this one, right? 

Speaker 4  (09:17)
Yeah, yeah, and is this not just purely Canada? Neil, right? It is all across judiction, right enterprise. 

Speaker 1  (09:24)
There's a 100% enterprise. 

Speaker 4  (09:27)
So yeah, from the drop down, please. Yeah, select other United States. Can United States? 

Speaker 4  (09:37)
Yeah, it will take by the default, everything right. And has your data stored reviewed as the ISO just put it as yes. I'm reviewing it with you and then has it a review advice to completion of full day. 

Speaker 4  (09:50)
Yes, that would be a yes too. Okay, let's go dunk. 

Speaker 2  (09:55)
I mean, I missed it this first okay, alright, there, we go bumping up with all the other names now. 

Speaker 4  (10:03)
Everything is fine, come down here in the upcoming trip tranche. Deliverables, we are just putting proof points Sath endpoints, so that proof points SAS endpoint DP item is it's for both right like for endpoint NIT M it's like Can we say proof point SAS 4 and point dp, and ITM is that fair to say 

Speaker 2  (10:28)
You know, it should be immensely like that. Or AP yeah, these are modules from the performances. Yep Okay, got it, Sarah. 

Speaker 2  (10:42)
Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (10:47)
I'm so smiling. 

Speaker 4  (10:49)
Can you put in the replacement of on Prem in like again? I don't know what does incumbent means. 

Speaker 2  (10:55)
Sir, sorry, that wasn't yet awk. 

Speaker 3  (10:57)
Can can we do it this? Can, can you edit it? Cause that's gonna save a lot of time if you do it? 

Speaker 3  (11:02)
Then I Don' 

Speaker 4  (11:04)
I know they're very coming with the, I can tighten the check, but I don't have access to make the updates that's the problem due to yeah. I can put it in the chat if you guys O knife. 

Speaker 3  (11:17)
Graham has ever been like, you can navigate faster than, you know, us. 

Speaker 4  (11:22)
Yeah, no, no I hear you and yeah, it's just Yeah, just put it replacement of on Prem a solution to, and then you can just take deploy the falling, something just put it to proof points as for N point dp, and then this, yeah, if you guys agree with this one. Okay, puffin, or chica. 

Speaker 2  (11:49)
Let's do the rest of it now for a second time looking for it. 

Speaker 4  (11:54)
So on the question side, I don't believe that's what we discussed last time. We are not creating collecting or capturing any new data right? Is the existing data. 

Speaker 4  (12:02)
Is that fair to say? 

Speaker 1  (12:08)
Say that again? What was the question? 

Speaker 2  (12:10)
This one number number one year 

Speaker 1  (12:12)
Will new data be created? Yes, new data will be created, collected collected or captured? Yes. 

Speaker 2  (12:20)
And this is ongoing, so it's always capturing new stuff, correct? Yeah, okay, so that's that's the key here, chica. 

Speaker 4  (12:28)
Okay, but as part of this initiative at the like, when we'd say, when we are migrating to SaaS from onprem, are we going to capture any new element? I know there will be always new that will be a volume of data, right? But 

Speaker 2  (12:42)
You type, okay. 

Speaker 3  (12:44)
No, it's not a nickname. If you're a greater, there will be no new type. Because the monitoring criteria is gonna be the same. 

Speaker 1  (12:54)
I'm sorry why, so we're saying no new data, because 

Speaker 3  (13:00)
So comparing to on prim, so comparing on prim solution to this one, you're monitoring criteria is going to be the same, right? So They are migrants, migrating your armpront policies to SaaS. So what she's asking she's asking, are we going to capture any new data compared to what we're capturing on unprint solution? 

Speaker 2  (13:25)
And I see exactly where Neil is on this other, you capture something next week. 

Speaker 1  (13:30)
If you've got a craft ton of net new features and capabilities that we've never had before, then it's possible. I don't 

Speaker 3  (13:38)
Well advised that that that is that is their kind of no confused confusion and confusing part for all data protection related applications, right? What we are going to capture it is unknown, we Don 't know what we' re going to capture, we know the criteria which we're monitoring that criteria is going to be the same, okay, can it can it capture? 

Speaker 1  (14:01)
And in that context, then your answer would be no I get it. So it depends on the applicability of context. So yeah 

Speaker 2  (14:12)
Because if you get instead type It is implied. 

Speaker 4  (14:15)
Like would it be a newer then? Yes, again, just to make sure 

Speaker 2  (14:19)
No, it's yet no 

Speaker 4  (14:22)
Then, let's go on the left side. We'll finish the left side, and we'll go to the right side there. Let's finish the left side, and we are not consuming any data from another line of business. 

Speaker 4  (14:30)
So basically. Just protect platform right knee. 

Speaker 1  (14:36)
Well, data from other lines of businesses be consumed by this initiative. Now 

Speaker 4  (14:42)
Okay, so this is no. This is related to data steward. Will data be migrated to new storage mechanism? 

Speaker 4  (14:52)
We are not migrating the data right or we are you said that we are not going to migrate anything? 

Speaker 1  (14:59)
No, we're not migrating any of my old historical events and alert data. No correct? 

Speaker 4  (15:07)
So that would be nonethe. Will existing data move from on-site to cloud version? How should we answer that? 

Speaker 4  (15:19)
Because if you hover over to the question, Dave? I know we are not my 

Speaker 1  (15:23)
Straightforward at face value. How the question is, I answer it app, as is, are you moving it from on-site to cloud? The answer is no. 

Speaker 4  (15:34)
But it's just not data, but again, if you see the question that's where asked Tim it says to migrate the product or service. So if you see here, if organization has committed the Intention to migrate their product survey from on prime platform to cloud hosted, with no changes to data being produced consumed. Auditilized, so that would be a yes, right? 

Speaker 2  (15:54)
Are we hosting the data in the cloud? 

Speaker 4  (15:57)
We are going to going forward. 

Speaker 3  (16:02)
Trick trick question, you, you know, you know, the the situation right with all those blob stor. 

Speaker 2  (16:08)
Yes, yes, yes, but it would be our blog, or when I'm planning on putting any of that data in the vendor blame 

Speaker 3  (16:15)
But at the beginning, it's going to be on their side for a year right? But long-term It is going to be no 

Speaker 2  (16:25)
So we're the cloud off that Chicago, but not retained on their cloud. 

Speaker 4  (16:31)
So if you go over or again to the question, just to make sure we are on the same page. I know it's a bit misleading, but if you see here a select, yes, if other team let it be their intention to migrate their product or service from on prim to cloud, that's what we are doing out with no changes to data being produced, consumer digitalized, so we are not bringing any changes to data, but we are moving our solution from on prim to cloud. So don't you think yes 

Speaker 2  (17:00)
Yeah, that's why we're saying, yes. 

Speaker 4  (17:02)
Yes, ok, perfect. And then will existing data be used in a new different manner or purpose? Not exactly right, it's the same purpose, right? 

Speaker 4  (17:13)
Okay, and will this data be consumed by any of the lineup business other than protect platform norm? No. Ok, and will it bring any changes to the data models within the cloud? 

Speaker 4  (17:25)
So any new 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
Honest models, okay. 

Speaker 4  (17:28)
Okay, will it create new excusing? Third party date exchange? 

Speaker 1  (17:32)
Surely, hang on, will it new it too? So will new models, so I'll tell you here's the only thing that I know that might get called out on this. So with proof point, having the ability to essentially do user modeling, where you can actually set a particular user risk profile based upon that type of thing that's all based upon modeling information. 

Speaker 1  (17:56)
And again, it depends on what information we send to it. So it's not natively like, I don't think it's inherently just turned on, I think there's some things that you have to do configuration wise in order to take advantage of that. One of the things that definitely got called out was part of the fact that we tested that the unpremed doesn't have the capability to do anything with models, and therefore I didn't need to submit anything to model validation. 

Speaker 1  (18:29)
And prove point themselves, the vendor said that it does support the ability to do that. And if we were going to operate using that software, we would need to have it certified through model validation so they know what models are actually being leveraged. 

Speaker 3  (18:46)
But we are not going to use it immediately, right. I think I Don' 

Speaker 1  (18:50)
I don't know that I don't know what you guys have planned. 

Speaker 3  (18:53)
Yeah, I think when we look into it, we can just come 

Speaker 1  (18:58)
So for now, like, for now, the answer Shika is no right now, because my default, we're not turning it on, it does have the capability, but we have to cross that ridge when we get to a point where models are being affected or changed, then we would obviously respectively have to update this record. 

Speaker 4  (19:19)
Okay, so let's put it 

Speaker 2  (19:20)
I don't know if I 

Speaker 4  (19:22)
Okay, add another and then, as part of this initiative, will it create throwd party date exchange relationship? That would be a yes, right? Because now we are 

Speaker 1  (19:31)
It's the uncloud, and it's 

Speaker 4  (19:34)
Okay, okay, and then are you renewing any contract with the vendor by any chance? 

Speaker 1  (19:41)
We just signed a contract. That's why we are going to the cloud. 

Speaker 4  (19:47)
So we are not earning the contract though, right? But not 

Speaker 3  (19:51)
I ought to only experience it. It turns out how you read it. We have a contract already with them, but we made another contract, which is basically a bigger contract which is covering this, not. 

Speaker 3  (20:02)
I don't know. I don't know if you want to put it in it yet. Not renewing existing contract, because that was a different Man in the middle between Austin vendor this is going to be a new contract, which basically is taking over this one. 

Speaker 2  (20:19)
So it looks like as you because it's a contract, so I over a rage. It says yes, it is a contract for an existing lender. No changes to data being produced consumed are utilized. 

Speaker 4  (20:33)
Okay, fed enough. So? Yes, no, because it's a new contract I saw that I mentioned, so that's the way it's 

Speaker 3  (20:42)
But if you're sorry, if you go over the question again, it says, if existing contract, it's like, yes, if the contract for existing vendors, that's existing vendor. 

Speaker 2  (20:53)
So we're not bringing a new third party, but this is, yes, it's for a new for 

Speaker 3  (20:59)
So reviewing, it's okay. Because they exist in my advantage, but just by reading the first line existing vendor it is existing vendor. 

Speaker 1  (21:08)
Yeah 

Speaker 4  (21:10)
Okay, okay, let's see if it's And can you come down Let's hit proceed, please. And I'll come down. I want to see how come it is still giving light score? 

Speaker 4  (21:33)
Can you come down? Okay, food Lia, perfect, so let's go to daytime full day we have to fill other questions. Okay. 

Speaker 4  (21:42)
So it would be a yes, just put it first question, would be a yes, data score steward from line of visit. So yes, data steward, engage, just unlock it above 1.1 just type in my name SHI 

Speaker 2  (21:56)
Bixby I Ain. 

Speaker 4  (21:58)
It's yeah, just pick it, pick this first one. That's like 

Speaker 2  (22:02)
Okay. 

Speaker 4  (22:04)
And then yeah, let's go down. We are not engaging. We don't have any life producing line of business so it would be no, and not applicable. 

Speaker 4  (22:12)
We don't have to engage any cross functional data, so it's so not applicable, just put it in here, and the below one is the same, so no consuming data Stuart, so yeah, not applicable and to your point Dave, is it a risk a project? Do you guys have Esc meetings? Yes, we do, but is it a risk a project 

Speaker 2  (22:34)
And as you wash her escape once in alright. Project profiling, well, he's like, well, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (22:55)
Can you check if the in the like, we can continue if you want that? 

Speaker 3  (23:01)
I Don'. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (23:04)
Oh, because I'm telling you, I have a data story. I'm gay, so we're gonna say, yes, I'm not a data name, but so I'm 

Speaker 4  (23:09)
Yeah, like if, in case only this is only valid. If your risk is a otherwise it is not applicable. So 

Speaker 2  (23:18)
I'm an executive data. Stuart does lead like 

Speaker 4  (23:21)
No, no, no, it increases, you have this risky, then you need to have it. But if it is not risky, then you don't have to worry about it. 

Speaker 2  (23:29)
What do I answer then? As I'm saying it's not risky. 

Speaker 4  (23:32)
Oh, it's not then no, no, and not applicable. Yeah, I yeah, I yeah. Not applicable. 

Speaker 4  (23:38)
Is this initiative been driven by any regulatory audit findings? 

Speaker 2  (23:47)
Ida, was there any finding? 

Speaker 3  (23:50)
There was no finding, but regulatory requirement. Do we have any regulatory requirement for this nail? Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (23:58)
Set it again, do we have any regulatory requirement nope? 

Speaker 1  (24:02)
We have, there is nothing that is regulatory required in my space. 

Speaker 4  (24:07)
Okay, so no, and not applicable. 

Speaker 2  (24:11)
Meta later managed to make 

Speaker 4  (24:13)
So this would be a question for you, Neil, are we going to create any risk regulatory financial reporting out of this initiative? 

Speaker 1  (24:21)
No, we're not. 

Speaker 4  (24:23)
We're not right. 

Speaker 1  (24:24)
Because passively, if I'm not under regulatory requirement, anything we create after that. 

Speaker 4  (24:31)
Okinaw. Okay, then then what is happening? Then we won't be talking about any critical data elements per se, so let's put it as no, and not applicable. 

Speaker 4  (24:44)
Okay, and then all these answers would be no, because everything is related to critical and elements, and we are not making any updates to enterprise data catalog. So no, and we are just put not applicable. I think to be about easy. 

Speaker 4  (25:05)
Not to keep it awa. 

Speaker 2  (25:14)
If grinnel did a Miller interview, user exchanged half data producers. So again, this isn't 

Speaker 4  (25:22)
We exactly got it, and then not, we got it perfect. 

Speaker 2  (25:27)
Well, data quality management 

Speaker 4  (25:28)
Yeah, so this will be also new, because it's also critical data elements, so no and not applicable. No, yeah, first of all, first one first okay and not applicable, perfect. 

Speaker 2  (25:47)
The Roosevelt played A 

Speaker 4  (25:49)
Okay? So this one I wanted to understand that, are we going to do any kind of testings like sit pad pro testing to check of 6 parameters out of 6 parameters. What are we checking like accuracy, completeness, integrity, timeliness, uniqueness, and validity? 

Speaker 4  (26:05)
Are we doing some kind of testing first of all 

Speaker 1  (26:11)
I mean, we're doing rule testing like, I mean Yes, well, data quality rules be developed updated and documented. 

Speaker 3  (26:22)
Yeah, we have. 

Speaker 5  (26:24)
They have a pattern of credit environment, so crazy testing 

Speaker 4  (26:29)
So let's put it, yes, we'll be developed And then just put it, sit, I think, momma, please keep you on a sit pad and bat testing. Dev patent pro testing will be executed to ensure And which sixth parameters moment, that, you know that we have done a couple of dis, so do you know like which all 6 parameters? We are checking akracy, completeness, integrity, timeliness, eudictus and validity. 

Speaker 2  (27:13)
We're testing against the rule right? So entrepreneur rule 

Speaker 4  (27:17)
Okay, so I'm You have the challenge all, just 1 like 1 or 2 or 3, like you can just mention to ensure 

Speaker 5  (27:29)
So when shootout, accuracy of the pullets, oh 

Speaker 4  (27:34)
Yet accuracy completed, it is That's the accuracy momentum. 

Speaker 2  (27:41)
Yeah, of their alert. So we test against all that adventure or whatever alert we're getting. 

Speaker 5  (27:51)
It was being captured. 

Speaker 2  (27:52)
Doctor yesterday, based on the rules we have, we've developed right 

Speaker 4  (27:57)
You're okay. Fad enough, let's go to the next questions. Build data quality, come down. 

Speaker 4  (28:06)
Will data qualities and validation to move data from one, so we aren't, as we mentioned that we are not migrating any data so it would be not applicable. So just put not applicable. 

Speaker 2  (28:17)
They have it here, and they're 

Speaker 4  (28:19)
Yeah, just put a nail so here yeah. 

Speaker 2  (28:23)
Okay. 

Speaker 4  (28:28)
Okay, so post implementation, who will be providing this support? If there is any issues identified, like would it be TED, or would it be vendor or both? 

Speaker 2  (28:47)
Data quality monitoring. This is about 

Speaker 4  (28:51)
Like post implementation, we are talking about once we go long. If we have any issue identified, generally, we have those L to L3 support teams from td, right? So would they be involved? 

Speaker 4  (29:03)
Or would we have vendor support? Because sometimes vendor also gives some warranty periods or something like that. 

Speaker 2  (29:16)
So this is a very upstream coming, right? Yep, yeah. The inequality monitoring 

Speaker 3  (29:26)
That's a very big question. I returned, but the quality monitoring or 

Speaker 2  (29:36)
Plan to my data quality is going to be 

Speaker 3  (29:38)
Prop, because operation comes when you talk about productions. Quality, if something's not working or simple. 

Speaker 2  (29:47)
Yeah, that's 

Speaker 4  (29:48)
Exactly exactly exactly as I thought I thought 

Speaker 2  (29:52)
Consolidate, a day today processes will be used to support ongoing data quality. So this is broad Ops support. So it's left engineering already. 

Speaker 2  (30:02)
You know, is it like June 2027. Touring an alert when it shouldn't be during an alert. Our missing something when it should be turning unalert. 

Speaker 2  (30:20)
That would be an apps question, right? 

Speaker 3  (30:25)
Again, that kind of Ops are we talking about? Opsism, triaging captured alert like nail steam or opts. Monitoring the production health 

Speaker 2  (30:37)
Um no, it would be. It would be 

Speaker 3  (30:40)
As if this data I started with data that's going to be me, people who are Nielsen, who's looking into alert, and who's saying AIDS working as expected. And we also 

Speaker 1  (30:51)
I would honestly say it's going to be the fourth option Data quality will be monitored via line of business. Specific model. 

Speaker 4  (31:01)
Yeah, I agree with you. And then who would be that team Neil, whom we can mention here? What would be that team named? 

Speaker 4  (31:07)
What would 

Speaker 1  (31:08)
The insider enhanced surveillance team while monitor the records and functionality as designed If there's an issue, we will engage security engineering. Is that fair Ata yep? 

Speaker 2  (32:09)
Sounds about right. 

Speaker 4  (32:14)
Okay, quickly, then I don't think so. We are creating or using any reference data, right? Like the currency, growth, country growth, so no and not applicable. 

Speaker 4  (32:29)
No, then notably, I just put it 

Speaker 2  (32:36)
I can't know. 

Speaker 1  (32:37)
It's not going to create any reference data, okay? 

Speaker 2  (32:45)
And wildlife data lights are commanding it. 

Speaker 4  (32:48)
This one I would like to hold on, until I have a discussion with Neil, because that's something we need to talk about once we have it, but if you guys are okay, I think that's something Neil can help us update it, or like we can connect, Dave, once we have inputs from Neil, then I can connect with you, but we need to update this application usages and vendor engagement also quickly. If you guys have time. So that at least we are done with this Di, filling, you know. 

Speaker 2  (33:16)
Yes, so we oh, which or her name. 

Speaker 1  (33:18)
Questions are, how many questions do we have left 

Speaker 4  (33:21)
2 more like these 3 would be only done 

Speaker 1  (33:23)
Okay, so let's just knock them out like 

Speaker 4  (33:26)
Hello, these 3 questions, we would only do it once we have those discussion on B Bo record next week next to next week, right? We just need to finish the application usages. Can you go up Dave? 

Speaker 4  (33:37)
Just to make sure, are we sure just 3 right everything we finish okay. And the yeah, let's go down. We just need to add two things, vendor engagements and application usages. 

Speaker 4  (33:46)
Rest 3, I'll catch base with you once I have Neil here, like I kneel, provide me the inputs, let's finish these 2 

Speaker 2  (33:54)
So vendor engagement is a new 

Speaker 4  (33:56)
Yeah, can you please hit on the top bottom right here, newspa? Just put the vendor name. 

Speaker 2  (34:06)
Okay, as images, this one type of data exchange 

Speaker 4  (34:13)
I bought right. And just we have to just put a functionality, and we can copy pace there. So How would it collect the information need? 

Speaker 4  (34:26)
Like, how does it pull those videos or about the user activity? 

Speaker 1  (34:31)
The information is generated based upon the agent that is installed on the endpoint. 

Speaker 4  (34:39)
Proof point, agent yep. Okay, information generate based on the proof point proofpoint, agents deployed On the based. Can you mention information like, instead of information? 

Speaker 4  (34:55)
Can we mention alert? Can we sell alerts and beyon? 

Speaker 1  (34:58)
Yeah, that's fine. It's alert. Data is generated. 

Speaker 4  (35:01)
Yeah, so let's put alerts generated based on the proof point agent. Roof point agents. Deployed on the endpoints, user endpoint To plan a user endpoints, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (35:21)
And those alerts will be full stop those alerts will be available. For actioning on Those alerts will be available. But actioning, why are vendors SaaS Porter? 

Speaker 4  (35:44)
Is that fair to say Via vendors, SAS. Okay, can you copy paste this information Dave? Yeah, we will need this save and exit, please. 

Speaker 2  (36:04)
We're not putting it down here. 

Speaker 4  (36:05)
No, no, no, no, no. Yes, Stephen excellent. 

Speaker 2  (36:09)
Yeah, okay, let me 

Speaker 4  (36:10)
We would have to put it somewhere in the next 

Speaker 2  (36:13)
Yeah, you know, I'm just putting it in my I guess I want not to earn it, right. 

Speaker 4  (36:21)
Okay, let's go to the below. Please below the screen, please. 

Speaker 2  (36:27)
Okay, so we did one. 

Speaker 4  (36:29)
Just one more left our application usages, please. 

Speaker 2  (36:34)
Okay, New York, New York. Okay, that girl is closed. 

Speaker 4  (36:42)
P point. 

Speaker 2  (36:44)
Okay, I got him. 

Speaker 4  (36:49)
And then type of change existing application And then Bobby pays the information, which we have it, which you already did as a control V. Yeah, perfect. And we are not going to make any changes to T. 

Speaker 4  (37:05)
D all right, like everything will be same if I'm not mistaken. Ata, would you agree at our mama? 

Speaker 2  (37:21)
In updating the book, a record 

Speaker 4  (37:25)
Okay, so we'll not take place and not applicable 

Speaker 3  (37:28)
Even sorry, I was just feeling good. 

Speaker 2  (37:31)
Sorry, I'll be moving. And I see the other options. 

Speaker 3  (37:38)
Yeah, then we have 2 options, I think yeah. 

Speaker 2  (37:41)
Interest, not adversarial, okinak. 

Speaker 4  (37:45)
All right, save and exit, okay? Perfect. So as that we have finished the Dr. 

Speaker 4  (37:55)
At least for this initiative. Just 3 questions left, Dave. Do you mind checking with me on the week of 7th July sometime? 

Speaker 4  (38:02)
I have a call booked with Neil. On 9th July, so if you want, we can connect on 10th of July. 

Speaker 2  (38:12)
Okay, voted. Alright, okay. Awes. 

Speaker 4  (38:18)
Offset, thank you guys, thank you so much. 
