
Speaker 1  (00:01)
A couple of you might find Stories Outside of that as well. Why don't we start off with Mr. Brown? 

Speaker 1  (00:08)
Hello, Warren, how are you up? I think that you aren't doing all right. Okay, what do you have in the vault related world? 

Speaker 2  (00:19)
Nothing much, nothing. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
What could you have in the vault related world? All right, so they're not volatile and not volatile core. My bad, my bad, uh I'm stuck in the past from my last call. 

Speaker 1  (00:35)
Okay, here's the cold core stuff I don't 

Speaker 2  (00:39)
I'm doing benefit at the moment or eye. 

Speaker 1  (00:43)
So none of these have anything to do with you, the NPS server, no Do we have you on any other calls today? It's not on the gcp, one or okay. And then let's talk about what Warren, what are you aware of that you saw? 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
You got this one to ramp up on the ventfi provider with Camellia, what else is going on with the venifer of the fif? 

Speaker 2  (01:18)
That's all I've got to do, isn't I want you to know I had got the other database one with Jeremy. 

Speaker 1  (01:24)
Do yes, you've completed that one story. Are there other things that should be going on? All right. 

Speaker 1  (01:30)
Do you know what those are yet? 

Speaker 2  (01:33)
Now every time I want to know he goes, Tony leaves. 

Speaker 1  (01:37)
Alright, so other than the venif stuff, are you aware of anything else that's gonna fall into your plate over the next 2 week period 

Speaker 2  (01:46)
I think once he's got the Eagle. Actually, we sorted out a recent programming work to do for the day today. 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
It doesn't sound like you're taking anything into the sprinter isn't that new as of today? Then yeah, would you doki, just the one for a story that lives in there already up to you? Well, I already know the answer to this, but I'm just politely gonna say all the same up to you, if you'd like to hang out for the rest if this call or drop off. 

Speaker 2  (02:17)
Yeah, sure, I think 

Speaker 1  (02:20)
Oh, yeah? Oh. Or a second I thought you might sure thing like he was going to hang around, but clearly I forgot who I was speaking to all right. 

Speaker 1  (02:30)
Let's look at some core related stuff. How are you doing when you should be feeling better today? 

Speaker 3  (02:35)
I just scared it a good time of saying, and my doctor's discolorated before this call, so I'm gonna go see her just so she can check my ear. 

Speaker 1  (02:46)
She is sorry to hear that boss. Okay, let's maybe quickly look through this. If you don't or you get to look through it or do you want to? 

Speaker 1  (02:54)
If you haven't 

Speaker 3  (02:58)
Most of the stories I kept put in the sprinter 6, already. 

Speaker 1  (03:01)
Oh, you did perfect. 

Speaker 3  (03:03)
All right, I'm 

Speaker 1  (03:04)
Ok, then is there anything else that you wanted to bring up or are we good to 

Speaker 3  (03:09)
Nothing at the moment, no on the thing is the story that I created on the very bottom that you see to an 8987, you need some help in terms of getting some directions. I mean, I have sent the emails Apollos, I send the email the one we're talking yesterday about, but not getting. Noticed. 

Speaker 1  (03:29)
Do we need who do we need to respond on that? 

Speaker 3  (03:33)
Some started some went from like David's team, david 

Speaker 1  (03:37)
I inspire great, so you're lasting real. Is this one here? Oh yes, okay. 

Speaker 4  (03:45)
And this is that was something where Manishi put it in there, we haven't constructed the past key epics in the overall of gsd, kind of work straight, sufficient to understand why this is the blocker for some of the functionality, but we maybe should I was thinking it really belongs over there, because the only reason we're doing it We have the commissional access policy that causes this issue is because we want to enable path keeps not mobile misauthenticated path keys, but inclusive of ubi keys. 

Speaker 4  (04:19)
So I'm just trying to figure out like how to make that relationship clear, and then we can should move it over to the GST epics. 

Speaker 1  (04:28)
Is this a risk for pasky, or like an impediment really for pasky? 

Speaker 4  (04:33)
It could be, as, yeah, it's like there's so there's like, I was saying, in the email minute, there's, there's 3 op, 3 or more options for kind of dealing with it. One is document to people that this is annoying, and you can work around it. Right? 

Speaker 4  (04:49)
There. 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Is that the that's right? That's true that for 

Speaker 4  (04:54)
For requirements, number four is yeah, like not us or that's largely discussion, but then 1 and 2 is probably annoying and demanding, potentially not really that secure. So 1 or 3 are the things that we probably need to do. But one is we don't need to do it, we need to ask and play enablement to do it, and it involves, you know, an underlying setting change to how much Chrome does authentication? 

Speaker 4  (05:22)
So it's like not trivial. 

Speaker 3  (05:24)
But that is the way Microsoft is moving forward with it as well, right, so is hopefully that is the direction we should take like in a long-term anyways, because they 're going away, looks like away from the ss extension. 

Speaker 1  (05:41)
That's right. Was it number two or number three is our recommendation that E recommend well number 10, right? The one that says recommended. 

Speaker 4  (05:50)
In Microsoft also I think basically recommended that Alright, I don't know if they officially said we recommend it, but that was like kind of their first option and I think maybe they did say something the way they're going, but it's like we need to ask another team to do the work to enable us to do something that enables something that enables something that we need to do for the teams. That's where those links are not super tuned. 

Speaker 1  (06:14)
Yeah, so the first person we need to ask is Robert, if we can go ahead with this. 

Speaker 4  (06:21)
Well, it's not us. It's we're asking them to do the work, it's all their work by, oh, come. So that we can unlock our work 

Speaker 3  (06:29)
We decided to fire it and proportion and identify with Microsoft, like this is what it is the problem and what the possible solution Okay, because now it's a little different team tournament. 

Speaker 4  (06:40)
We have a dependency on another team. 

Speaker 1  (06:42)
Alright, so 12 or 3, I'm looking at it. Then there's two things that need to happen moon, one is that They will come back to Who they means need to make a decision about, which of the 3 approaches is most is the one they want to move ahead with. And then 2 Oh, s***, okay. 

Speaker 4  (07:09)
When it's staying to decide whether they're going to do it at all or not, based on that, we are asking them to do it. 

Speaker 1  (07:16)
So if they do one, we don't have to do 2 or 3. Well, we don't have to do 23 is not really A. No one has to do 

Speaker 4  (07:23)
We know we need to communicate to people that they can't change them, we'll change people's, these are experienced in a way that's quite annoying. And we didn't tell them how to deal with that. 

Speaker 1  (07:33)
The usually that makes it sound like that's probably not the way we're gonna do it, because we don't like to make things annoying for our users, where we can help it. So realistically probably 1 or 2, which means it's The disturbing is the kind of like awk. Like a standoff here where, like we're saying you should do one. 

Speaker 1  (07:55)
And then probably Robert's gonna come back and say we should do 2. 

Speaker 4  (07:59)
I stopped Roberts. Who's a hero? I mean, I would say it's that David's or I guess I don't think Roberts roberts' decision, nor was he necessarily saying no, but these are our recommendation as the people who are owned the identity right, the identity platform that this plugin allows authentication to, you know, we talking with. 

Speaker 4  (08:21)
The vendor recommend that you switch how right switch, how Chrome handles authentication to our service that we do have some, you know, claim to authority to make the request, but they could also they're the ones who need to say, well, no, it breaks, you know, Sally Smith use case. 

Speaker 1  (08:38)
Is that one of the things? I was already listed in this Okay, is this the right? Those Tuesday and Thursday calls is that the right forum to bring this up now? 

Speaker 4  (08:51)
But it's not a window somehow for business. 

Speaker 1  (08:53)
All right, duh. Okay, when do we like? Where and how would you bring this up to gift? 

Speaker 1  (09:00)
You got people to review and make a decision. 

Speaker 4  (09:05)
I feel like I Don' But that was why I was saying it ties loosely. That into some of the work we're doing to set up the past key functionality. 

Speaker 1  (09:17)
I'm writing art. 

Speaker 3  (09:20)
Maybe have some sort of a conversation with like architectural level, like Germany and decide like regarding on the pasque. And then maybe if this is a concerning. Annoyance, then maybe we need to go back to the Himalayan enablement and saying, okay, we need this feature enable, what do we need to do or do we give them an option saying, are you willing to do this? 

Speaker 4  (09:44)
Well, we're asking them to do it. We'll see what they say, if they say, no, then we need to push back. I think that's my that's my thing right is like we making mainland things dope, and then 

Speaker 3  (09:54)
They could do it, and with cause more problems, because we have not tested it right, the opec that doesn't mean it made 

Speaker 4  (09:59)
Culture, that's part of them doing it, right Without them, do it and then don't bother to test it and roll it out to everybody. That's not what we're asking 

Speaker 3  (10:08)
We're asking for I'm assuming 

Speaker 4  (10:11)
Then, that's fine, I'm up from testing, though, right, I am not able to test every end user use case. But if they want to deploy into my workstation and have me verify that I can still use Chrome happy. 

Speaker 3  (10:24)
And according to that, the links I poured in there, this is the like, basically and also what Microsoft said, right, like the concerns I raise with them, is supposed to seamlessly, replace the experience with the what the sso experience is right now. So to the end, user should be no change at all. 

Speaker 4  (10:43)
Yeah, and agree should be no change. And they're able to deploy it without breaking stuff for a different example. So let's Again? 

Speaker 4  (10:51)
It's 

Speaker 3  (10:52)
Because 40 Yamis should be busy. 

Speaker 4  (10:53)
The evaluation and then we can help with testing, but If they choose to proceed with it, and if they choose not to, then we need to have a discussion about why we would like them to and what the rationale for that and the timefra. 

Speaker 3  (11:07)
They can do to our work special like your mind. For example, and we can test the actual the problem 

Speaker 4  (11:13)
And this is where it gets a little complicated, right? You see this as task key design, right? This is also required for ubiques, this is required for pasques, as a brand ubiquitous, right, not just 

Speaker 1  (11:25)
Got all right, God like the dog definitely bumble picture. I see it okay. 

Speaker 4  (11:29)
So our dependency for you became also 

Speaker 1  (11:33)
Walk away. I think we're, I think we're under the right epic right now, because we are moving forward with this, but the past key epic is It's technically blocked. So my recommendation is let's link the 2 I would say that As he Yeah, like this decision is depended on by like paske depends on this, and also, ubiquit depends on this. 

Speaker 1  (12:00)
What is our EU? The key options for the Service initial on the port. 

Speaker 4  (12:10)
There's no integration. So like the design just and the actual, you know? 

Speaker 3  (12:18)
The physicality is called art. 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
Okay, so at least we've got the links in there. And then Do you think if you get some Facetime with Jeremy, you're going to be able to resolve this, I'm not feeling, as you know, from my tone at the 

Speaker 4  (12:39)
Why would I don't, I guess Doing a serious check with Jeremy fine, but he's not going to resolve it or he'll just 

Speaker 3  (12:48)
I mean, what I was trying to say is For the passkey vision, and what this challenge we have, is it's going to be a bigger problem in a hindsight, kind of thing. Just to understand the overall picture And maybe I might have more ideas to how we can move forward with it, in terms of escalating with the Dave's team or any other direction pursuit. 

Speaker 4  (13:19)
One of the things is, I would like to the one thing I think we just should confirm with him is Just like in the eventual path, deep design, you know, I Don' 

Speaker 1  (13:33)
Let me lose you, Paul. Yes, you went there. 

Speaker 4  (13:41)
The Behal. What I would like to confirm so the password off requirement basically is the thing that this is the compensating for right. So if and that's the thing where everything I've heard so far has applied to me that the password author requirement will still be required but confirming with Jeremy and Jonathan That is still going to be a thing in the like, you know, medium term ISIS the thing that I think would be doing. 

Speaker 4  (14:11)
Fifth. Yes, then we don't need to like, get into the details of a solution with them, I would say, then we can follow, or we can they can say, hey, this is what we're going to do. Maybe with something to pass on to Andrew to go harass them around or something, I don't know, right because it's not a it's not a it's something that that project needs. 

Speaker 4  (14:31)
But it hasn't really that they haven't registered. Because we're, we're trying to look ahead. All that stuff isn' 

Speaker 1  (14:41)
One last thing, I don't think I would recommend a single story to both evaluate and implement the mitigation, just from what you're saying, I'm thinking it's probably going to take at least a couple of weeks to finish or evaluate peace. Not necessarily from an effort perspective, possibly 2 points is correct, but like In terms of duration, do you think you'll be able to get an answer and implement that? 

Speaker 3  (15:08)
It was the joy of the independent party, how it worked. 

Speaker 4  (15:12)
Or not, they are, we're not implementing anything that's what I was saying, right if we're assuming that we asked them and play an inbound to do it, that work is on them, and it will absolutely take more than it is for them to deploy with everyone in production. Which is more or less? What we watch? 

Speaker 1  (15:30)
So the acceptance carterion, this is really to make a decision about like from what you're saying there, right? What Like, decide on what which of these 4 options you take realistically 1 or 2. Is that the correct acceptance criteria for that story? 

Speaker 4  (15:54)
I feel like we've made it this much. 

Speaker 3  (15:57)
I think what we do need for perfect 

Speaker 4  (16:02)
It plays in, but we need to submit a request that then to ask you to do it. I think 

Speaker 3  (16:06)
Yeah, we don't know what to make of doing. 

Speaker 4  (16:07)
There's no request to complete 

Speaker 3  (16:10)
Yeah, what do you take to submit? So that is like one of the basic asks is what intake do we need to submit for them to consider this as a request from a official request? To make these changes So I don't know if they have a specific intake form or any other channel to go through this, to get it in their board, to get this work done. 

Speaker 3  (16:32)
That is partly not clear. 

Speaker 1  (16:40)
And her acceptance criteria I don't like the word Gat, but E to agree to resolve from specific etc et cetera and to plant stories. So that makes sense. 

Speaker 4  (16:59)
Yeah 

Speaker 3  (17:07)
Yeah, that's fine for no, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (17:09)
Thank you bye to meet you. Sounds terrible. My friend okay? 

Speaker 1  (17:17)
See where you can get if you need someone to raise a stink, let us know. All right, otherwise we'll try to not ask you questions so you don't have to speak for the rest of the hour. Oh, let's look at what you got on the go. 

Speaker 1  (17:37)
The key you've got a fairly full sprint that you're taking in as well. I'm just gonna move the in progress stuff to the top, so we can delineate it from the to dose. 3 4. 

Speaker 1  (17:54)
Okay, so there's 4 points there, and another eight fresh points. I would assume that that probably is The right size of things have you already been through this or is this? Yeah, like this isn't. 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
Hey, we're cooked for us, right? 

Speaker 4  (18:13)
I'm unsure why the MC2 deaths are rebelled in the next minute. I'm not sure about being in the sprint, but I ig. I 

Speaker 1  (18:21)
I think we moved it there yeah like a while ago. So yeah, is that I mean, I Don' 

Speaker 4  (18:34)
I mean, really, it's requests, maybe requests, I thought we were going to figure out whether they load balances in front before we put in the, I think, I think we were going to figure out the low balances situation. Or we have the servers built-in case we built that in the wrong place. 

Speaker 1  (18:53)
Right. Who's looking after that? Is that you who's looking into the load balancer. 

Speaker 4  (18:58)
I have a meeting with, well, it's the infrastructure architect, and he asked us to submit a consult with networks so that he could figure out what to put in the denial. So all I lied. And then we have a meeting on Friday on it. 

Speaker 4  (19:09)
I learned so this steps over doub. So maybe I think it's Put in the requests for deaf servers could be a fast follower from that 

Speaker 1  (19:23)
Definitely, let's remove this. Um, U. What definitely, let's remove the S there we go. 

Speaker 1  (19:35)
Dude, we want the separate story for put in the a story or probably more a task to put in the request to build 

Speaker 4  (19:42)
That was what I was saying, I need to put in like And we're stories, and that nps server are going to reflect the actual work as I better understand it now. 

Speaker 1  (19:52)
Can I build this one out for you? Just for the load balancer, just not the load balancer decision, the putting in the Submit request for VN2 death server build as a task Or would you rather take it away? And do A 

Speaker 4  (20:11)
Let me just I do, say, just doing one won't really get us very close to her, the epic be complete. Oh 

Speaker 1  (20:20)
If you are ready to talk about it now, I dare say we will probably have some time to add a bunch more stories for you before the end of this call. But if you need more like Quiet, reflective time. Before we do that, then I will lead you to it. 

Speaker 1  (20:35)
Both options are entirely available. Okay, so that one is gone. Let's refresh and look at what else is in there and make sure that everything else makes sense for you. 

Speaker 1  (20:54)
Anything else that you're seeing in here, you don't like 

Speaker 1  (21:09)
Um yeah. 

Speaker 4  (21:11)
I mean. AA couple of these are converted seconds tickets that I really haven't talked with you or collet or microcosm, whether we should even be doing them. But they are like, of course, the teams are like, well, it's a priority. 

Speaker 4  (21:28)
So I Believing them, and they submitted a delivery ticket, and it turns out that it's not being right. That delivery is getting less requests, I feel like are getting less and less baus. Time goes on so right, and there's also like they're not features either, because it's like one of them is like 21902 is like, create A And that's a that's one that came in through second, and I just converted last week, which is like a you know, a new kind of just an average to reflect an API, but it has like it's not something that we're technically like allowed to do, but that people are thinking that it's only some, it's, we don't do API registration on our side, but this team is like agreed on a poc with the apa M team and stuff, so we're going to implement it, but I didn't, I wouldn't I didn't think that it was like a Bau delivery thing, because it's not a pattern that we have right now. 

Speaker 4  (22:25)
Nor is it potentially something that should get promoted to higher environments, so I kind of took it likewise for the team's sip gateway, there's like a bunch of Gender documentation around the potential conditional access changes that are required through the San Francisco phones that are the connections. Access, go phones in India with our tenant, I initially, I was trying to figure out why they're even talking to us, because we don't care where people register phones from. But there's some sort of authentication component to that. 

Speaker 4  (22:56)
That they're going to be doing a poc. On. So I kind of took that one. 

Speaker 4  (23:02)
In the "-un" into the sprint, but I'm really not Because maybe we should be making them go through intake to us, but I don't know if it's a feature, it's really just like a potentially a set of CA changes. But we don't we don't know the nature of them until they've actually done some testing which they're going to do this week, and they kind of asked for and we have somebody to talk with about cavaluate, any failures, and what changes are needed to accommodate there Phon enrollment processes. Oh, no, no, no. 

Speaker 4  (23:37)
Thank you, I'm saying that those aren't determined kind of somewhat random ones, the other ones, I think that I've taken in from the second gtsmci meeting. 

Speaker 1  (23:49)
Okay, if it's I'm already on the CA, one, let's talk about that one onest. So you can think of a couple of things. Number one, we can have a story to consult on rather than create. 

Speaker 1  (24:02)
Thank you. 

Speaker 4  (24:04)
Oh, yeah, it's initial. It was initially A 

Speaker 1  (24:08)
Yeah, like this, we don't know 

Speaker 4  (24:10)
We don't know what they're going to need, but we need to help them analyze if they when they, when they do this configuration and start failing. If they fail for conditional access reasons, then we need to design and conditional access around what the parameters of that failure look like. 

Speaker 1  (24:26)
All right, so I think you've convinced me that this should be a consult story. Yes, yeah Or and you're good with taking that one in and then let's just adjust the acceptance criteria on that a bit. I'm ready to accept that it was 6. 

Speaker 1  (24:54)
This cannot Then, document the failure of reals, and Create stories to fix. 

Speaker 4  (25:15)
I'm sure or to design, you know, alt. 

Speaker 1  (25:20)
I determine girls. Yeah, because that might be stories epics. Tell them to go into an intake. 

Speaker 1  (25:33)
It could be a bunch of different ways. So that could potentially happen, that, I suppose. All right, and then the other one was this one for the alb fabric capacity right? 

Speaker 4  (25:47)
Yeah, well, I mean, I'm trying to remember if they put comments on that. 

Speaker 1  (25:53)
Yeah, it's it's kind of old. It's been sitting around for a while. 

Speaker 4  (25:58)
This payment stuff I didn't realize that I think it was payment. Oh no I didn't, because 

Speaker 1  (26:07)
Yeah, you can settle on this one for a while. I'm a friend. What do we want to do with it? 

Speaker 4  (26:11)
Yeah, well, they didn't respond for a month or 2. So some of The Times on that, but then I think they just did. And then I didn't, I haven't a time to look into. 

Speaker 1  (26:23)
Alrighty, um, thank you, thank you. 

Speaker 4  (26:28)
I don't know if you're playing and I will continue to think about whether or not I 

Speaker 1  (26:34)
Continue to dangle it in front of them. Like, don't like I'm on the face of the AR. 

Speaker 4  (26:47)
I guess I still think they should talk to the fabric. Admit about it and not us but that I'm unsure. 

Speaker 1  (26:54)
Can we tell them that and close this out? 

Speaker 4  (26:57)
I did, but uh, U. 

Speaker 1  (26:59)
Maybe he I think. Right, that is what you suggested to him, and he came back basically saying like, I don't know how Which is like fair enough, but how is that Paul's problem? 

Speaker 4  (27:33)
Yeah Okay, my theory right now is that one of the things I need to give one of the fabric administrators authorizations that came in instance. So I can suggest that and then see where it goes, I didn't 

Speaker 1  (27:48)
I'll leave the photo a light with a shake. Our friend Gilroy off. Sent in Ulsan or meeting? 

Speaker 1  (27:55)
Yeah, I' All right, anything else in here that looks wrong. I know. If you could measure, let's check the backlog. 

Speaker 1  (28:08)
Anything else in here that looks urgent. 

Speaker 4  (28:14)
Oh, boy, I mean Probably a lot of it, but I 

Speaker 1  (28:22)
Not that one, though, okay, the reason that one comes to mind for me is because I did know it, but oh yeah, this is a consultation one, right, so there will invariably be 

Speaker 4  (28:32)
I keep eating that the purview side of the project if they are going to be proceeding with this, and they're just wrangling, or if they don't want to keep needing to check on that and see whether see whether I should cancel or not haven't done it yet. Yeah, I' 

Speaker 1  (28:48)
Sorry, because I but even if we were to close this, we wouldn't be able to close this epic, we had just had to keep it open for any additional consultations, right? Yeah, they want to okay, so then potato potatoes have Or if you ask them about it now or at some future date on this modules and support Sorry, miss delivery. Anything here that? 

Speaker 1  (29:11)
You feel I should supersede anything that you already have in your sprint. 

Speaker 4  (29:31)
No, I mean, I don't have I'm unsure what else I should bring in. It's really the creating the stories in some of these epics, like I was saying, for nps that need to have There, and then those question of whether those should take parity of oversteff, that there might be open I define what those are. 

Speaker 1  (29:51)
All right, so let's do that, then if you can spend some time looking at what other stories are needed for the NPS and writing those up, maybe we can look at them at a future date and see if Well, I mean, really at a future date, we'll be talking about Q4 stuff, but if we got them ready, by then we can talk about what the Q4 version of that MPs server looks epic. Looks like Alrighty, I think you're good for sprint 6, though. 

Speaker 3  (30:24)
I'm going to drop alt. 

Speaker 1  (30:25)
Yeah, for sure. Hope to feel better soon. My friend 

Speaker 5  (30:33)
Hi, how are you? Same hanging in there. 

Speaker 1  (30:39)
All right, all what you do I don't These are these real things that we can do in sprint, 6 consult with Jonathan, and I am authentication patterns. Is he writing to talk about this now? 

Speaker 5  (30:54)
I don't know, I don't think so, not yet, but we're not pretty sure when he will be. 

Speaker 1  (31:00)
And that doesn't sound like the sprint 6 activity to me in that case But I feel like we should drop that out. I mean, in any way, proactively, like, I mean, I know he knows that we're waiting for this, but is there anything else that we need to do to remind him? 

Speaker 5  (31:18)
I think we're I don't know Mike, have you talked to him I know that you sent me something yesterday and I'm gonna see if we meet with him soon. 

Speaker 6  (31:27)
Is that the one for 

Speaker 1  (31:30)
War. I'm Paul. 

Speaker 5  (31:35)
That's for yeah. 

Speaker 6  (31:37)
Are be so or I guess. Just cause our beast though, right. 

Speaker 5  (31:43)
Yeah, we have we finished that he did send a message any mail yesterday. I don't know if you saw saying that there was no problem. 

Speaker 1  (31:53)
But I'm assuming you closed that story 

Speaker 5  (31:56)
Yeah, I closed that one. 

Speaker 1  (32:00)
Okay, so no one consults with Jonathan on. I am authentication patterns in sports 6, because we're waiting for him to get back to us, I suppose, if he does at some point, we could move this into sprint 6 or whatever it is that 

Speaker 5  (32:14)
I can move it as soon as we get any update. 

Speaker 1  (32:17)
And then what's this research permission? 

Speaker 5  (32:21)
That when I'm working on 

Speaker 1  (32:22)
Oh, God, nice one. 

Speaker 5  (32:24)
That happens. 

Speaker 1  (32:26)
It's 2 points, the right size for it or 

Speaker 5  (32:29)
Yeah, I think that shouldn't 

Speaker 1  (32:32)
And then what else 

Speaker 5  (32:38)
Yeah, I was gonna reach out to Sam to see if there's anything on the Bau that I can. 

Speaker 1  (32:45)
We're gone, coupled with things that are proactively assigned to you in da. You one is this legacy Admin rolls Do you know what that is? It does not have a lot of Or any detel in there on Jeremy, they're not special, okay, so not that one. 

Speaker 1  (33:03)
But then what about this pim group thing? 

Speaker 5  (33:07)
Obviously yeah. No, this one, we're not not there. 

Speaker 1  (33:12)
Look up artwork. Alright, send me to find some stuff. Mike hall had any suggestions for where Molina should be directed to for the next two weeks. 

Speaker 6  (33:29)
Draw to the lob air Tecton epics Selena. I think we talked in our 1 on 1. If you want to take a gander through there and cherry pick one you like. 

Speaker 5  (33:41)
Yeah, I was looking this morning to see if there was something I can Scrabbing, learning something we love for guidance. 

Speaker 6  (33:48)
Into the corner is good. If you don't let me know, and I can find something, and you can try something new. 

Speaker 5  (33:56)
Yeah, this sounds good. I'll take a look and if anything I'll hear something. 

Speaker 1  (34:02)
Do you know how a story to a sprint and assign it to yourself? But in case you don't know where to find you definitely know how to ping me in teams and ask me for that as a matter of 

Speaker 6  (34:10)
Her option Melina, that you can help Paul out. Once we get clarity on the ubiko, is get your hands dirty with some app on boardings. Because it sounds like Paul, we'll eventually need to do that reading through the documentation from ubiko. 

Speaker 5  (34:28)
Yeah, I can meet with Paul as well. I can tease you, Paul and see if there's anything I can help you with. 

Speaker 6  (34:34)
I think there's one out there I saw Paul, I can give her, and that might be an easy one. 

Speaker 4  (34:41)
They have 5 votings for what sorry. 

Speaker 6  (34:44)
I thought I saw someone requesting an app bombarding that was out here, maybe it was an Seng but I'll find one for you, Emily, and if we don't have it here. 

Speaker 4  (34:51)
I mean, like ss h*. 

Speaker 6  (34:54)
Yeah, and that's 

Speaker 4  (34:55)
Oh, yeah, they've got. They have like 30th in that bag. Yeah, I got 

Speaker 6  (35:00)
I haven't done this, but it should be nice so hard to job on the one hand. 

Speaker 4  (35:05)
And then they and then did to get millennia, all the access that's required to help 

Speaker 6  (35:09)
Yeah, she's gotten needed anyway, so I figure let's have her struggle through one of these low-hanging fruit once, so she's ready to roll by time ubiko comes back around. 

Speaker 1  (35:21)
What epic is that for app onboard? 

Speaker 4  (35:23)
It's not, it's something it's until 

Speaker 1  (35:30)
All right, if you need my help to move that over et. Cetera, just point me at the ticket number at some point. Other than that, anything you want to bring up or Core related stuff colled. 

Speaker 1  (35:50)
Mike, you got this, consult for cyber arc integration. Created by my favorite PN do you know what this do you know what this is? No 

Speaker 4  (36:07)
I thought we were going to cancel this. There is no cyberwork integration. As you're Vicki. 

Speaker 4  (36:13)
It could be wrong, but I don't think it exists. 

Speaker 1  (36:17)
Mike, what are your opinions? 

Speaker 6  (36:22)
Why is Okay, I think this is an old one that I think we can close. I think this came out of the mythos KEDGE flare up paw on on And we don't need it, or we're not going to do it for a while. But decided 

Speaker 4  (36:42)
No, I guess I thought this was just reflecting what the 20 ubiquises that we gave to the cyborg team that they're using, and how they're going to deal with that in the future which is to say like, manual. Process for having ubiques, so 

Speaker 6  (36:57)
Yeah, I would just say dine, and to say, we discussed this, since there's only 20 of them Aron, we're just handling them manually, because it's only for the cyberark admins. 

Speaker 1  (37:23)
No cyber park. A lot of gunner canceled, don't We discussed something. Alrighty, anything else? 

Speaker 1  (37:52)
All right, folks, nothing else. Then let's send the call early. And yeah, let me know if anything comes up. 

Speaker 1  (38:03)
Doing good stuff, take care by the time you go. 
