
Speaker 1  (00:00)
It has us Curaçao. Hey, see there you go. 

Speaker 2  (00:09)
Did they once call 

Speaker 3  (00:12)
People call Curaçao karacha. Am I crazy? Where is 

Speaker 1  (00:18)
That's it the that's in the Caribbean, or something, isn't it? I thought it was 

Speaker 2  (00:26)
And caraca, or uh U. That's our institution. 

Speaker 1  (00:33)
Yeah, we're going to be embarrassed for geography pronunciation, dudes. 

Speaker 4  (00:37)
Curaçao is an island nation, a little bit north of lake marrakaibu, and caraca is the city that's somewhere in Venezuela. Okay, thank you, Dan, yep. 

Speaker 1  (00:55)
But you didn't tell me the way the eyes are right now. Yeah, I talk, Caribbean. And yeah, well like me and Grenada, and all that stuff down, it's down that far. 

Speaker 1  (01:06)
I thought 

Speaker 4  (01:07)
Nope, Grenada's Far East Curaçao is basically south-central Caribbean. It's just north of lake Maracaibo oh okay, okay? 

Speaker 1  (01:20)
You win the aint you working? Yeah, my daughter's like, I I'm pretty good, but those little ones roll me off in any event. I was also good with flags too, but okay, what do we have a pretty good crew here, but we're missing high on you, Mike, we're missing a couple people, and I guess while we're here because it's 5 past I have a litany of open items from my summary. 

Speaker 1  (01:44)
The other day. Just give me a second I had it on my screen. They were kind of carrying over the call them the action items for my teammate. 

Speaker 1  (01:54)
Pedan and Daniel for jet and Joel and myself, did anyone have a chance were those we gonna pick up with those team, would that be a safe Assumption we want to make sure those are done or did we have another item on the agenda I wasn't sure where we left it at the conclusion of the call. To be honest. It was the reaction I was like, Dan. 

Speaker 1  (02:16)
We're reach out to navenda via teams, confirming that we already covered that Control APIs query in specific real-time configuration settings and the log API documentation. I'm pretty sure you sent at the conclusion of the call or during the call. The other items team were for jet and Daniel, I'm 

Speaker 5  (02:41)
What were the items again? 

Speaker 1  (02:42)
So here I can pop them in again. I apologize, I sent a summary out yesterday, but I come in into this meeting I'm just coming out of a cutover, so I would have had a more succinct summary for the team I will try not to ever let this happen. But walking in here now. 

Speaker 1  (03:00)
These were action items in the email I sent from our call yesterday that put in a chat, I wasn't sure when we concluded our working session on Tuesday. Hey, are we picking up with making sure these Adona, or these homework items for the group go get these done either way. I'm responsible to put them on my plan, make sure they get done that typically would bother Dave and say, hey, these are the things at the end of a meeting, we gotta make sure they get done I fold the email into my completed file and we continue with the working session, this would be independent of that does that make sense team. 

Speaker 5  (03:35)
Yeah, I'm looking at Daniels and mine that those are done already. 

Speaker 1  (03:40)
Yeah, that's kind of what I thought. 

Speaker 4  (03:44)
It's fantastic. 

Speaker 5  (03:47)
And the removal of the received Headers, look good D km looks good as well for uaet, so td.com. We got that working. Yep, and of course, the disclaimer issue that was fixed as well. 

Speaker 5  (04:08)
So we're pretty much good with all the rules at this point. 

Speaker 4  (04:17)
I am quietly applauding you folks right here. 

Speaker 2  (04:25)
So what was the issue, Jack for that just 

Speaker 5  (04:28)
Just all I was copying the information from one of the emails. So I'm assuming something was slightly off. So I just copied it from the original annotation that I had set up in the rule. 

Speaker 5  (04:44)
Part of it and I plopped it into the knot, and that worked fine so that that stopped the duplication. 

Speaker 2  (04:52)
Oh, not the platform for that. Then come on. 

Speaker 5  (04:59)
And also I fixed that rule of yours, by the way. It's not an or it was supposed to be an ad, that's Yeah, it took me a few like She thought, and it's going, or that sounds familiar, that seems right. But then, you know, by the logic, we were doing it, it had to be in a Naan. 

Speaker 4  (05:22)
Yeah, sometimes there was like a lot of operators, just kellyah ya, thank you, thank you. 

Speaker 5  (05:29)
Yeah, so everything could for the disclaimer part 

Speaker 2  (05:34)
So what else do we have anything else that needs? Encryption, let's think about it. The encryption portion, okay, but that's Sr, so we're switching to acr right now. 

Speaker 2  (05:48)
So I figured out that TED's blocking connectivity out it's weird, because we can make the initial connection to proof point the Cr, but then so we get the panel and all that stuff, but as soon as we try to start kls, then it dies. Right from outside, it's working just fine and also from the server from from a server network, sorry from an IP of a server which is in a different zone. It works as fine right, but from the user, this is where we're trying to connect to a connect from, it's not working and that's something on the TV side that it's blocking that Video but yeah, from your vdi, so they told me no, but again. 

Speaker 2  (06:46)
In conflict of information, but anyway, that's something on that to decided that was blocking, right? So we're going to figure out that What was your question of 

Speaker 6  (06:59)
Let me share my screen. And I'm So last week we do I went into relay The music management I created this, I had problems relaying, but finally, when I used this idea. I was able to send an email now. 

Speaker 6  (07:27)
The question is these emails that are being relayed through this particular rule? How can we encrypt them? So I thought It would be something under email protection. 

Speaker 6  (07:40)
I went in there and I looked around, I went to email protection. 

Speaker 4  (07:49)
Let me just pause you there, those are going to be going out through the scr cluster, so you, if you are making the change to ser, you do want to make sure you're on that cluster. 

Speaker 2  (08:03)
Yeah, that, so go to the top, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah, trap right for sure, right, and you don't have acces. Let me. 

Speaker 6  (08:14)
Sure nice. If you got cutting a bit of 

Speaker 2  (08:21)
Sorry, let me share my screen. I'm sure that couldn't just 

Speaker 2  (08:42)
Okay, share. Yes, there' So this is See, I'm here have different clusters. 

Speaker 6  (09:06)
But I don't see them, right 

Speaker 5  (09:08)
When I lie yeah, you have a little more than me. Yeah, yeah, I don't sell the ser either. 

Speaker 2  (09:14)
So I have all of this cluster. So when you go in here and you see you have to look at 

Speaker 6  (09:24)
Those Put the rules up nice and such a line, and there's a desktop plugging encrypt, okay, now so I was looking for them and okay, so I don't see that particular cluster, I don't know, it's something that needs to be set app on my account. Everyone else so they could see. 

Speaker 2  (09:47)
Let me try to see if I can step it up to you right now. 

Speaker 6  (09:52)
But this is something you could do later too. So my question is, once you come in here. In order to Create AI could I see AI see a rule called subject lining print, right? 

Speaker 6  (10:10)
So I think it's going to look at the subject, if it has a specific ward, it's going to encrypt that message. And I believe that's just an example of a rule, they could probably copy that and create our own custom rule. Yeah, sure, but I'm just guessing I'm just guessing cool co. 

Speaker 4  (10:28)
You can use any pregnancer mechanism you want in the subject or body. 

Speaker 2  (10:32)
Yeah, and I can show you how to do that. 

Speaker 6  (10:36)
Already, I'm not going to ask any questions, so I already know what to do okay, so as long as I have access to that ser post of cluster, then we wish we 

Speaker 2  (10:46)
You just need access to this, because the rules to create them, it's fairly 

Speaker 6  (10:51)
That's going to be on this class, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I know, yeah. Yeah, try not. 

Speaker 4  (10:56)
And feel free to email me if you do have any questions at all about that. Yeah 

Speaker 6  (11:00)
Yeah, we'll do that for sure. 

Speaker 2  (11:03)
Where are you? 

Speaker 6  (11:08)
That's me, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (11:11)
But I thought there was a built-in, like, set up. I forgot where it was now. 

Speaker 4  (11:19)
There is it's in the oh oh, do you mean for the ruler for the admins? Sorry? 

Speaker 5  (11:23)
Or for the rule 

Speaker 4  (11:24)
Yeah, and the email firewall, there should be a subject line encrypt rule, and that's just looking for a key. 

Speaker 5  (11:31)
Oh, that's what you're using still right? Okay, you modified it, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (11:35)
And and you can, you can add any additional condition that you want to that, so you can have a bunch of ore conditions where it can be XYZ in the subject, or you know, a :) in the body of the email, really, whatever you want. 

Speaker 2  (11:51)
Then, what do I give him access to the cluster, they have access to? Oh, this side, but the clusters 

Speaker 4  (12:03)
What is that? So from the from the S ER hosted cluster? If you go to the admins on that left hand side, at least it used to be there, the double person icon right there. 

Speaker 2  (12:16)
Sorry, here US. 

Speaker 4  (12:20)
The double people icon And then under administrators, do we have the ability to add him? We do 

Speaker 2  (12:28)
Upper right corner, I had to 

Speaker 4  (12:31)
And you should be able to select which cluster 

Speaker 2  (12:35)
Okay, okay, I see. That's Katie, ask me the email address again that you're using first chef sure, yeah. Yeah, I get because I know you're not using your feet. 

Speaker 2  (13:09)
Okay, are Samsung, just scrap it right now? Oh, it's just that the you're already you're already there. Okay, so 

Speaker 5  (13:17)
Can you have more than one closure to it? 

Speaker 2  (13:19)
Yes, I'm going to try, so edit, thank you. I'd another 10 yeah, there you go. Not in just yet, because this is not something that we managed 

Speaker 6  (13:37)
Yeah, don't give me anything, not really. 

Speaker 2  (13:40)
No, the dlp, it's their s*** right, and they're working true well. 

Speaker 6  (13:43)
Today, if it's not related, I don't 

Speaker 2  (13:46)
So this is, so this is it. And jet for you to write Check that our escape. Well, you have the tlp. 

Speaker 2  (14:01)
But you don't have the esr, okay? 

Speaker 5  (14:06)
How come you have the rights to add? And I don't 

Speaker 4  (14:10)
That's it within managed stopproof point.com. 

Speaker 2  (14:15)
Okinaw, that's how it works, Chad. 

Speaker 4  (14:21)
And somehow the powers that we decided Daniel was going to be one of the people who could give and remove access. 

Speaker 5  (14:28)
Absolutely, that's fine. 

Speaker 2  (14:30)
Absolutely. Absolutely. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (14:31)
So now you guys should have, can you do? I'm sure I should 

Speaker 6  (14:36)
I do I do I see 

Speaker 2  (14:38)
Okay, perfect. Okay, I just want to make sure that you can. You can go into your testing and all that stuff properly. 

Speaker 6  (14:44)
Thanks, Dani, stanium, appreciate, okay. 

Speaker 2  (14:47)
Oh? Further, then for ser The S ER authentication portion is clear. That's that's easy, we can we can do that then emails after S ER they go to wear. 

Speaker 4  (15:07)
When you authenticate, you are authenticating with a cloud service shared across all proof point customers and we know that it is yours, based on the goid, that's the username, and then the password once it goes through that layer, it goes through a dedicated S ER cluster, which is what you saw in that upper right? Hand corner, drop down. 

Speaker 2  (15:28)
Okay. I Don' what it's in that cluster. 

Speaker 6  (15:36)
We have 

Speaker 2  (15:37)
I have dlp, and we have to have some type of an mta right? 

Speaker 4  (15:44)
Yes, I mean, it is an mta. Every proof weight cluster has the mta built-in. I don't know offhand if that one is licensed for dlp. 

Speaker 2  (15:55)
Okay, so we're gonna need to work this this stuff out because everything we cannot send anything outbound without the lp period okay, there's no outbound traffic. Does not go through the dop, there's no such complaints. Yeah, right now, I'm not worried right now because we still have the old dlp in place, but not for tests, right? 

Speaker 2  (16:24)
Because this is going to be a their connection, right? Yep, so so we need, I need to understand a little bit, how where is the dealp coming into play? I understand for the other cluster, the regular 1 that first is going to be the dlp for outbound, right, and then the dlp, which created the routes, to route the traffic back glass, right? 

Speaker 2  (16:49)
Right? But in this case, is that kind of like the same thing. Can we specify after the authentication to go to the dlp, and then or how is that going to work? 

Speaker 4  (17:01)
Yeah, it's going to be basically the same thing I'm reaching out to hardest right now to get the technical details. 

Speaker 2  (17:07)
Okay. Okay. Yes, I would like to understand that. 

Speaker 2  (17:14)
And how do we configure that? 

Speaker 5  (17:21)
I was just wondering if that's the case, is we not Federal on the DLP portion, right Do you have any direct On the dlp side on that side, yeah, if it's going to dlp first Do we not put the the firewall rule redirect there to send to The theory. Feels like a gearbox, but it's just scarcely a bit 

Speaker 2  (18:03)
No, but this is a different part right? 

Speaker 5  (18:07)
Yeah, but they're saying that the lime man is the same right? So normally. 

Speaker 2  (18:12)
You will work the same way but I don't. It's a different puddle together. Right, my understanding then that's what it is right. 

Speaker 4  (18:21)
I believe so so 

Speaker 2  (18:22)
Yeah, so the S ER Bud in itself, that's a cell sustain, has the authentication piece first, and then it has the dlp and the mta attached to it, and my understanding from that was that it's working seamlessly, they're seamlessly integrated from one to another, they flow one to another now. I need to understand how that flow works and where do you configure the stuff because if I manage just the relay portion of it, I'm not seeing anything in here that I can do with it. 

Speaker 4  (18:58)
And that's where I'm getting all clarification on right now. Of course 

Speaker 2  (19:02)
Yeah, yeah, so unless the flu is automatic, it's, it's automated behind the scenes that if you do have the DLP but then where would you see that? And how would you configure that that's right. Yeah, so if you can get that by clarify for us that would yeah, because that's the piece that I have. 

Speaker 1  (19:26)
For 1 second, we do not have email DLP for S ER here. We have email DLP for your user traffic. Okay, that data that I'm 99 and 9one0 certain on, we've gone over this, but if you're asking about how are we DLP for S ER that that I mean Greg's here and I don't know if nab's here, I don't remember that oneI know we have email dlp. 

Speaker 2  (19:55)
So all of our outbound, I'll tell you right now, all of our outbound email has to go through the deal. Bhutan, it's impossible for 

Speaker 1  (20:02)
All right, so let me deny, I don't see that reference, but there's a slim chance I could have missed it. I don't think so, I'll double-check with Greg and navinda and like, all, you know, I'll look at all of our skus. I don't remember seeing email dlp for ser, but there's a small chance I overlooked, and I 

Speaker 2  (20:23)
You don't know. That's okay. I'm just saying that like this is the requirements that we have if that all the outbound emails, they have to be scanned by blp. 

Speaker 2  (20:32)
Now do we need to have separate instances of dlp? For every single part? I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (20:41)
That's something that maybe you guys can tell us if that's how it works. Yeah, or can we have a single instance of the dlp in one part, and then we can use that as the entry point, and everything else, it's going to get, it's going to get If we're from there or split from there, right? 

Speaker 3  (21:02)
Traffic application traffic would never be sent through your user pod. No 

Speaker 2  (21:08)
Again, I understand that, and that's, and it makes sense, I just don't know how that works right for the S. E! R. 

Speaker 2  (21:16)
If you' 

Speaker 3  (21:16)
Alp is going to let's, yeah, let's let's just instead of us talking about it anymore, let's just get you the answer 

Speaker 2  (21:21)
All right, okay, all right 

Speaker 1  (21:24)
So that's that. We'll, we'll is that a place to just carry on move forward, ser Actually, notably, I'd like to take this opportunity team, because as ATP M and I think you can appreciate this Daniel, and everyone on the call, I just came back from leave. I said to note to Daniel and Dave, I don't know if Dave you out there my tpf, you, he and I we had a postponed a couple of meets, we had a postpone and reschedule a couple meetings. 

Speaker 1  (21:56)
But particularly Daniel, I just emailed yourself, I don't know the other day yesterday, or the day before right around these types of topics, I'd like to meet with you Anya and jet and Dave offline and a better align our agenda coming back to email, particularly because I need to promote to all of you, I'm responsible to all of you a little greater transparency around the world where we're going and how we're spending our time in these working sessions does that make sense to everyone I have a pretty good idea. 

Speaker 1  (22:30)
We're okay and I'm saying quite sheepishly, but I don't think I'm communicating that. Well, and that's so I yeah. 

Speaker 2  (22:38)
Yeah, I don't have a problem with that we can. We can definitely have a call about 

Speaker 1  (22:43)
The alignment. Yeah, I just want I just want to tight. I want to tighten some screws here a little bit and say, okay, this week, we've this is where we are. 

Speaker 1  (22:52)
We've configured, instead of it being up, you're going through rules, we're almost done with that. We have to do some testing. I'd like to we talked yesterday the other day about what does testing mean? 

Speaker 1  (23:02)
How exhaustive, what is the timeline? These are, the things we talked about, that would incorporate questions like email dlp, it will incorporate things like ser, because those ser is its own animal, it's not complicated, but how many applications do you have? What are your requirements for testing those applications? 

Speaker 1  (23:19)
All of that I'd like to, that's all yeah? How's this I know? I threw a lot at yaw. 

Speaker 2  (23:28)
Jim, unfortunately, it's not as easy or as direct as you might think, we're working on multiple streams at the same time. So while Jed is doing the, you know, the testing of the rules I have. I have, you know, for sure, I had working on the Sr, and how that's going to impact how the how that works. 

Speaker 2  (23:50)
So we're finding various things as we go along, for example, as I said we have an issue right now in which we cannot reach a racir at this point in time. Right, so we have to work on something and I'm doing that at the back and interview to get that going right. But it's not as easy as it seems, because we have to open up for all the servers that are going to consume the acr, and that's a much bigger animal. 

Speaker 2  (24:15)
So there's a lot of these small little things that, you know, we're only discovering as we go, you saw right now, we don't have, you know, first-hand didn't have permission to actually even see that plaster, right, so we're going to encounter a lot of this, and as much as I like the format in which everything is clear and consistent, right? I don't think that that's going to happen for the immediate future, right? Well, we can have a conversation. 

Speaker 1  (24:44)
Yeah, I'm not saying we're not going to trip wires, all I'm getting at is I'd like to see the road at least and so we'll take it offline here because yeah, today was learning for the first time. Hey, let's just pivot to ser, and I think I could I owe you the responsibility of preparing our teams for that's what we're going to talk about over the next week or 2? Similarly, any of those things you're calling out, I'd love to forecast it. 

Speaker 1  (25:11)
So we have we have the tools ready to go at least at a minimum, and if we trip a wire, then we work on that that's off, I think we can do it, but I just want to Para, that's all 

Speaker 6  (25:24)
I have a question on encryption, actually 

Speaker 3  (25:28)
We prepare for Chad, I just want to follow-up on the last conversation that we're having, I did check and I didn't want to speak up before I checked, dlp will happen on the on the ser cluster that's where it will be enabled if it should be licensed. And that's where dlp will happen for application traffic that is routed through ser 

Speaker 2  (25:47)
But okay, person 

Speaker 6  (25:49)
Fantastic. Thank you for the correct information regarding the protection, the encryption, our existing encryption service today. It provides 2 types of profile for external customers. 

Speaker 6  (26:06)
One is called web mode. The other one is PDF mode. Webport, I believe, is very similar to what proofpoint provides, where email is encrypted, and a notification is sent to the Excel customer, they click on a link, they log into a portal and they could get to see the email. 

Speaker 6  (26:25)
The PDF model is where they don't have to log into any portal, they actually receive a PDF, encrypted file that they have to have the passport for it in their own email account. Whether it's Gmail hype mail wherever they are. I want to know if proof point also provides something like that where they don't, where the customer doesn't necessarily have to log into a portal in order to see their email, there would be another option where they actually receive the email and the email itself is encrypted, where they may need to have a password. 

Speaker 6  (27:00)
In order to go to it See the content of that email is this something proofpoint provides or not yet now 

Speaker 4  (27:07)
That is not a feature of our product oklaho. 

Speaker 6  (27:11)
Is this something that is on any roadmap or There's some questions I have to answer. Yeah, of course, because you know, they're going to say, hey, you know, we have, let's say 50% of our customers on PD. F. 

Speaker 6  (27:23)
Then how does it going to work when we move to proofpoint? And that kind of questions I need to just address. 

Speaker 7  (27:33)
Yeah, I could take that for us to understand there's no plans to support secure PDF, secure, zip or any of those other methods of encrypting the payload, and then providing a service to manage passwords, our method is portal encryption, we support both push and pull with portal encryption, and so yeah, if that is a requirement, then for your business. Yeah, that's not something I anticipate will be delivering the foreseeable future. 

Speaker 4  (28:08)
Okay, so we're going to get an RFE in front of product engineering. 

Speaker 6  (28:16)
We will discuss that with our manager and the powers to be and see what they say about it, I mean, they may, they may even say, well, it is what it is right. Companies move from one technology to another, and customers have to follow that could be one attitude and then the other one could be wow, maybe we should have okay, let's put rfc in the effor. 

Speaker 8  (28:41)
But I would argue that, you know, doing that requires somebody to download. And the whole thing is, is that people want it to be mobile friendly, that's not really mobile friendship. 

Speaker 4  (28:53)
Exactly just how I am it is. 

Speaker 8  (28:55)
Just by two sets 

Speaker 7  (28:56)
Yeah, it's on his point that's been my feedback. Melissa banking clients are going to interact on their smartphone Vs like a laptop, having a PDF experience is a little bit more cumbersome on that versus a desktop experience. So so the the the the Web only experience is much more Portable and also improved deliverability, especially around organizations like, you know, in our best practice is to block password protected files. 

Speaker 7  (29:29)
So that was the reason why we never went down the path of secured PDF. So we can discuss the pros and cons but I can but the that's the main thing about that delivery method, but if your business absolutely needs it for a specific use case maybe insurance needs to send out their certificate and this is the method then we won't be able to support that. But if it's mostly B to C. 

Speaker 7  (30:00)
And it's like, quick updates, the other method of portal which, you know, is that because we can bring them into, like a web base interface, it's very easy for them to do an attachment to attach a file so one common use case is especially during COVID was exchanging. Like mortgage application documents and so forth, many clients don't have access to like maybe a printer, but they can take a picture and then attach that picture in the portal interface and then send it back so we can definitely give you or your business Partners like the demonstration of our experience is probably not unlike what they probably already see with the portal, but it'd be good for them to see, you know, some of the differences with our technology. 

Speaker 2  (30:52)
You mentioned that you have 2, you support 2 ways full and push. How is that going to work to push? 

Speaker 7  (30:59)
Yeah, push what we do is that we send the ciphertext to the user. The user register, then, when they click on the link, the cipher text is posted back to our portal, and then the message is rendered. So that's pushed, pull means you just get a link. 

Speaker 7  (31:19)
And then you click on the link and it copied the message that's retained in or portal. We retain a copy of the message for one year if they need to access it beyond one year, then they have the post method that's typically why you would use post over push 

Speaker 2  (31:43)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (31:54)
Jed, do you have any other questions regarding the rules? You're 

Speaker 5  (32:03)
Oh, sorry, that was me, no, I'm good. 

Speaker 2  (32:11)
Okay, what else is there? No, I think that's a that's it, at least for the path environment, right? I'm working right now to cut over some domains actually all of our domains that we have. 

Speaker 5  (32:39)
We'll probably have to go through the other rules again. It's pretty for the broad side, right? 

Speaker 2  (32:44)
Of course, of course, of course. I'm just talking about the rhino specifically for for for Pat. Because yeah, yeah, that's what we care. 

Speaker 2  (32:58)
Did we were we successful in testing that they came a jet? 

Speaker 5  (33:03)
Yeah, it's passing, it's working. 

Speaker 2  (33:05)
I'll see right now, okinaw. Because that took a long time to replicate, for example, formalized life 

Speaker 5  (33:11)
Yeah, as do you enable it, it took a good hour at least or what sounds like an hour at least? 

Speaker 2  (33:20)
No, because I enabled that the night before. 

Speaker 5  (33:23)
Yeah, I don't want to do a collaboration because I kept testing it and and it will still fail. I didn't see it until like I checked another, I waited an hour. And then it started, I started seeing the the decam stamping good, so it took a long time. 

Speaker 2  (33:43)
Yeah So we have the decam, the stamps Yeah, thank you. The S PF it is enabled now. There is perfect enable. 

Speaker 2  (34:02)
We should disable that Because we don't have, we don't currently have a disabled and we're not going to have it enabled in production. Okay, write this, PF, checking the air. Yes, that's a that's a different type of Then, remind me, is there for spf. 

Speaker 2  (34:27)
If we enable it, can we create exceptions? 

Speaker 4  (34:32)
Absolutely. We can have a multiple spf policies based on policy route. 

Speaker 2  (34:39)
Okay, so this is a yeah, so to go ahead. 

Speaker 4  (34:44)
We typically recommend starting out with 3 policies, one will be your domains, and that will include emails that your organization has send and any vendor sending, as you one will be verified demark, i.e. partner or vendor organizations you work with where, you know, they're demark, record is P equals reject, and you trust all of the email from them, and then the 3rd category will be everybody else, so we can look to take that trusted demarc category and set rejects on spf hurdles and demark failures for that one onest. 

Speaker 2  (35:22)
Yeah, no, but this is going to be great, because right now. Currently, that's that's one of the reasons why we did not necessarily enable spf. On the second, it's because we don't have a way to create exceptions, right? 

Speaker 2  (35:36)
And we know that there will be exceptions for we will need to create exemptions. 

Speaker 4  (35:45)
Because nothing can actually let me do that. 

Speaker 2  (35:47)
Yeah, so that's why if we can, if we have some Partners that, you know, yeah, they didn't get their s*** together. And they didn't, they don't have the proper records, we and we still need to do business with them, we could add them to an exemption based of some kind, okay. 

Speaker 4  (36:03)
A 100% with you on that, and it's as easy as policy route. 

Speaker 2  (36:07)
Okay, okay, okay. Same, so the dicka. And that's going to, that's also enabled, okay, we're going to have to figure out that and the debarts enabled, they came signing, no I think we're good Tap, it's working. 

Speaker 2  (36:37)
Well, yeah, we're in the process right now in doing the single sign on Anya, it's working on that so so to see how that works and also to figure out any you're also working on on the user. Or how are we getting the user? The 

Speaker 8  (36:59)
I'm gonna have both of those done on Monday, so they're both polls from app registration. So Both of those will be done on Monday on just prepping the ticket for the second half, so I've already done it for sso and boatley. I'm working on the ticket for the aldepack bill. 

Speaker 2  (37:19)
So what are you putting the users from Andre Andra, okay. 

Speaker 6  (37:26)
Whatever? 

Speaker 4  (37:26)
Thank you for being proactive on you. 

Speaker 2  (37:32)
Okay, also adding to it. I saw the ticket I approved. I approved the first one so whenever you need the second one, let me know anymore. 

Speaker 8  (37:41)
Yeah, maybe while I have you, we should create what you might call it those pad instances, because again of those malcodes, just because otherwise we have to wait 5 days. 

Speaker 2  (37:56)
Should you say that again? 

Speaker 8  (37:58)
You need Pat instances of those configuration items. Otherwise, you have to go by paid the time. 

Speaker 2  (38:09)
There isn't no, there is a path No molocode, there's something in there that I could use, don't worry. Yeah, when you create the change record, there is one of the option is path, no malcode, or some stupidity like that. And if you select that you can go ahead. 

Speaker 8  (38:35)
Yeah, I' 

Speaker 2  (38:36)
Yeah, so you don't have to wait the 5 days. I don't think we tried this before remember. With the sec with the semantic, we try to create a path instance, a male code for the path instance, but because I don't remember the exact reasons why. 

Speaker 2  (38:55)
Because it was a cloud service and they don't have any type of infrastructure, they couldn't actually put it in India. In ServiceNow not yeah, not in ServiceNow in whatever. As A bad instance, so we still have production is still a products. 

Speaker 2  (39:12)
The production instance and we still have to wait 5 days, but Wow, just shrunk in there that I can that I can something else that I can use. 

Speaker 8  (39:24)
Okay, if you can can pass me that later, then I can finish off this ticket. Yeah, yeah. Let me just sorry, that was an aside nothing with other than that. 

Speaker 8  (39:37)
We'll have that we can probably go into production. For the single sign on and the ldep queries If we have our prod instance, I can get those done like Probably mid, July or Yeah, after after the Pat 1 is done, hopefully we'll get that all done by the end of June, we can do all that other stuff prepping we won't have the rules in place. But at least all that single side on everything can be tested probably sometime may July. 

Speaker 3  (40:20)
And when do we start planning the end user experience? In other words, obviously the user digest is going to be sent to all your end users when messages are stopped on their behalf by us that are non malicious. 

Speaker 8  (40:34)
So you're asking what we cut over domains. So 

Speaker 3  (40:38)
I'm not asking I'm not asking a cut over, no, I'm asking about prep that we need to do to make sure that we have all the communications and everything in order for your end users is that currently being worked on is that something we need to discuss? 

Speaker 8  (40:53)
It's not being worked on at all, so we're going to have to discuss it. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 3  (40:57)
All right, I think that that's an important topic of conversation and one that we can have, you know, immediately, because we do have all we have a lot of material that we can provide to you that are templates, and that sort of stuff for end user experience. So I think we should gather that up, and get that over to you as soon as possible. 

Speaker 4  (41:13)
We'll start working on that. Very often it's those end users that are going to make or break the success of these transitions. 

Speaker 3  (41:23)
Dan, if you have got that package done, can you please send it to the team? 

Speaker 4  (41:27)
I don't, because they've moved everything to communities, but I do have links somewhere, and I will get that to Tim thanks 

Speaker 2  (41:33)
Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (41:34)
I speed, I maybe even have the same, because everything went from 2A community link. 

Speaker 2  (41:43)
Quick question for you, I ran into an issue yesterday when opening a firewall, not an issue, but It was weird, so I had to open app a firewallish, a firewall request, but now on our side and the engineer from the other side they wanted to see the document that you guys have for acr and IPS behind that right, how can I get that to him? Because right now everything is behind a logging 

Speaker 3  (42:11)
You can download the feed from the article 

Speaker 2  (42:13)
If there's high I was looking at that, and I couldn't figure out how to download it, there was nothing there there that there 

Speaker 3  (42:19)
It's possible there isn't a PDF for the article you're looking at, but it likes to hide in the page itself. I'll tell you that. 

Speaker 2  (42:26)
I don't even know if I have it right now open anymore. Okay, let me just see if I can go to my history. 

Speaker 3  (42:36)
Well, I'll do a search You're just looking for the ser deployment guide. 

Speaker 2  (42:43)
No, it was an article about acr. IPS, we cannot use fqdns on the fiber rules for whatever reason, so they want to use, they want to use its. So I had to. 

Speaker 2  (43:00)
Yeah, so I was searching for a for the article that was giving me that and I did find it, it was not hard to find. It's just and see if I can bridge quickly right now, tonight. 

Speaker 3  (43:19)
Do you know the name of the guy he's talking about to I don't Okay, I got it here. And then we shot the Kitch. And then let's see, where's the down? 

Speaker 3  (44:10)
This might be one of those that doesn't have a PDF, so that you'll just have to copy and paste the article. 

Speaker 4  (44:16)
Or you can do a print to PDF, I would think or 

Speaker 3  (44:19)
Parents of pediatricians, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (44:26)
But the bigger question is, why do you have this behind the locu? 

Speaker 3  (44:30)
Because Danny, because we don't have a good explanation, it is what it is and it aint getting changed, so I'm sorry for that. 

Speaker 4  (44:38)
Yeah, product engineering has determined that there may or may not be some mildly proprietary information in some of those articles, so we are very much trying to limit it to just proofpoint customers, then the anecdote editors scrubbing it, and exactly that's actually the exact anecdote that I heard is that minecast was taking. Some of our documentation, because it was better than theirs, essentially 

Speaker 2  (45:03)
Okay, so this is, let me just share my screen quickly, because I found that 

Speaker 3  (45:10)
I did put the Lincoln 

Speaker 2  (45:11)
And 

Speaker 6  (45:12)
The worst, the browser here 

Speaker 2  (45:15)
Yeah, so this, this was the exact article. 

Speaker 3  (45:21)
Most articles, when you scroll 3, quite, you'll find a little tiny section that has download links for pdfs. This one unfortunately doesn't 

Speaker 2  (45:33)
He wanted to like, I give him this because I just allowed the IPS for this. So the United States and Canada, not the UAE right. But he wanted to see the list, the exact article because for his manager right to open app all of this right, and I couldn't give it, I sent him a screenshots and stuff like that and I said like I'm sorry but I cannot give it to you right so it would be very handy if you would be somehow an option to go to be. 

Speaker 2  (46:06)
You know, even bdf yeah, like, I guess you can print it to the PDF sure, yeah, but again that's not necessarily 

Speaker 4  (46:16)
Not always the easiest option. 

Speaker 2  (46:17)
This, but whatever it is, what it is, right. 

Speaker 3  (46:20)
Yes, duly noted for the feedback. We appreciate it. 

Speaker 2  (46:25)
Yeah, if it's nothing yeah, yeah? 

Speaker 6  (46:29)
Is the information that you're looking for on this webpage? Yeah? Yeah, well, why can't we just give him the link? 

Speaker 4  (46:37)
Because they need a proofwind authorized support 

Speaker 2  (46:41)
Behind the login, all right, you have to log in, you have an account. 

Speaker 4  (46:45)
And you can add it really as many authorized support contacts, as you need. So if you did want to add 1 of them to that list of admins, you could do so and then they could log in and see all this. 

Speaker 2  (47:00)
I know, but I mean, that's awfully complicated for something that they just need to see once right, because that's that's that's all it is, right. 

Speaker 4  (47:07)
I've run into stuff like that when I was approved point customer at my old organization it was the same thing the network security team, the people who managed the firewall said, oh hey, we need this and we need an actual copy of the article so I sent him a screenshot and they said, well, that's not good enough we need a link, so then I said, well, to get to the link, we're going to have to create an account and sign in. And they're like, well, we can't do that. Well, pick and choose, there's your 2 options. 

Speaker 2  (47:32)
Yeah, so pretty much the same conversation was with me yesterday, but the difference was that they were okay with just messing them a screenshot. Of this, yeah, with the url with the link, like to make sure that it's coming, they're okay with that right. Right? 

Speaker 2  (47:49)
So 

Speaker 4  (47:50)
They are beholden to auditors, and they need to show that link, and maybe, you know, years down the road, an auditor will come back with. Oh, we tried to follow that link you gave us to verify XY and Z and we couldn't access it, but most of the time, the auditors just want to see that it is a link and it was verified 

Speaker 2  (48:09)
I didn't just request that it would summarize out of my a**, right? So that's why they wanted, yeah, so that's why they wanted to have something, but they were okay with this right. So, but I found a little bit, I found it a little bit Hard to do. 

Speaker 2  (48:26)
But anyway, it is what it is. As you said, it is what it is. We're a good 

Speaker 4  (48:33)
Okay, you are on a roll today. Daniel, I appreciate you 

Speaker 2  (48:40)
Yeah, it's just it is what it is. Okay. So there's I don't have anything else I don't think that we have anything else jet for shard, or anybody else on the line for that matter. 

Speaker 6  (48:53)
Last question. So if I create a user management rule for my application to be able to relay, should that rule be sitting on the same cluster that I'm going to create all the encryption rules under production under email protection. 

Speaker 4  (49:12)
Is this for application traffic? 

Speaker 6  (49:14)
Yes, for application traffic. 

Speaker 4  (49:17)
Yeah, you'll want it on that ser cluster specifically, okay. 

Speaker 6  (49:29)
I don't have any more questions so jet. If you do 

Speaker 2  (49:33)
Go for it. Thank Okay, so what do you guys and getting them back? We can pick mixed up 

Speaker 5  (49:41)
Yeah, get them an extra 3 minutes, 3 minutes, because we usually cut off 5 minutes early. 

Speaker 4  (49:48)
I don't like to think of it as cutting off early. I like to think of it as giving me time to grab a glass of water or use absolutely. 

Speaker 2  (49:55)
Absolutely, absolute, we're gonna give you 

Speaker 5  (49:58)
3 yesterday, a minute, that's the start. 

Speaker 4  (50:01)
I would f******, I can grab a snack too. 

Speaker 2  (50:04)
Okay, gentlemen, until next time. 

Speaker 4  (50:07)
Thank you all so much weekend, everybody 
