
Speaker 1  (00:00)
So that we don't have to get into any of this kiosk type scenario, at least not for the self-service. I mean, maybe that comes into play with manager assisted. But for the for the full self-service It wouldn't be full self-service if they need to go to someone else's. 

Speaker 2  (00:19)
Yeah, and you can see that that's the green line full cell service. He goes through, he identifies himself. There was discussion in last week's. 

Speaker 2  (00:28)
I don't know if you're already there for Andrew's gsd meetings, you know, the ones, he has weekly, I believe they are they want to flow this through identity proofing, which Jane is working on. I think vm has a separate project going on for identity. Yeah, I don't know whether there's funding and all I don't want to go into solutioning, but that was what has brought up. 

Speaker 2  (00:55)
So that's why I put it as a separate module, just identity, you know, it could be through identity proofing, it could be through some document, upload, you know, put, you know, upload your driver's license, only then I can let you register key or something like that. But then you would also like, you know, Jeremy loves the point of it going through sale point and workday, and you know, you know, blood ride access, those type of things, he loves that idea so I don't know whether they're going to combine everything. 

Speaker 2  (01:26)
I don't know how to go into solution, but yeah, that's why I put identity as a separate module, we can always plug and play Here. 

Speaker 1  (01:34)
And then I put It's very confusing, a few things there are actually Anthony. So the like The birthright entitlement port. Which, yes, I expect, would run through sale points, and then you know, the ub Fido connector out for provisioning, but that that's for The film that aspect has got nothing to do with this recovery. 

Speaker 2  (02:00)
Welcome so that we can put out in the provisioning hall. And I guess that would come in the provisioning model over here M4 in the game. 

Speaker 1  (02:10)
Okay, okay. Okay. Yeah, I made it that okay. 

Speaker 2  (02:13)
Where, you know, where we put it, that's a different that would be a completely designed kind of architectural decision, I'm just making sure we can separate them, and you know, maybe tomorrow somebody called phydoch, you know, td, ubiquity, some other company may come up, and we can just plug and play with them, we Don 't need to really be tied to ubk, APIs and sdks, and those type of things So that's why I put hardware provisioning in the 

Speaker 3  (02:45)
I am sorry, but we're talking about ubiquit. 

Speaker 2  (02:48)
Yeah 

Speaker 3  (02:49)
But what you're talking about 

Speaker 2  (02:51)
You know, but I think as far as we're concerned, we should make it. We should make it, you know, we should make it a model, because we don't want to be tied to a particular vendor because that's what happens in tds, I've not seen anybody, they don't want in the past 5 years, I've been watching the fun. It's like, okay, every 3 years, we seem to be changing vendors. 

Speaker 2  (03:18)
So keeping the hardware profitioning separately would allow us to be, you know, when diagnostic at some point, if necessary. And then, of course, so those 2 would work together, but a separate models. 

Speaker 3  (03:40)
No, no, so this is where I'm a little bit, I think the idea, the idea that there's an identity verification application, that right engine is a little bit a generic term. Whenever really. 

Speaker 2  (03:57)
Remember the code, I'm sure how to get the code if you don't want 

Speaker 3  (04:03)
And the second one around the secure session isolator is I think that's really like that's an alternative. 

Speaker 2  (04:13)
O'reilly, that's an old interview, dude. 

Speaker 3  (04:15)
So you end up like, as following one another in the diagram, I guess I would say, but I also, well, I actually I'm not sure if we've really, we have really haven't gotten to the level of detail in the flows to determining if the secure the isolated secure browser, let's call it right is A 

Speaker 2  (04:36)
It's a viable option. It could 

Speaker 3  (04:39)
Or whether the user would be invoking the identity verification application with the secure browser or if they would be Enroking the There's an intraid Myself registration in her face, I think to some extent 

Speaker 2  (04:57)
Yeah, and my backyard, this one I like to my sign on thing. I think you're talking about the Nile sign. 

Speaker 1  (05:04)
Anthony, can I share my 

Speaker 2  (05:06)
Yeah, yeah, sure, go ahead, go ahead. 

Speaker 1  (05:08)
Okay, I want to take one step back, I had put together a blow myself a few weeks back just, you know, so I could try to step through it and work it out. So this is a recovery scenario. And And I think yours is definitely 1 or 2 steps beyond this, but I like to start with simple and so this here, as you can see by the title there. 

Speaker 1  (05:37)
This is, I have nothing, right? I am now a nobody. I've lost it. 

Speaker 1  (05:42)
I've lost my ub. I don't have a backup mobile passky. I got nothing. 

Speaker 1  (05:48)
So scroll down, you're Be quickly because, okay, I got nothing. I need to re-establish identity, but what are they gonna do how they're gonna do that. And I'm saying from your mobile phone, you're gonna hit this employee portal, which we have to build. 

Speaker 1  (06:04)
Okay, when you're on that employee portal, you're gonna click whatever option. You know, I'm a nobody I need to recover my identity, and that's going to send you off to some process to be determined, it could be a third party idv. Right maybe maybe if we don't get funding for that, we've got to send it off to this to the service desk and the sale point one time password type scenario, regardless some form of identity verification will have to happen. 

Speaker 1  (06:39)
Right? So once that has happened. It could issue a temporary access pass Through entra, we give it to the user. 

Speaker 1  (06:49)
The user then gets You know, redirect it to the my account port. Where they're going to be prompted for the tap, and that's all great, and then they could go ahead. And register the new ubiquity. 

Speaker 1  (07:04)
And then I also threw in this part about, hey, we really should be deleting the old, the old, the old one. So this was my, you know, higher level version, and then, like I said, you're probably a couple steps ahead there. And saying, okay, what does hey, we need to build an employee portal? 

Speaker 1  (07:25)
We need to do something for identity verification. 

Speaker 3  (07:28)
Yeah, those are actually if we're taking, if we're taking Anthony's Module modular definition approach, right? The employee portal is distinct from the identity verifications system process. So there's 2 pro things there that maybe Anthony eve pushed one, which is 

Speaker 2  (07:50)
As to how we are, I just created models based on my understanding, subject to change. 

Speaker 3  (07:58)
The useful discussion. And that's right, given the trends to make things clearer, so I think, Jonathan, I like that flow. That one of many options for one of the 6 flavors of that same flow. 

Speaker 3  (08:13)
That are possible, but I think that's a mobile only I don't have msuth indicator I have a mobile device, but I don't have ms authenticator flow, you have been and I am physically resident in a branch so A physical asset somewhere, as I guess everybody's gotta feel. 

Speaker 1  (08:33)
Right, everybody, everybody's got a phone. We don't Nope, we hope and and but that is the prerequisite in my mind for being able to do a full self-service recovery, right. The 2 paths, if you got the phone okay, you're on your way, you're on the way, if you've got the phone, you have you got the key, you know. 

Speaker 1  (08:53)
The blank the blank key. Okay, you're on your way. 

Speaker 3  (08:56)
So let's let's let's let's if we want it, if we'd like this, if we want to do something like this modular approach, then we have two things that we just identified, one of which isn't done here, or the identity verification engine was really two things. Right it's a user portal, a user, you know, many of us are 

Speaker 2  (09:17)
I go to solutioning whether it's a portal white, whether it's a cube. 

Speaker 3  (09:22)
No, the identity, the identity verification process is different than the presentation layer, so there are distinct components right? The identity verification process and the user interface presentation are different. 

Speaker 2  (09:38)
We have used the entry points here right at the top. If you look at this and this could be, this is your UI kind of thing, and this is your orchestra. We've 

Speaker 3  (09:48)
What is a self-service self service mobile user? But that's not the application that they will be accessing. 

Speaker 2  (09:54)
We don't know. Yeah, that's what our discussion so far has been, hey, you got a mobile, you can let's try to register you using your mobile when you get a tap, and you'll enter it. And you'll, you know, and you'll work it out, kind of thing. 

Speaker 2  (10:11)
But that is one approach that was one approach, the other one is, you should just surf over your colleagues, desktop, and do yourself another one was get into the Microsoft registration portal and do your stuff. So there are a couple of ways you could enter Yeah, but and then yeah, you were talking about the I call that the credential life cycle engine, the one which is event driven, because we Don 't really want people to be responsible for deleting their own keys. I guess. 

Speaker 2  (10:52)
It will be a well rhythm, you register your key. Your old key should be automatically deleted. You shouldn't have been waiting for a summer. 

Speaker 3  (11:00)
No, right, it's if you lose your key, but not if you let leave it at home, right? So that that's a contextual thing that's not a given. 

Speaker 2  (11:08)
We're going to have people to hold more than one key at the same time, like if you forget your key at home, you come into the office, you get a spare key. Now you have 2 keys registered against you, will that be a violation? I mean, I know Jeremy and all and you have brought up this. 

Speaker 2  (11:23)
Issue, there are no controls around this. And somebody has to come up with controls, I think, enterprise protector somebody, I guess. 

Speaker 3  (11:30)
Yeah, and that's fair, but I would say, right, in that lost a key scenario, if right? What are the they? I guess we have to define what they're going to do? 

Speaker 3  (11:39)
But I would say, right? We haven't said that. It's a given that every time that someone can only have one. 

Speaker 2  (11:47)
Yeah, nobody has made those things. 

Speaker 3  (11:49)
So we can we have to assume that that's right, that that's not a given. And that we have to understand whether the scenario in question involves the need to delete an old key or not. Alright, but you're right that the deletion of is a thing that may happen. 

Speaker 3  (12:06)
But under what scenarios kind of drives, what the flows are going to like, look like. 

Speaker 2  (12:10)
Yeah, yeah, because 

Speaker 3  (12:10)
I guess the hardware provisioning service thing here doesn't. I don't think that's what would be doing. 

Speaker 2  (12:17)
It's you like, if you see I put the color in blue so that everything in blue and green should be nearly automated. It shouldn't be like someone, because even here I put the, if you see M3, this is basically we shouldn't be letting the user decide what he's going to do whether he's going to get a mail-in ubiquity, or is he going to pull it off of the spare board? What if the spare board's over? 

Speaker 2  (12:47)
Yeah, I mean, there are no spare keys at the branch, you know, it has to be smart enough to know. Okay, this guy's a teller, he needs a key right away. Okay, this guy is a back office guy. 

Speaker 2  (13:00)
He doesn't really need a key right away. He can use his windows hollow login and continue working, so we can mail it to him. You know, it has to be, you know, it has to 

Speaker 3  (13:11)
It's smaller that because people have multiple great That just runs into that some people have laptops. Some people have laptops, and they also send into desktops and the branches where I don't see the ability to know that without asking the user. 

Speaker 2  (13:25)
I guess we can. Yeah, I mean I don't know those are those are solutioning stuff, but possibly there may be a flag tell us only shared desktops back off his guy, laptop and something, you know, those are things. Of course, we'll be segmented as we go forward. 

Speaker 2  (13:45)
But I don't think we should be giving the user the decision to decide whether he wants a spare key from the. It should be a role based, it should be science. There should be 

Speaker 3  (13:56)
The synthetic that we don't even know what branches many people are at, because they float, so I think that's a fantast. 

Speaker 2  (14:02)
And that's another, that's another pain point there, some of them just keep on flooding on a daily basis. 

Speaker 3  (14:09)
So I haven't heard anything that would mean that I It just doesn't sound like we can understand that information without asking the user, at least something so we can't programmatically say we're always going to do Exxon user. Y. So like we have to build in flexibility unless someone has defined a way that we can tell that information for sure. 

Speaker 1  (14:32)
Yeah, there's really, there's going to be the standard way, and then Exception, right? Type thing, right, self-service for instance, for example. Oh, while I think of this while I think of this so Ben was able to do some testing. 

Speaker 1  (14:49)
And he is able to sign in with a ubq, to a freshly imaged laptop. 

Speaker 3  (15:00)
Oh, nice, yes, thank you very, very, very helpful. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (15:05)
Yeah, he said it didn't prompt him for windows. Hello for business, but he signed in, so he was going to Analogs and see why it didn't prompt them to set it up, but still, yeah, so that was excellent news. 

Speaker 3  (15:19)
Yeah, yeah, it was really vague in the documentation, so I'm good to know. 

Speaker 2  (15:23)
Yeah, so that has the back office people. What about the tellers? 

Speaker 1  (15:28)
Well, it helps for new, it helps for new employees. It helps, you know, it helps helps for yeah, it helps us get to password less is 

Speaker 3  (15:38)
It doesn't, it's, it doesn't help much with the recovery scenarios, but it does help with the new user on a computer new user in TV situation that makes it easier and less involving of passwords. 

Speaker 2  (15:55)
I remember there was there were some issues like. Are you going to mail the key and the first time access code to the user or 

Speaker 1  (16:07)
We've got flexibility there and 

Speaker 3  (16:10)
It depends on the user's situation when they're starting right? Yeah 

Speaker 2  (16:15)
We get this multiple, I don't know. Okay. It doesn't look right to give too many parts also because, you know, you're like, they say, insecurity are creasing your blast radius, but but yeah, that's a different. 

Speaker 3  (16:28)
But it's funny you mean tonight. 

Speaker 2  (16:30)
I mean, some people are going to come into the office and you know, initialize their keys, some people are going to do it from home, some people may do it from the, you know, from a central location where they, where they come in the first day and for sure, maybe the manager may have to intervene and delegate someone. To the root. 

Speaker 3  (16:54)
It's across the different situations, it's going to just be you're pulling a key from a shared pool, because you're in a role where you deal with where you're in a branch where we don't know where you're going to start. So we couldn't have shifted, something you didn't advance and then the other people will have it pre-registered and shipped to them for like a back office thing, where we know you're burning, and then figure out it' 

Speaker 2  (17:16)
Yeah, I mean, yeah, those are the things that we left to work up, but, yeah, I mean But it's good to know that you can actually use your ubique and register and log in on the first day, but does that. But since you're not getting connected to windows Hillel, does that allow you to get into all the applications, or does that restrict you from getting into certain applications? 

Speaker 1  (17:40)
No, it would still work, but we will have the windows low for business registration. That was just, you know, he did want test. Dad, that was the extent of it, so it's good news, it's not, you know, directly applicable to what we're talking about here, but for the big picture down the road that's important. 

Speaker 1  (17:59)
We Don 't know when we're going to get Et, cetera, you know, interjoined, and And to this, here could put us many, many months ahead of the game to get to password us. 

Speaker 3  (18:11)
Sewawell, see, yeah, and it's relevant, it's relevant to the starting scenarios right? Jonathan, so we are going to go over the starting ubiquity, right? You're a new user in a branch scenarios, so yeah, I mean we'll be right with that. 

Speaker 1  (18:25)
Deployment, yeah, like, if it meant that we didn't have to change The policy it could be really, really helpful from the pilot perspective. Could you could literally just Give them the keys and say here you go. But policy Whatever group policies you have in place around You know, like, when does love business put on like the se force? 

Speaker 1  (18:51)
Whatever the policies look like to enforce the use of the final plea. Right now, we need to make sure, just how do you get started in a branch like you don't, if you didn't, you don't want to turn on the policy, if everybody does never key and is ready to go, but you could certainly have them start using it. And then it's gonna remember that method? 

Speaker 2  (19:12)
Okay, and I put one question, does the person have to be on the td network to actually do this for the first time? 

Speaker 3  (19:20)
Well, that's the right. That's one of the main questions, and right, we've been, we've been talking about these recovery scenarios. If it needs to be accessible on a mobile phone, it has to be on the internet, an application that's available on the internet. 

Speaker 3  (19:36)
So then it'll be a question of how do you secure that? But it'll be an internet facing an application. For for the purpose, the identity verification and And you know, obviously hid is a sad service, and we have to expose ub registration off of the network for that scenario as well. 

Speaker 3  (19:58)
So there's a bunch of stuff here that we need to be accessible need to be accessible from. From outside the TV network 

Speaker 2  (20:05)
Yeah, because if you're a mobile user, you're not going to be connected unless they're going to give us into, you know, something to connect to something. 

Speaker 3  (20:14)
But now the person's lost their way of proving their identity. So even that wouldn't work, because that requires authentication, so you need a I'm You know, I have nothing to the team, right? It starts from. 

Speaker 3  (20:28)
I'm nothing to TD. How do I become something? How do I prove I'm something that's my journey to proving? 

Speaker 3  (20:34)
I'm something so that I can register at a high assurance credential. So 

Speaker 2  (20:41)
Yeah, because I think that there is that decision point where hey are you on TV network or are you outsourced TV and how many holes does TV have to open, which I don't think they're going to let you open. 

Speaker 3  (20:56)
Then, we're, we're, we're out of luck, and that's part of the solution we need to get the approv. 

Speaker 1  (21:02)
For Anthony, I've already figured it out. We already, myself had managed, I've already tested it, we know what's required. 

Speaker 3  (21:12)
That's not that's not exposing an application that allows registration to the internet, that's the sense of part right? 

Speaker 1  (21:17)
No, I like the security registration. Yeah, we figured it out how to do that. You, just you protect it with. 

Speaker 1  (21:24)
With mfa, right? That's the whole network 

Speaker 3  (21:26)
This is after someone's lost. It's This is someone someone's lost it, and they can't sign it into their computer. That's the state. 

Speaker 3  (21:33)
We're talk 

Speaker 1  (21:33)
Yeah, well, we're going to get the task, right? I suppose, this is this is this step? You hit the employee portal, you do idv, you get the tap so that you can hit the registration portal, which is protected by mfa, or 

Speaker 3  (21:46)
Hey, that's one of the things the idv portal employee portal that's the part that needs to be. It's supposed to be internet and lets you start from nothing. Approved your assimilation, that's the opposite. 

Speaker 2  (21:58)
Yeah, but when but what about the news is he able going to be able to use the security registration? The same way, get an mfa, kind of get a Tapp. 

Speaker 3  (22:08)
Well, that's what we're saying is there's 2 flavors, 2 flavors, there's the flavor of user that was already shipped the ubique, and has it already linked with their account and had the pens sent? To their personal email account so that they can access it which is flavor one, and those people should just be able to plug and play, just go The alternative flow is somebody who shows up and is going to a location where, without dedicated Without dedicated. Without a dedicated key, having pre provision to them, and then that person that's the open question about, do they go to the idv portal to do the registration, or do they follow some other flow to get it linked to them, like manager assisted or something that I think? 

Speaker 3  (22:58)
A bath that is a situation where there's basically the self-service I came in without a key, it's about the same as I lost my key. 

Speaker 1  (23:06)
Right now, there are all the they're all the same, I don't have a key, that's what I you know But at the top, right? You can Up with it, it's broken. It's whatever It doesn't doesn't matter. 

Speaker 1  (23:20)
They're all the same. 

Speaker 2  (23:23)
Yeah, because ultimately all this will have to be tracked through some sort of service portal, which I'm thinking is going to be because I think we'll have to are ubiquities, going to be considered an asset and need to be registered in me, managed through ServiceNow through cmd. 

Speaker 3  (23:43)
I hope that would be a nightmare. 

Speaker 2  (23:46)
Because they become, they become assets right in a way, they'll have to have a tag number. You just got 

Speaker 1  (23:53)
So I think 

Speaker 3  (23:55)
Crazy I can't believe this is something we would do. 

Speaker 1  (23:59)
So not as an asset like a laptop. I don't think that, but If we want to, if we want to automate The full life cycle of these devices and I mentioned in the last meeting about, well, how would we go about automotive in a branch? Right, make sure they've always got always got stuck on. 

Speaker 1  (24:23)
And you can only do that if you are tracking all of these devices so they're tracked through serial numbers, right? Now do we go to the extent of tracking serial numbers at branches? So that we know and one has now been activated so that we deprecate one from their stock, that this is the type of stuff we would have to do to make sure that we could keep 3000 branches stocked with spare keys at all times and if we don't, then we're gonna absolutely run into scenarios where they don't have any stock and somebody can't work. 

Speaker 2  (25:02)
Yeah, right. And that was the reasoning why I put this model M3 over. Here we need some smart way of managing what is out there Vs you know, there's the registration, there is the security part of it, but there is also a need to manage it physically as to hey, how many does that branch? 

Speaker 2  (25:20)
Have right now, you know how many more do they need kind of thing, how many are actually activated there? How many are actually dominant? I mean, these are types of reports that people will ask, ultimately. 

Speaker 1  (25:33)
Okay, it's okay. 

Speaker 2  (25:34)
Yes, it's time to go, yeah, time to go for say thank you for training. Thank you back by 

Speaker 4  (25:50)
People are great. It's got to be something more 

Speaker 4  (26:28)
It was the what he's doing. This is what he's doing. Hey money. 

Speaker 4  (26:44)
I do that's connected to his Turkey to be 

Speaker 4  (27:06)
You have to be on the back of the 

Speaker 4  (27:26)
It's changing everything you really yield. When it changes The thing on this 

Speaker 5  (30:16)
You're going to do a good player who plays played a barbecue 

Speaker 4  (31:47)
The key, I think I'm wondering a bit I hold this. Yeah, I mean all day when you put man 

Speaker 4  (37:11)
Sorry, doctor why is it? You're sending it back up? 
