
Speaker 1  (00:02)
Okay, we can. We can 

Speaker 2  (00:07)
And as long as the cer 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
It's from A 

Speaker 2  (00:11)
There's any specific requirements for the certificate 

Speaker 3  (00:15)
No, but just any CA from a or any search from a public CA like digit server of aerosine or Symantec. 

Speaker 4  (00:24)
It's over, sir, right? And not, it doesn't need to be client. Type certain 

Speaker 3  (00:28)
The correct certificate for website identification It's not like it's going to be used for only tls, where you don't need it to be a publicly facing certificate, you know, for tls, all we care about is the separate pieces, one public, one private for for this, it needs to be publicly facing and issued by a CA that is going to be recognizable by all browsers? 

Speaker 2  (00:58)
So I'm not sure to yet, I'm not sure have to check into this. I'm not sure if we have to actually request. The sub domain to be to be created specifically. 

Speaker 2  (01:08)
I don't think so. 

Speaker 4  (01:09)
I think you do because you need to create the CNA right 

Speaker 2  (01:15)
Yeah, oh s***. 

Speaker 3  (01:16)
You know, the seating records are just pointers, they're saying, if it's this redirect to this so it doesn't actually have to be a zone within your within your dns. 

Speaker 5  (01:28)
Daniel said to answer your question, you're going to have to create a sub demand text record has to be created for validation of the certificate. 

Speaker 6  (01:34)
Peso, there you go. Yes, yeah, yeah, yes, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (01:36)
Hang out at prip point eights as part of that. 

Speaker 3  (01:39)
Yeah, okay, and that's part of the CA that that's not part of the proof point requirements. 

Speaker 2  (01:44)
No, no, no II go yeah. 

Speaker 4  (01:47)
Talking josier, the New Haven give us a sub. 

Speaker 6  (01:51)
Yeah, here you go, guys. Here we go there. 

Speaker 2  (01:54)
There you go. Okay? So 

Speaker 1  (01:58)
We're going to go, and it's good to know that we're going to go. And 

Speaker 7  (02:03)
We're going to do this in pad to see exactly how how that's going to work. But okay, so that's good to know that we we need to prepare for that, okay. 

Speaker 2  (02:14)
I'll take care of that. I'll start the process and I'll look at the job 

Speaker 7  (02:18)
Let's see what we need to do. 

Speaker 3  (02:24)
Appreciate the time folks as always. If there are any questions, do you please email me? 

Speaker 2  (02:31)
Absolutely, absolutely, I Don'. 

Speaker 8  (02:32)
Thank you very sorry to hear so much. 

Speaker 3  (02:35)
Thank you, I appreciate that. 

Speaker 9  (02:40)
I will be sending out the meeting minutes and I had the notes and our call for Thursday has moved to Wednesday tomorrow at 9 AM eastern, so we'll talk then okay. Okay, wait, then, thank you. 

Speaker 10  (07:46)
Thank you. 

Speaker 10  (17:52)
I'm 
