
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Unlike some other products that prove point you get me, you get an efd consultant, I will stay with you for as long as you pay for the agreement, or if there's a transition made because of my role, changing or something like that, you could get a different efd consultant. But typically I will be with you for as long as you pay for the service. And so that's where part product and managed service comes in. 

Speaker 1  (00:32)
Any questions with what I presented so far? Okay? So um So race, did you want me to go into really demoing EFD or is it more important to maybe talk about how do we get visibility in EFD and look at certain parts of it? 

Speaker 1  (00:57)
Does anybody have? 

Speaker 2  (00:58)
Thanks tonight I'll pass that question to Shannon or Hey, or somebody the holy, how do you want him to perceive it as this 

Speaker 3  (01:15)
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm just trying to get caught up. I don't necessarily have any specific questions I am still trying to understand some of the different products from proof point, because again, I'm, you know, getting 10 emails all about proofpoint, but different products 

Speaker 1  (01:30)
Yes, yeah, make it overwhel. 

Speaker 3  (01:33)
Yes, I'm just kind of trying to keep things straight, because again, with the teams that I have under me, I have a lot of different things going on. So both when it comes to the demarc, when it comes to the email gateway, when it comes to just various parts of this, so Sam, do you have anything or like any specific questions? I don't even know where to start. 

Speaker 3  (01:55)
So a demo would be great, maybe 

Speaker 1  (02:00)
Yeah, so oh, gosh, okay. 

Speaker 4  (02:01)
Without steering, you in moan agenda, I would say, Shannon, and team is probably more interested in anything that would add value to thread operations, you know, for email, like how could they detect or 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
Or either? 

Speaker 4  (02:19)
Actively or reactively respond to email threats for td. Like is there anything in the dashboard or reporting that would give insights into the team that would be actionable data, not sort of A compliance dashboard, you know, that that that they would be, you know, worrying about governance, that's that' S what my team does. They're more specifically focused on thread operations, any kind of you know, fishing threats, things of that nature. 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
Ok, yesterday 

Speaker 3  (02:52)
Thank you, appreciated, Joel, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (02:55)
Yeah, so Yeah, was that in mind? I think what I'm going to do is Let's go to the canvas for so I'm going to have to build a little bit here. To help you understand what the purpose of the canvas is. 

Speaker 1  (03:15)
So I hope you don't mind me going off on this. It's not a tangent, it just kind of helps fill in some gaps. So within email fraud defense, we have this system icon over at the left now I talked earlier about visibility, but how does the FD get visibility to spoofers? 

Speaker 1  (03:37)
Well, it's destinations that are given us the aggregate ports, but within the tool in order for me to get visibility to the spoofers. I get it, I gotta build sold. Some things, it's easy, it's not hard, so I gotta create a group, but what is the group? 

Speaker 1  (03:56)
Well, the group ISIS really anything you need to focus on in regards to a domain or domains. So if I have some domains, so, really, what we're talking about for email fraud defense as a whole is email authentication, right? Demark, is part of that spf, is part of it. 

Speaker 1  (04:19)
Dkm, is part of it, right? But it really is email authentication as a whole But coming back to this grouping, right here, you already have some groups all domains this is just anything think of all domains as everything that you have claimed in efd through domain management. So we've imported, or we've added, or claimed all of these domains. 

Speaker 1  (04:46)
63 is what we know about as of today. But you create the the group, it's real simple, you got 2 types. You can select from static, which means you're just adding in one or many domains up to you. 

Speaker 1  (05:03)
Dynamic, again, one or many domains but the difference is you have this criteria. As it's is The Domain type sending nonsensing, well, what policy is it at reject? Are you looking for P equals none so domains that are monitoring mode are you looking for domains that have no record, which means you don't have visibility to the spoofers, important to create a demoral record and then invalid record again. 

Speaker 1  (05:36)
We don't have visibility or full visibility because the demarc record has a problem and so it needs to be fixed. So you create these groups Once the groups are created Then, you'd come over here to this third item which is an interactive canvas. Now this is where you kind of follow a process So the way to look at it now you can see here, I created my canvas based upon a group of all domains I have another canvas that I created based upon sending domains that domain type. 

Speaker 1  (06:18)
But if I click on a view Now efd is presenting the data we've received from destinations. So When you go into the canvas, think of it this way. My domains is the 1000 foot viewer. 

Speaker 1  (06:41)
It gives you All the domains you've collected. You've grouped so sending domains all of those are listed here, but It gives you information about those domains from a demark S PF and a dm perspective. So the way demarc works is it's all about alignment. 

Speaker 1  (07:06)
Now it still wants to know if spf. If the result is a pass, it still wants to know if the dkim result is a pass. But what demark does, in addition to having that information is to is concerned with alignment. 

Speaker 1  (07:24)
So, did the male from domain? So The Domain portion of the envelope sender did it align with the header from If we're talking D Kim Then, with dkm, there's a there's a signature that's applied to a message. And within that signature, there's AAD equals value, and that value is a domain that the signer is taking responsibility for Hey, Tams got stopped Eva, so 

Speaker 4  (08:02)
So so this is all kind of just compliance stuff. I mean In in a Gary, the tool that we have today, right that we're, we would be likely to transition from, they have the support for RD A-and-R UF does EFD have RUS capability. 

Speaker 1  (08:22)
Yeah, it's provided via the demarc racker to republish it RUA and there's an RUF and they both would have a male 2. 

Speaker 4  (08:35)
With a mail box correct, and so in that RUF you can receive pieces or parts of the emails that failed demark. Yeah, we're going to see stuff like that. 

Speaker 1  (08:47)
So that's going to show great question. Thank you. So that information is actually going to appear under Messenger, but keep in mind Destinations Don 't have to provide a demarc failure report, it' S optional. 

Speaker 4  (09:03)
I am on your side, yeah, it's 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
The required is not to tell that for the greater yeah, that's really for all the people you're helping them keep track of what we're talking about. But his message of your, which is part of the search tools IP viewer, is another search tool. This gives you more granular view. 

Speaker 1  (09:24)
Then what interacts, a canvas will give you So the search tools can be launched. From here and so you have like I said, the 1000 foot view of each domain, how it's performing messages that have been sent that are permitted messages that have been sent not permitted. And I don't have it added. 

Speaker 1  (09:51)
But messages from unknown centers An unknown sander ISIS is really a sander that we Don 't have much information about in order to create a profile. So as I moved down here, it's kind of a good segue into discovered centers, well, these have been im. 

Speaker 4  (10:11)
Fc did Rus' email like, is there an example of what we would see in an ruf email? Do you have 

Speaker 1  (10:17)
We'll see let me come back over here. Typically, there is, but not always depends on The Domain I choose. 

Speaker 4  (10:24)
So I guess some kids like, I don't know if you have like some like a sandbox that has some of this stuff if we don't have it. 

Speaker 1  (10:32)
No, I don't have anything. Why is that not? And I do something wrong, eating.com. 

Speaker 1  (10:42)
Ah, sometimes this needs to 

Speaker 4  (10:49)
Yeah, I mean, you know, Shannon and Dave probably have their own use cases that they'll develop, right. But from my perspective, I could see where the RUF data could potentially be of value if it were developed, and also if we had any of the other Like sudden spikes in deborn, failures Like, we've been able to investigate 

Speaker 3  (11:12)
You know, there's information that we can get on. Yeah, like like Joel said the stuff that's failing, that's the stuff that I mentioned again the 1000th of the view is great, but like that doesn't do my team any good necessarily, that's again, a more of a Joel thing. 

Speaker 4  (11:26)
Yeah, I get the boring compliance stuff unfortunately. 

Speaker 1  (11:31)
So here's the thing that Dean mark does. Whenever they send a demarc, failure report usually will have urls in it. Sometimes these urls could be bad. 

Speaker 1  (11:43)
So if we detect that the Ural is bad You'll see it here under your elbows. Now I don't see any for this, and I probably picked a bath. But this is where it would show them, and then if I don't know if you guys are using takedown and um U. 

Speaker 1  (12:01)
We're not, but if you are using takedown, you could submit that. And then I am not We can do the block to prevent Now normally tap is going to catch a lot of this right? Because that's what tap does is look at the urls. 

Speaker 1  (12:16)
So when it comes into your environment, if pod is the perimeter gateway, it's going to detect it. You know, and they're just going to block it, but we do get we do have some integration here with takedown, where if there is a suspicious url of course you want to vet it, but basically you could do a takedown. If you have that tool and again, I don't know if you do or don't But. 

Speaker 1  (12:42)
That 

Speaker 3  (12:42)
A part of the proof point A group that we may or may not be getting is that we were saying 

Speaker 1  (12:48)
Well, it depends, you've probably purchased a bundle. It'll be my guess. And if you did purchase a bundle, there are certain packages that you can. 

Speaker 1  (12:57)
You She used to have been that bundle. Takedown could be 1 over 1 of them. But it may not if you chose not to select it, your account manager your se. 

Speaker 1  (13:07)
I don't see them on the phone today ear. 

Speaker 3  (13:11)
I can answer that, oh I can. And we have. We have 25. 

Speaker 3  (13:17)
We can do that 25 times on a monthly basis. 

Speaker 1  (13:21)
Awesome, so you do so. Yeah, so this is one thing that you can see a possible threat. And then the other places that you could use So email fraud defense is really to help you prepare For enforcement, you guys are at enforcement for many, if not majority of your domains. 

Speaker 1  (13:47)
So what I'm going to switch gears here, Joe, with Shannon, the ears, put feedback, I'm going to switch over to something that we haven't really discussed. So if you want, mic 

Speaker 2  (14:00)
Where you go, what was wrong with this message? By the way, I'm just curious. 

Speaker 1  (14:05)
Oh, this actually is a complaint. It's not a demarked forensic samples. We get these samples from two different sources, of course, from the destination, if it's a demarc failure, but we also get it from our other product. 

Speaker 1  (14:28)
And so cloud mark, if It works with Google Yahoo. These email providers is what cloud mark that our product Work with so for example, if they have complaints, cloud markets have access to that, and all that we're doing is we're calling these complaints in, because again, the tool is really meant to help you get to enforcement for a domain demarc force. So one of the questions you have to ask yourself as you're moving, or as you're going through that discovery process is, is this a center I care about or not well, if we see a url here and it looks suspicious, more likely that's a center that we're questioning, but we don't want to mark them as permitted. 

Speaker 1  (15:20)
Permit means that we're going to spend the time to authorize them so that male can pass the femar, checks via spf and D count. So the urls of this context is more about is this the center that we want to markets permitted? 

Speaker 4  (15:42)
Can we take a step back on this one? So how does how does proof point perceive a complaint? And how do these? 

Speaker 4  (15:49)
How do these emails reach proof point, if they're not demarked related to it? 

Speaker 1  (15:52)
Well, if the ESP is using our cloud mark, then they'll have that complaint, and so what we've done with the FD, not me, but the engineering team, they pull that information in to enhance the Messenger or to help us determine if a sender can be permitted should be permitted or not. 

Speaker 4  (16:16)
So a customer of proof plate is receiving this email, and they have reported it to proof plate denial control. 

Speaker 1  (16:24)
The destination and the recipient could be Google, it could be Yahoo okay, it typically is going to be someone that has a that has been given a free mailbox, right? Which Google and Yahoo, both do. There's others, but our cloud mark It is polling those complaints now I'm not a cloud mark. 

Speaker 1  (16:49)
Person, I can't tell you all about that. But what I can say is from the efd side, we're pulling that those complaints, if we see that it's from one of your domains that's claimed we will pull that in as part of the theater. The best is for your outbreak. 

Speaker 4  (17:07)
It's a proofpoint Partners with companies like cloud mark to get this data, but how does cloud mark get the data? 

Speaker 1  (17:14)
Sloubach is trick point. We purchase some, but for 5 years ago. 

Speaker 4  (17:19)
So how Brexit this goes back to how does proof one get to stay within 

Speaker 1  (17:24)
Well, again, I'm not a cloud mark expert, but cloud mark is integrated with gml. And I don't know who all the esps are the disintegrated with, but we pull that data. So cloud mark is somehow integrated in with Gmail and Google. 

Speaker 1  (17:48)
Or arrest, same thing or yaver. And so I don't know what all they would be, but the way it works is if I'm a recipient in Gmail And I receive an email, and I mark it a Spam, or in other words, I complain that's a complaint. If I complain about it, then the cloud mark would have access to that data. 

Speaker 4  (18:15)
Okay, so use your own Gmail. Complaints about an email that email is then ingested by cloud mark to some degree. 

Speaker 1  (18:23)
That's right. 

Speaker 4  (18:24)
The user has to complain about the email before proof point sees that data is that activate that 

Speaker 1  (18:29)
That's right. Yes, yeah, so if it's, if it's benign email or a good email, you know, so so those are complaints, that's why the raw format here at the right is different than what you would see for AD mark. For the source time, so source tie complaint, source tie demarkini. 

Speaker 1  (18:51)
Okay, and so this format will be slightly different. 

Speaker 2  (18:56)
Any chance you have a sample of the other one? 

Speaker 1  (18:59)
Absorbed that up. Let's see if we can find one here. Yeah, so here's an example of abuse. 

Speaker 1  (19:16)
So This right here, since it says of use would also come from cloud martyr, and then that way, again it goes back to whether we want to permit the center or not. Shall we think that there's something suspicious about this? And there's a lot of urrals in that one. 

Speaker 1  (19:40)
So That's part of it I was trying to find a demark for the source to be eat. Well, you guys are apt. You're at rejack, so we're only gonna be showing those that are, you're not going to see many demarc failures. 

Speaker 1  (20:02)
Because you're already at rejacked, so the majority of that's going to be passing. Yeah, I'm not seeing it, they don't. I don't have A filter button here where I can say complaint or demarc. 

Speaker 1  (20:15)
And it's not giving up to me if I hit these Yeah, it's obvious and that goes into complaint. That's all we're seeing is complaint of use. So there's nothing here for dimar. 

Speaker 1  (20:30)
If you have another domain, I can try and put that in If you want, you can track TV scarities. TV security, one word okay. Let's see what we get from that assess. 

Speaker 1  (20:55)
So the complaint is still good information. I mean, yeah, you're rejecting everything, but if you're seeing a lot of complaints and these subjects are all similar. Then, so that would mean something to the group that is responsible for sending these emails, possibly, so if they are legitimate. 

Speaker 1  (21:18)
And if the debt and the recipient is complaining about it, well, that could, in fact, your deliverability. For that marketing message, or whatever it may be. That's something that that group We'd want to know about that so they can check it and say, hey, you know, we don't want to get on Google's dotty list. 

Speaker 1  (21:40)
You know, if we have some type of hi, I'm hi. If we're, they'd have to do more digging into it to understand and make really why they complained a feedback loop is what I would recommend subscribing to Yahoo and Google feedback loops very helpful. I mean I know it adds more work for an administrator but when you're seeing something like this, you can go to the mailbox where the feedback is going and you can look at those emails, because they are complaints, typically. 

Speaker 1  (22:15)
And so you might be able to identify a pattern, then you got enough information to go back to the group responsible for that vendor sending it and you can say, hey, this is what we're seeing, it's being complained, you might need to take some action so that you don't get on somebody's naughty lids, of course, you don't want to use postmaster tools, things like that to find out hey. Are we trending into the bad area or not? I haven't looked at the postmaster tools for Martz, so I don't know exactly what they show you. 

Speaker 1  (22:54)
When I was an administrator feedback loops were awesome because we They were getting blacklisted. About every 3 months we had a relay, and we kept getting blacklist, and that's more in what you guys want to know. But feedback loops are helpful, so I'm saying 

Speaker 2  (23:10)
But it would be helpful to know how we get a complaint, because 

Speaker 1  (23:15)
It could be. 

Speaker 2  (23:16)
You know, somebody adding to their marketing at stamp fall, you know, right? 

Speaker 1  (23:22)
Yeah, yeah, it's a complaint ISIS very In general, right, they could have marked a Spam, they thought it was Spam. They didn't want it, so they complain about it. All right, through the feature that Google or Yahoo or whoever the destination is. 

Speaker 1  (23:41)
Is that recipient just complains about it, so we listen to just a complaint. Staking more general because we don't know why they complained about it. We just know it was a complaint. 

Speaker 2  (23:56)
It's a retempt day here Shannon, so I need to jump to another club, but you're in good hands, you're Shannon with Joel and jet, and you know, any is also here, but just email me if there's anything that's needed in the NFL, but you have to just I don't just, I know what you want us to do next, alright? 

Speaker 3  (24:16)
Thank you so much, vickeye I'm 

Speaker 1  (24:22)
So hopefully, that's a little helpful there as far as threats again, we're in the context of the demarc world, right? However, something that may be more useful to you. There are going to be reports, so since you're at reject. 

Speaker 1  (24:40)
If I come into reports, I can create a report and we 'Ve already got TV and subdomains last 30 days, I' M just going to use this. The purpose of the reports is to help you determine mainly how demarc is working for you. So if you're a permitted sender, you expect to see high however For Denmark block ray, you might see some spikes here. 

Speaker 1  (25:07)
Well, the spikes could be indicated that you're under attack. Right, so we see a spike on and I don't know the count or anything right here. 47%, 68 messages well, as administrator that wasn't really Slack. 

Speaker 1  (25:27)
This for me, yes, it is higher the rest of them, but the volume isn't really that high. But if I came in here and I looked, and it was in the thousands or hundreds, okay, that got my attention, what's going on and so you can go back and use the IP viewer. With its search criteria to match this, so we're looking at not permitted undetermined senders. 

Speaker 1  (25:51)
You can specify that you can specify the date range. And then with that information, you should be able to narrow down for that day. You want to do the date range for that day. 

Speaker 1  (26:03)
But then you go in to say, okay, who is the highest sender? Now, purple indicates. Yes, they are not, they are undetermined, not permitted, but this indicates it was delivered. 

Speaker 1  (26:16)
It was not blocked. The green is shown that it was block. And so as administrator I can look at that and go okay, something's up to again. 

Speaker 1  (26:25)
This is a bad example 68 messages, but if it's in the hundreds or a 1000 make me And then girl Cape, there's something going on, I need to get more information about it, so I would take this information here go to the IQ here or do some searches, try to try to pair this. These data points up, so I can see who that sender is. And then go from there. 

Speaker 1  (26:50)
Well, is there a demarked failure report okay? A is an inbound, or is an outbound, because if it's inbound, maybe I have something in smart search, I could use the efd data that I have go to smart search, find that and then figure out, okay. And now I know more about this, and so either it's going to be benign or You know, meaning that it's just some group that that's To generate more traffic than usual, or you may determine based upon the smart search or other information. 

Speaker 1  (27:24)
That hey, this could be a bad guy up to no gut. We want to make sure the spells get you blocked. So 

Speaker 4  (27:33)
So if you start curiosity Tim, I understand from our previous conversation that this does not or doesn't currently have any notification capabilities like it, we can't set up reports and then set thresholds for things and then be notified when something exceeds its novel. 

Speaker 1  (27:50)
Oh, no, the suddenly or 

Speaker 4  (27:53)
It's not really a strength tool in that regard, then so my question is does it or has anyone been able to integrate this into something that can provide that flexibility is there an API that can be accessed? Has this been a design that some other customer has taken and implemented on their own, because from a threat the defense operations perspective and even my perspective I can't really be tied to a dashboard. I need to be, you know, able to multifunction and multi-task. 

Speaker 4  (28:32)
And that sort of Dylan, check on reports periodically, is what I'm saying, I need. I need to be flexible in regards to dry. How can we get there? 

Speaker 1  (28:43)
Well, you have a lurch. So these alerts are looking at block Permitted an email. So you can subscribe to this alert, and then if it And if you don't get into it, let's edit that Psychiatric judge, just like any any alert, right? 

Speaker 1  (29:04)
You gotta figure out. Well, what's the threshold? I need to be here. 

Speaker 1  (29:07)
Well, this is looking in the minimum of the minute. The 25 massages you might not, you might look at it go well, wait a second when we've seen stuff in the past. They generated around what up. 

Speaker 1  (29:20)
Okay, well, we'll put this at 1:00. You know, so use your experience right here. But this is how you can see Information related to the report not directly from the report. 

Speaker 1  (29:33)
But that The court is looking at undeterred or well. The top one is looking at permitted. Italy. 

Speaker 1  (29:42)
And there's A 

Speaker 4  (29:43)
Can we become notifying when these alerts and triggering rights? 

Speaker 1  (29:46)
Oh, you'll get if when you subscribe. You're subscribing the email that you use when you When you set up access management to get access to efd, it's going to use that email address. 

Speaker 4  (30:02)
So there is some sort of email 

Speaker 1  (30:05)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so this is that. And then Potential threats is anatomous, so we're talking about urls that could be suspicious. Well, this is another one that you can subscribe to to get an email for 

Speaker 4  (30:20)
Okay alright. So so at the bottom left, there looks like there's a number of things that we can configure to be subscribed to right, and that will notify us are those. A configurable beyond like a like a specific like it looks like I assume that we can tailor the threshold, but does it allow custom reports or cuts? 

Speaker 1  (30:46)
Justin alerts, now this is a can. I mean, I'll just say 

Speaker 4  (30:54)
It's already there, and we can just tune the threshol. 

Speaker 1  (30:57)
Right? Right. Now I don't know if you guys want to do this, but In previous meetings, I talked about the APIs. 

Speaker 1  (31:06)
I've got a number of customers that I want to use Intuit as the example And totter, it doesn, 't, it's They're more concerned about Email being blocked. Now, that's not necessarily a threat that you guys are looking at. But it is an example of them taking the APIs pulling data in and they create their own alerts, they got that expertise. 

Speaker 1  (31:36)
With splonk, where they just create their own works, so they don't subscribe to anything here, they just go to the API, and they pull it in, they have someone whose masterful with that, and they create the alert, and that's how they are alerted. But. There Their usage is more about If we permitted the sander, and we start seeing Sanders that are failing, that's something we want to know about. 

Speaker 1  (32:03)
If we have nonsense domains and They should have no centers. So if we start seeing traffic, what we want to know. They've done those things now from a purely threat. 

Speaker 1  (32:19)
Perspective, I think the biggest Bang for your buck to be honest is going to be supplier risk for supplier ballot. 

Speaker 4  (32:32)
Grow asleep, for example, the approach I would take with that is I say that we have an inventory of domains or some domains etc, that we're expecting email to come from, and if and if something new weren't to start sending email that we're not aware of we would want to be notified so I wouldn't be listing the things I'm monitoring explicitly, but I would be saying, here's my list unknown. You know, some debates, debates, anything outside of that I should do not know that. Is that A? 

Speaker 4  (33:10)
Is that something that proposed can do 

Speaker 1  (33:13)
It's not something we can do. We can give you the APIs, we can say, this is the data you'd have to consume it beyond that. Does that make sense? 

Speaker 1  (33:22)
What I'm showing here is these are what's available traffic anomalies, you know? The traffic of nonsense, we already talked about blocked potential threats to urls, those are the things that we can alert you to from this tool. When we start talking about these other tools this one, the supplier risks Explorer, the supplier risk Explorer has given you It's given you data. 

Speaker 1  (33:54)
About a center. Who could be passing the Em? On? 

Speaker 1  (33:59)
But nevertheless, they are a threat to your recipient. So if you don't mind, I'm going to switch over and talk to this. Since the since you guys said that, you're more concerned with, well, how can this help us determine threats? 

Speaker 4  (34:15)
Well friends can also be to my point, if something that we're not aware of is now starting to send email from one of our debates. So so today my question and I guess just confirm that I got it right that if unless we specify the debates, if we're willing to monitor there's no 

Speaker 1  (34:37)
Alerting, that would happen to senator. 

Speaker 4  (34:39)
Say that, you know, if we have the these, I don't know. 60 some odd debates, if a new sub debate in one of those starts sending emails, there's no way for us to kind of alert A With what's available in the product today? 

Speaker 1  (34:57)
Yeah, there's not alert that would do that. Could you do it? I'm yeah, it's not guilty then, but it's being the API, but it would be this is what you'd be monitoring. 

Speaker 1  (35:12)
All right, discovered standards. 

Speaker 4  (35:14)
Well, we're not really looking for perfect. No, this would be 

Speaker 1  (35:18)
A. If 

Speaker 4  (35:19)
I mean, even if TV were sending what I'm saying is even if TV were sending It's owned email, but from a new sub to bank right? That has not ever before sent email. And suddenly today it's sent an email like we would want to know about that. 

Speaker 1  (35:37)
As long as the claim And you have those alerts set up, yeah, you get information back. So the key is The CFD know about it, so it was a claim. So if it's clay And then I got my lurch set up then yeah, you shouldn't receive those alerts for In this case, I am ah A traffic anomalies, if it's blocked permitted mail. 

Speaker 1  (36:05)
Traffic and nonsense. 

Speaker 4  (36:07)
Alright. So II think I understand you, can you can go into your deck stocking, okay? 

Speaker 1  (36:15)
So Supplier risks Explorer is isn'. Oh, wait a second, why do we have net? Oh, let's go altomas, we don't have anything. 

Speaker 1  (36:28)
Is your mx reactor not currently pointing to proof point? Your exchange, your index record is appointed your appointment not yet. 

Speaker 4  (36:45)
We're not corrections for anything other than attest to date testifying. 

Speaker 3  (36:48)
We can we have the UAT doing right but nothing anymore, right? 

Speaker 1  (36:57)
Okay, so I can't really explain. I can't demo this. I can explain So the purpose of supply risk for is this is really working with tap To give the visibility to inbound senders again, they could be passing demarc. 

Speaker 1  (37:21)
Here, let me begin Let me switch over to 

Speaker 1  (37:36)
I Don'. The data is not really very 

Speaker 1  (37:57)
Kayleigh. So the purpose of this tool is to give you visibility to domains that could pose a threat to your recipients. So what we do is we look at these domains we're looking at inbound data. 

Speaker 1  (38:13)
Passing through your gateway pod. As that data passes through the gateway, we have the language learning model that's looking at that inbound data. It's looking for anything that has financial type of information. 

Speaker 1  (38:31)
It's a purchase order. Things like that. If it detects. 

Speaker 1  (38:39)
Then We're going to we're going to score So a very high risk is typically anything that's last 7 days. As the email ages, you know, 14 days, 30 days, that risk is going to lower over time, because we're making the assumption that you are aware of it, you've already addressed it. But we will show it as being very high risk, and what we're looking for is well, are they fishing? 

Speaker 1  (39:12)
Well, there's 21. And now this would indicate it passed through your gateway. This is the spread down below this is across all points of you know, 1000 + 3 point destiners. 

Speaker 1  (39:28)
So docusegi. Dot ned is a risk to an organization. Because there is some breach. 

Speaker 1  (39:38)
On their end. And that they have a drug Now, if I want to drill down on that, if I'm a tap Avenue, and I'll be able to drill, if I'm not a tap Admin, this shouldn't be lit up should be like this. Well, that's 0, but it's not going to be in blue. 

Speaker 1  (39:56)
So I can click on this Now I'm going to list the fishing threat And again, if I'm a tap administ Then, I can throw into this 4 to learn more about what type of fishing threat is this So the purpose of this tool in most cases Well, in every case I've seen so far. The tap has protected the organization What's more important is if you are using docusign, this is evidence that They're passing on something and yeah, fruit point protected. You today, wonderful good for proof point. 

Speaker 1  (40:45)
But I might want to go back to some representative docusign and say, look, dude. We've had X number The fishing comes from your organization. Are you aware of this? 

Speaker 1  (40:58)
Or do you know what type of fishing it is now? I'm not a tap expert. But you could get the information here about, well, what is the type of attack? 

Speaker 1  (41:09)
And then you could pass it on to the donkey, Sin 2 say, look, we're Partners. You know, this is something we want you to address. Yeah, we we taught it We protected our usernames. 

Speaker 1  (41:25)
The bad guys always changed their captives, and so So maybe they can modify this so Through the point of point, you won't catch it the next time. I hope we do you know, we have a good protest. I feel We're not perfect. 

Speaker 1  (41:40)
Nobody is And so I would want to go back to them to say, hey, are you aware of this? We saw this, and that's number of days. So I'm Come back over here. 

Speaker 1  (41:57)
So when you say frets, this is what comes to mind for me. What can EFD do? Other than what we talked about earlier. 

Speaker 1  (42:08)
To try and determine who is the biggest threat to our organization. Now there is, and you may already have it on you, are you yeah, on you. Do you guys use supply threat? 

Speaker 1  (42:28)
It's called st. Ep. Supplier threat protection, yeah, we will be yeah. 

Speaker 1  (42:35)
Okay? So This is great, but this is just monitoring. It has no key. 

Speaker 1  (42:43)
I mean, supplier thread protection SDP UQ We'll show you pretty much the same thing. That gives you more details, because He isn't taped or part of tap. It is a better crop, that's all I'm saying if you have it, then Today you're not going to be in here as much, but I'm, but this has proven to be very helpful. 

Speaker 1  (43:13)
And multiple instances, I'm not going to give you the name of the customer, but back in 2022. We had a customer. There was No one knew about it's such a very, very well-known customer. 

Speaker 1  (43:32)
Um, U did you see him on TV or the advertising on TV constantly? Anyone who's They were listed here. And we started digging into it, it wasn't me. 

Speaker 1  (43:45)
It was a sales engineer that used to be on the threats to make it me He come across here, and he started drilling down on it, and what ended up happening was that organization, it was discovered that they had some software that had downloaded on their edge surprise. So they are used to Microsoft, and it was one of the, and it was an edge server on that machine that software had. Have been installed, and it was sending out all these other organizations. 

Speaker 1  (44:24)
It was pretty broad And so anyway. If you're talking threats, then this or sp would be better. I would recommend to maybe take a more advantage of STP. 

Speaker 1  (44:41)
Again. I'm not an STP expert. I would recommend that you reach out to your count manager and say, hey. 

Speaker 1  (44:48)
Can we have a demo on st TP? You know, you've purchased, get your money's worth of So anyway. But this is what comes to mind the most now, again, I have a lot of organizations that say Tim, I am, I Um, um, we have other people. 

Speaker 1  (45:11)
We don't want to give them access to efd, you know how else can we give them this information? Well, there's an API for this. So so I'm going to come over here, we'll get out of that, and then I'm going to give you the link hasted in and then you guys are welcome to To go out and learn more about it. 

Speaker 1  (45:34)
This is our main API site, so I'm going to copy this I'll paste this into the chat. 

Speaker 3  (45:45)
I'm sorry we don't have access to the chat. They've turned it off to external Partners, so they'll have to be sent via email. 

Speaker 1  (45:55)
That's not a proof point saying, I can do this if anybody else that's someone else. 

Speaker 3  (46:00)
Yeah, I know it's a td thing or 

Speaker 1  (46:05)
I can put it in an email so I Don But anyway, this is where you come and you have all these different endpoints for efd data, ap access, this is more for getting information like IP viewer, if you wanted to pull that information into your SIM, you could do that, and so I just wanted to make you aware of it. But Supply chain is Is where you've accounted for the API for supply risk Explorer. And he would come down here, and this will get all that data. 

Speaker 1  (46:48)
And then you can consume it, do something with it, so at least wanted to point you in that direction. There But that's really, I can't think of anything else. Reports is where you could see, you know, where does going on? 

Speaker 1  (47:06)
That could indicate there's a threat. The your year urls within messages covered that I'm trying to think if there's anything that I missed, I don't think so. But that's kind of what efd is meant to do is really? 

Speaker 1  (47:28)
It's more about email authentication, and determining, hey, do I want to Mark the center is a permitted center, so I can authorize that center's traffic. That's really what it mainly is meant to do as well as the host's services. And I didn't get into this because it's not, we were looking more at threats. 

Speaker 1  (47:51)
But. Pulse of services you can get around the 10D and S query limit. I'm sure Joe, or somebody probably may be already communicated this out to the rest of the group or a jet, I don't know, but But we're really a monitoring tool, except when you use these tools right here, spf and dkm, then we're partly into your mail flow. 

Speaker 1  (48:16)
So The other thing that's more threat. It's looking like domains. Almost forgot about that. 

Speaker 1  (48:27)
Let me get over to my portal and get out of Costco. 

Speaker 1  (48:46)
So Demarc does a great job of protecting your organization. From a from explicit, when they use explicitly use The Domain, the correct spelling But what bad actors will do is they change their tactics. And they'll start using a look alike. 

Speaker 1  (49:09)
So if you have other domains that are more characters than just td, they could use them. If those are saying, you know, if those are brands, then they can use them. So demark doesn't protect you from a lookalike domain attack. 

Speaker 1  (49:31)
So this is meant to give you visibility to look alike domains. In order to before you get the detection, which is here, you first have to configure it. Which is here and down at the bottom, right? 

Speaker 1  (49:48)
So you and the way that it works is you have to take A second level domain, in this case, for me, it's zizzer.net, I have to add that seed, and then we're, and then EFD is going to start crawling the internet looking for lookalikes. I'm going to skip the ignore rules these you don't want to create any ignore rules until you've had a chance to review detections, so there's nothing to really talk about here. Corporate name servers, I will talk about that real quick. 

Speaker 1  (50:25)
You only want to add a corporate name server, and this is for me playing around. These shouldn't be in here. Corporate name servers. 

Speaker 1  (50:38)
Here's what you want to add, meaning, it's a name server. You have complete control over However, if you're using cloud flare, if you're using go daddy, you would not want to add those name servers here. So that would not be done Because by adnam here, as we evaluate the lookalikes, if we see that the name servers here, then we may not show that look alike as being a detection. 

Speaker 1  (51:11)
Because we'll think it might be yours. So Don't add. It's okay to add corporate name servers that you directly control, but any other name servers you would not want to add here. 

Speaker 1  (51:26)
You can add logos. That what I'm going to do is I'm going to get out of this real quick I'm going to come over here to the lookalike domains. Because these could be threats. 

Speaker 1  (51:41)
But maybe not the threat you normally think of four example I can have a look alike right here. That lookalike may have A copycat website. Maybe it's got a drive by people go out and it downloads up to the local workstation. 

Speaker 1  (52:02)
Well, I'd want to get that site brought down and again, takedown can help you with that. So local likes is another thing that does fall into possible threats. And if you click on these, we have this information web presence. 

Speaker 1  (52:24)
So again, if there is a web presence, we'll get a screenshot, you can click on that. See it this and doesn't have it, it's a bad example. We'll give you The WHO is about to look alike. 

Speaker 1  (52:37)
More dns information, and then the it addresses that we're seeing. We even check to see if there's NASA cell certificate. But the idea is, it gives you information to help you Determined, determined, could this look alike be threatening? 

Speaker 1  (52:57)
Your organization is going to And then if they are threatening, then we need to take steps, take down to take down services that you're using. It could be helpful and this information here can be used as possible evidence Like it's a sufficient attack. First, as opposed to A Website. 

Speaker 1  (53:23)
So this is another thing that eft has that could help with determining threats. We're at the end of our time. I believe so, if anybody has any follow-up questions. 

Speaker 1  (53:40)
Feel free to email me. That's not a big deal. I will get back to you as soon as I'm able to. 

Speaker 1  (53:47)
Sorry, we don't have time. 
