
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Ashley key track of base, so we can get a base. I aint had people providing a place like if you have a store for you and again, I think we have to go back to them and we don't even though we don't want to where we have little Springs. And people, we have all the stories that we want to work with and have you need that. 

Speaker 2  (00:20)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (00:20)
Yeah, otherwise, this is going to go crazy. 

Speaker 2  (00:23)
Yeah, yeah, it needs to get organized. IA 100% agree Howard, like sprint sprints, could give a given. Some some organization to all this 

Speaker 3  (00:35)
Have you assigned them to anyone? 

Speaker 2  (00:38)
No, but that, that's the thing like this. This particular In Gs D And and I think it's sweeter, anyway, they don't have it, they're like This team like gsd, that They're new to jjira. And yeah, they just, they don't have it in place yet. 

Speaker 3  (01:01)
I put in the ticket I just put somebody's name there, whoever it's going to do it. 

Speaker 2  (01:04)
Oh, yeah, no, there's there's yeah, we got assignments. Right? We got assignment 

Speaker 3  (01:08)
Yeah, but then, as that then has, but let's say, and if that's the current guide, then I'll follow-up with him. 

Speaker 2  (01:13)
Yeah, that, that. But that yeah, that's for yeah, so there was an update. On that. 

Speaker 1  (01:20)
I saw 

Speaker 2  (01:22)
I saw that update, I think today or the other day, and so there's an intake for this right for cyberark. Yeah, so this is the request, okay. And yeah. 

Speaker 3  (01:37)
At least I wait because we just went through the same thing with an email. 

Speaker 2  (01:42)
Yeah 

Speaker 3  (01:43)
It's a bit different, they're training process, and it's kind of like loose like it will. Nobody's probably looking at that request. 

Speaker 2  (01:52)
For nti or 

Speaker 3  (01:54)
Or for nti, I for nti, AI okay so that they should create a worksheet and send back to a saint male in this case, but to leader with me. 

Speaker 1  (02:03)
It's remains to the risk cash, yeah, Ellen FIS going to help we get a person in our team, also act as APM Ali, what I'm going to do, they, that's okay with you are going to get Ali to work with you right that one0 and see if she can actually go through all each of these stories with you, right all right go, maybe she can go through all these different items and she can actually go and start following app with every person that is assigned to it and maybe be obtaining the ticket right, okay good and maybe we can test in a little bit of a target like hey, we have, I don't know X amount of items open and we want to close 20% a week or 30% something like that right. 

Speaker 1  (02:47)
But I would like to see this item moving somewhere, right if that's possible. Let me talk to you, Alice can actually schedule and help you out with this right? And I'm And in that way we can actually keep Keep holding that traction. 

Speaker 1  (03:05)
Yeah, exactly. A few other things that I wanted to ask, I know, we have that conversation today with Chad, and one of the guys from the csp team, one of the situations that we've run in today is that What is it? You know how the CSP processing was actually replaced with a scale? 

Speaker 1  (03:29)
Right? And so that means then in there, we shouldn't have people pushing back saying, hey, you need csp approval, but that's not what we're experiencing today, right? We're actually going to look into this, but maybe we're going to need your help trying to get some of these things moving. 

Speaker 1  (03:48)
Because we're being asked to provide something that is no longer require 

Speaker 3  (03:53)
Oh, what was the asking for SB? B? 

Speaker 1  (03:57)
No, for example, the guys from the whoever does the registration, they basically push back saying, hey, the ecsp approval for them. Us. Like what 

Speaker 3  (04:10)
He okay, got 

Speaker 4  (04:12)
I just cleared it out with Harry's manager Harry's just new. I don't think he knows at all. So they're not going to ask for csp for deaf, and I reach to scale team. 

Speaker 4  (04:23)
They don't require deaf. There is no intake for deaf, the only intake from skill perspective, it's only for patent prod, so we should not have any issues with Dav. Going from part and broad, we will for sure need to have csp approved. 

Speaker 1  (04:44)
So if you assign somebody else to the ticket, because the key is on the kitchen right now, that's my understanding. 

Speaker 4  (04:51)
Yeah, so They are extremely busy teams, so I'm trying to talk to them so I cleared out that that we don't require csp for the F but I will ask them to see if they can assign someone else. 

Speaker 1  (05:06)
Okay, perfect, thank you. 

Speaker 4  (05:08)
Thank you, however. 

Speaker 1  (05:12)
The other thing is, the other thing is that we had conversations. This week was the container so that actually went well. If you asked me That was fine. 

Speaker 1  (05:27)
The possessed service in him and Peter okay, so the only thing that I had concerned was the the when you call it destination, whatever price, the whatever the kind of charges to build servers, right? I booked a couple of calls, yeah, one for today, the person declined, I book another one for tomorrow, and the person which I'll say and that the person he was going to be away when I called the whole day tomorrow, so I need to move that again to Monday, hopefully, that's going to be the last. 

Speaker 3  (05:59)
The lies wouldn't be needed in a call for actor there's, but they don't know the amount of service or what 

Speaker 1  (06:04)
I have no clue. I asked the guy, can you just tell me where the gift so I can answer that via email and he keeps just pushing for him. 

Speaker 3  (06:15)
This isn't some Prof. how many hours and yeah. 

Speaker 1  (06:20)
I asked him like, what do you need? What are the cash? Can I ask via email like this or the complain? 

Speaker 3  (06:27)
Let me find next 

Speaker 1  (06:30)
So anyways, they'll show the stuff that I would like to give moment for next week. If that's great. But yeah, we can probably jump back into this virus. 

Speaker 1  (06:37)
I apologize. 

Speaker 2  (06:38)
That's okay. Yeah, it's all good. Alright, so why don't we just we start at the top? 

Speaker 2  (06:44)
So so Chad regards to the to the threat model, we had a target of July, third and eighth and 8. 

Speaker 5  (06:52)
Yeah, I think that was sent out to Ata and team for 

Speaker 1  (06:56)
Approval. 

Speaker 5  (06:58)
Is there zoo response? Yeah, even if there's no response, it's just auto improved after 5 days, so it's pretty much it's pretty much done. 

Speaker 2  (07:06)
Yeah, so I can mark it as done then. 

Speaker 3  (07:10)
I don't want to implement that with the speed tickets as well or approved. 

Speaker 1  (07:15)
Thank you, I'm So this is a good stuff, because Arthur was talking to me yesterday about going over the debt that file and so I guess I don't have to do it anymore if it stop 

Speaker 5  (07:31)
Proof I mean the whole point that that file is like, it's things that you should just be aware of and whether you address them or not, it's sort of just for your awareness and eventually be so can review them to programmed, okay. You know, so it's not something you need to act on now, but just be aware of that, it could potentially have things in it that need to be considered long-term. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (07:51)
Burnoff, isn'. 

Speaker 2  (07:55)
Should we either change the the end date or do 

Speaker 5  (07:59)
", it's okay here, I can give you the ticket that it's related to so that it shows that we should all come. 

Speaker 2  (08:06)
I think, is it more too serious? That's it okay? Okay, so we just watched that ticket. 

Speaker 2  (08:15)
Okay, let me park that to the side I'll put a relates to Lincoln here. Okay, then I'll push you off the date. 

Speaker 5  (08:25)
But I think the next time I review this, it'll be safe to put ourselves down. 

Speaker 2  (08:29)
Yeah, so I'll just make it. I'll make it next week, I guess right? 

Speaker 5  (08:36)
Yeah, I realized this fine F. 

Speaker 3  (08:46)
If you just put everything nice food, yeah, that's what I'm doing. Yeah, for sure. My Aaron. 

Speaker 2  (08:53)
Sorry is the best time in my life. Don't ruin? All right, okay, so nti, we kind of checked. 

Speaker 2  (09:01)
We talked about Yeah, that's going to need some coordination. Okay, anything in here? 

Speaker 1  (09:11)
On the skill side, I don't think so I think the next step is basically Chad, and I have to spend some more time on the on the add the housing questions. But that's something for proud, right? I think we will be able to get around that. 

Speaker 1  (09:26)
But. 

Speaker 5  (09:28)
How do you feel about that Howard? Like? Do you think that we'll be okay to kind of put together? 

Speaker 5  (09:34)
Those tables look like the walls, and all that you think 

Speaker 1  (09:38)
I think it will open a kind of warm if you ask me, but that's what it won, right? It might be nothing but You know, the more clarity, the better I see his point, right? Especially with our team using the same ang for everything and you know, people using the name governance, you know, wily, I think it's a good point because it kind of it cannot shows who will have the eyes of what the scope and clarifies a lot of things, so I think it's okay and it shouldn't take us that long. 

Speaker 5  (10:13)
Okay. And also I guess they're really they're just looking for a plan. I mean, even if it changes over the next month or 2 as long as it's up-to-date and accurate, that's yeah, okay. 

Speaker 5  (10:25)
Yeah. You made a books or I've been reading books and things like that. Yes 

Speaker 1  (10:37)
I'm gonna be inviting more people to the call, probably some of the guys from corners, because I couldn't actually go over that specific item to there in that way we can actually clarify who will have the access, and who want, and we'll send them an email today. But hopefully by the time we have the call, we have all the answers that we need. 

Speaker 5  (11:00)
So just quickly, by the way, unrelated, that dspm, the snippet thing you were saying that they were hoping they would send you a physio. Yeah, I don't. This is totally unrelated, but I don't know if you got anything. 

Speaker 1  (11:12)
No, not to get I will follow-up with nap to that. See if they haven't ready. Alright, sorry to 

Speaker 5  (11:20)
Another thing for you know, porish. 

Speaker 1  (11:26)
Dp's second storage, so I can tell you. We got a storage No, we're still working on this, so let's just get this. 

Speaker 2  (11:36)
Yeah, that's your risk, right. So just just that just so you know, everyone that all the risk and impediments, they were moved at the feature level. So that's the way that the 

Speaker 1  (11:53)
I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (11:54)
That's the way they decided to do things now. So you have to kind of go. Into the feature level to look for your risk and impediments 

Speaker 1  (12:04)
Okay, perfect. Yeah, I still got into the date and the good thing is you actually put the link in front of mistaken that yes, dca number. 

Speaker 2  (12:12)
It's yeah, yeah, and and I think there was some discussion a few weeks ago, about a potential risk with sevrik, and so we got, we got a placeholder here for that as well. If that's still valid. 

Speaker 1  (12:27)
I don't know what would be the risk, but I have We can ask you right 

Speaker 2  (12:31)
Ok, so it, it's anyway, it's it's just a placeholder at this point. Okay, so that's where you're going to find your risk impediments now, so that they're no longer from an epic point of view. Sounds good. 

Speaker 2  (12:46)
All right, so okay, so that's programmed to supernatural. That's bigger than the program that's the skill, the scale decision TD scale decision. Okay, so where do we leave off here? 

Speaker 2  (12:56)
Okay down at blob? So we're at the sort of tomboat retention. So at the That's the amazation stage. 

Speaker 3  (13:17)
Can you pick me the number service to be built? Good job. 

Speaker 5  (13:25)
I'm for DPC. 

Speaker 3  (13:27)
Yeah, it's quite of an estimation supposed to be about that. 

Speaker 5  (13:30)
We know DP sector but we're still working on TPS PM. It's the more in a computer, but I'll send you what we have. 

Speaker 3  (13:36)
Parking was totally active closer by zomania and Sonia. 

Speaker 2  (13:43)
And this is the meeting that you have on Monday. 

Speaker 3  (13:46)
Our imaging, the train we can get rid of that meeting. That's what it is. It's an estimate. 

Speaker 3  (13:52)
So to get her that close as possible, and we're on my aw, thank you so much. 

Speaker 2  (13:57)
Okay. So I'll put it update in here. Meetings scheduled for Monday. 

Speaker 2  (14:05)
And that will probably be It's about Monday. 13, so I'll just put it for the 16th again. For the next review Anything else in here 

Speaker 1  (14:28)
I'm a sandwich sharing melodies. Sorry, integration, not early, not in change any of these items. So the mp police dragger set up. 

Speaker 1  (14:47)
You can probably mark that as a completed, unless you have a subst story underneath. Or which one? 289. 

Speaker 1  (15:00)
So he has the best in 29. 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
2 2 89, just 2. 

Speaker 1  (15:06)
Oh, you went down here, okay, sermon, okay. So we're down here. Did you have anything there? 

Speaker 2  (15:14)
Yeah, we got 2 stars Samsung. 

Speaker 1  (15:18)
I want to say a sales currency mandate the stone policy, immigration policy immigration. Okay, perfect. That's what I thought. 

Speaker 1  (15:26)
So we still make grand policies PPI tm that is in progress. What is the tracker? What do you have on 5 33 51 that 251, so tracking documentation. 

Speaker 1  (15:46)
There is done policymaker, great policy, so initial set up and testing. 3 9 8 9 8 2. You can move that to progress. 

Speaker 1  (16:04)
And we probably need to beg 

Speaker 2  (16:09)
So it danced, do we have for that then? 

Speaker 1  (16:12)
We streamed the appropriate cards. A month and a 1 ago. 

Speaker 2  (16:21)
Of course. Yes, and we do exhibit 

Speaker 1  (16:27)
Always my Grandpa is safe for the national setup and testing. I would say should be done by next week. A trial 

Speaker 2  (16:38)
He's there at a site here. 

Speaker 1  (16:42)
I don't know, I guess. Put Fernando for Fernando, thank 

Speaker 2  (16:47)
Yeah, he's not yeah, he's on vacation. 

Speaker 1  (16:50)
Yep, that's the rule it goes down the cell of covering forward this everything is solved. 

Speaker 2  (16:54)
Be for my name in there, I'm What happened while he took off yesterda? 

Speaker 1  (17:10)
What we 're doing is we're actually going to give the ventricle to migrate all the settings from one environment to another, and that includes the speed So when we do bad, we'll probably do production at the same time. 

Speaker 6  (17:29)
I don't know, like the whole thing we identify with the instances and linkages of the portal is that It's something that or checking or I Don' 

Speaker 1  (17:39)
And when I was here, yeah. Yeah, it's part of so we should, but we shouldn't, because it's basically a raw blow in their duty. It's exactly like ah. 

Speaker 1  (17:52)
And it's just basically the last front complaining, some of these data, so it's something that we should have just as part of our team. 

Speaker 6  (18:00)
When I brought it up is because it kind of impacts some of those things you're just mentioning so 

Speaker 1  (18:06)
No, it shouldn't, he shouldn't remember the issue with the mapping is through the vspm, the migration of the policy, which is just detectors, right, is only at the it, and the lp platform level, even though it's 40 ESPN, right, so it won't impact the mapping or anything. Like that, so it should be fine. 

Speaker 6  (18:30)
Yeah, you know, I was a mart looking at it like cause it doesn't stop you from making the detectors or whatever in the one console, but like just the linkages and being able to test and validate, whether it's actually working as expected. Is, until that's linked up? You can't do that that was the main main point, but just mentioning it. 

Speaker 1  (18:55)
Yeah, they don't need to be linked up from the it and the lpc. They do shared information from the back end system right? Everything that we're doing right now on the app that I normalized Io is pulling the data directly from the broad environment, so even though we don't have the detector's synchrony like that. 

Speaker 1  (19:15)
Right? So it is doing all the stuff in the bike game. So based on that, I would say, we shouldn't worry, because even if we don't have the linkage in place, it was still synced the detector. 

Speaker 6  (19:29)
And yeah, I guess I was just thinking about the different environments, then because we're going to have to, it sounds like we have to work directly with Prague, but I guess that's a time thing. But And then I think about the whole scale concern, and whatever later on about Okay, after I guess and Dev teach you do this in Pat and what not cause. For app normalize that IOI don't know if they've actually made A I like the guy in support, said they didn't make an instance for Dev yet, or I don't know if I can't remember. 

Speaker 6  (20:00)
Over a Pat, but they sprawl, that just looks like there's only a Prague instance. 

Speaker 1  (20:05)
Lisa prudent, there's a debt of the Misha de Misha pakude. And the way you are, the way they actually differentiate those with based on the email address, right? But AM let's not stick that off line, yeah, it's actually impacted from this perspective. 

Speaker 1  (20:21)
If you ask me the item that I took my room to actually sit up for next week, is just the detectors. I think we are almost sunnibal detectors, right? It's just a matter of test in the Okay, and find unit Sorry, go ahead, admire my im. 

Speaker 2  (20:37)
It's okay, no, no, it's okay. So so What part of it? So I'll change the target start date to July 1st for this one. 

Speaker 2  (20:43)
Then, however, being we, at the same time as Pat. 

Speaker 1  (20:47)
Yes, boys. Yeah, okay, alright. 

Speaker 2  (20:52)
Thank you so much for just make it for the. I don't know if I can make it today or whatever. Yeah, it doesn't matter. 

Speaker 2  (21:03)
Ok, um, um, U. Emailed. 

Speaker 1  (21:09)
In the dlp, whether you have on the bat, so so Integration in path is done, you may have late integration that is done. Which one, no. No. 

Speaker 1  (21:20)
No, it's not done I mean, trying to get the access to those things. And I kind of get pieces started. I can tell you, can probably Mike those 2 as it started. 

Speaker 2  (21:32)
Sorry, which one were we at? 

Speaker 1  (21:34)
The proper lay and UN people relay, I already reached out to the messaging and improved point program in all the details that I need to get those integrated 

Speaker 2  (21:44)
So this one's in progress. 

Speaker 1  (21:57)
And I would say, if you ask me yesterday, that's right. 

Speaker 2  (22:02)
Yeah, you can. You're reading my mind? And do you have a target end date? 

Speaker 1  (22:08)
Roughly a couple of weeks from now. There it is. Yes, that makes sense. 

Speaker 1  (22:23)
Okay? 

Speaker 2  (22:26)
And you said the same with 

Speaker 1  (22:29)
With the upper life or fourth for Pat So that's, that's a story as well, that by 73. 

Speaker 2  (22:40)
I'd put them in order and didn't realize it was it? Yesterday? 

Speaker 1  (22:55)
Yes, so again, this 

Speaker 2  (22:57)
And in the 30th, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (23:03)
If I cannot get information that I need before the end of the day tomorrow, then I will need to push back another week. Because the fill will post that it involves Only if we can get doses padari, which probably we could again, I could get some help that they just need to make the Vanessa surgeon. That way, we save a week. 

Speaker 1  (23:21)
But that's that You know, everything else seems to be done evm. The firework rule was completed. I just need to test it so the deployment and testing that's still ongoing. 

Speaker 1  (23:34)
It should be completed by next Friday. And after that is done, we'll start, but so I'm not going to touch that yet. So compared to an excitement, improve ponish and wireless stuff. 

Speaker 1  (23:58)
I am not sure what you have here in This is something that I Don' I forgot to forward you. 

Speaker 6  (24:09)
Pyra said that he did send a response, but I think he sent it to yah yourself and And Fernando is in But I don't even know if that is still the Let's see the response, but basically doesn't. This isn't this, we're seeing in a way that we've actually like you've done the weightlisting of these products right? And we kind of covered that this would be probably a tour at the end thing because you have to give each one of these towels like log evidence as well as the bench. 

Speaker 6  (24:44)
And there's stuff that they are actually interfering. And we don't, at this At this point in time, we don't even have, we don't have those like log evidence, or I'm actually interfering, right? 

Speaker 1  (24:57)
Yeah, that will be my 

Speaker 6  (25:00)
But so I think the vendor detailed answer is 1 of it, but then you actually have to have the the Like, show me analog that you're actually having a problem. When you go to the crowd, strike guys, or whoever, whichever guys 

Speaker 1  (25:15)
Yeah, I just forward you. What they sent me. Honestly, they just look like. 

Speaker 1  (25:20)
One of those cand responses doesn't really provide evidence. It's more than like making assumptions that this could happen. Right? 

Speaker 1  (25:27)
So I think we're going to have to set the race and the fact that we're going to have to win for at least in the pilot or beta roof ray, and try to find the evidence from there is something that's going to get affected. But You're going to have to make the decision internally, thank you. 

Speaker 2  (25:46)
Okay, so I'm not sure if I caught that there was an email that said that all these were done or just some of these 

Speaker 1  (25:54)
No, no, no, just keep things as serious. 

Speaker 2  (25:57)
As it is okay, okay. And this is another team, I guess, smell, and to your point I guess some falloff is required with Mel. Is that correct? 

Speaker 1  (26:12)
I could tell you that the test in debt actually work. I tested with jury, so you can probably move that in progress. You could assign that jury, but you could put a note in the testing updating credentials. 

Speaker 1  (26:33)
Programmatically. Improve point work. That was done early this week on Monday. 

Speaker 2  (26:49)
Okay, I'm just gonna make a bike an order that quickly. What was it starting in? 

Speaker 1  (26:56)
I mean the start, I don't know what he started doing the development right but we started the testing on Monday this week on the sixth. 

Speaker 2  (27:05)
And it's, and it's done right. 

Speaker 1  (27:07)
Yeah, that is done and work. 

Speaker 2  (27:11)
So what's your wording game updated the credentials? Sorry, I can't do repeat it. What was your update updated? 

Speaker 2  (27:20)
The you updated the credentials? 

Speaker 1  (27:22)
Yes, update, it is can credentials programmatically. It's certainly I'll programmatic programmatically program. Add tea. 

Speaker 6  (27:42)
Bad tinkly, like automatic. I am Ata CLLY interval of 

Speaker 2  (27:51)
Yeah, sorry. May I accent? I heard that word before, so it's okay. 

Speaker 2  (27:57)
Updated. The scanned curdent shows 

Speaker 1  (28:02)
Automatically, she says funny, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (28:05)
Successful, we think thank you. Yeah, the way I was speaking. 

Speaker 1  (28:09)
I could start go back. It's definitely be so shy of both meat for 

Speaker 5  (28:14)
All together. 

Speaker 6  (28:17)
Yeah, well, cool. 

Speaker 2  (28:17)
All right. Thank you. I learned a new word. 

Speaker 1  (28:22)
See the music and the retirement party. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (28:27)
Like problematically, had another beer. Okay, sorry, that started on the sixth. She said, alright. 

Speaker 2  (28:39)
And finished. 

Speaker 1  (28:41)
I always have finished next week, because actually not finish that tomorrow, does it you're just a good location and we already had a conversation. You're really saying, yeah, everything's working as intended, so okay. Actually, my career has done. 

Speaker 1  (28:54)
There's no point my career has done 

Speaker 2  (29:00)
Yeah, okay, it makes sense. Okay, that's that one. If this updates, you have to refresh anyway. 

Speaker 2  (29:10)
And you know that, okay, next, one functional gaps. Now that 

Speaker 1  (29:16)
Yeah, I mean, they're still in progress. We're still learning to finance infrastructure. 

Speaker 2  (29:23)
Yeah, no, no, it's okay. So what I see emails from With this with this sheet that gets updated, and I just pop it in here. So the last one is June, the 19th current gaps. 

Speaker 1  (29:39)
You know what, I just realized that I'm trying to rush through the question, and I'm thinking that this was half an hour call and didn't realize it was an hour. Okay, sorry 

Speaker 2  (29:47)
That's her lyr. 

Speaker 1  (29:49)
Yeah, so functional gaffe of yeah, but this is on male side, right? We will still test things here, the small stuff that needs to be added, I get a list of 20 different items that we probably need to log under this particular item, right? Okay, II just tried to get a list of mail and see what we're missing when I list and open what is required. 

Speaker 1  (30:19)
What is left and then I will come back and update this. 

Speaker 2  (30:23)
Okay, ok, okay. Okay? So currently The sheet from Mel that's that's in. 

Speaker 2  (30:29)
It's attached or linked, rather, because you can't attach things apparently. Oh, I did attach anyway, my bat. 

Speaker 1  (30:40)
Yeah, there's some leaves that I created as well where all the like, okay. 

Speaker 2  (30:45)
Okay? Because 

Speaker 1  (30:46)
His slaves is just a this is why we think it's mission. First mission, my list is more comprehensive, because it goes into specific, and it also captures the tickets that we have opened with the vendor so we can always go back and reference, and ask the Bender, where are we with this specific request, right? So his list doesn't have a oh I see. 

Speaker 1  (31:10)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (31:19)
I think some of this one here, if I recall That says it's done. 

Speaker 1  (31:30)
Wait, wait, wait, wait, that's not cost scanner. Scott, yeah, not really sure why it's done. 

Speaker 2  (31:36)
Outskirt of the plane, so it says here. 

Speaker 1  (31:39)
That's that's not done. 

Speaker 2  (31:41)
No, I don't. 

Speaker 5  (31:44)
That was just an engagement ticket to talk about it. Of course Yeah, I need the outcome was just do it in a separate subscription, and we actually probably need to have a follow-up conversation there about getting that subscription set up having a name there. Maybe we can put it in this ticket. 

Speaker 1  (32:09)
Shoot, so we go ahead and create an old detail like we did from the For the deep side to scruple, the sight 

Speaker 5  (32:19)
You already did create a subscription for dp sub. 

Speaker 1  (32:22)
We opened at the Egypt, that's the one that got pushed back for csg for a while, but we can probably create a new walk for this guys. 

Speaker 5  (32:30)
Julia was saying that we should talk to Kevin nedzweiki enzuiki. About it, because he's the one that manages descriptions maybe that would be faster too I hear, let me plug in it here at least. 

Speaker 3  (32:50)
I was trying to get him in that meeting on Monday tongue. Yeah, I' A minor aid from him because he's It's trying to Dutch still the lesson. It's busy Yeah, but a Kevin has a lot of thought at least they unjust a lot of the things we need. 

Speaker 5  (33:09)
Reading Azure's description of the view 

Speaker 1  (33:12)
Oregon. 

Speaker 5  (33:26)
Howard, maybe you would want to submit either way. You know? Or we've literally attacked both Wazir ticket and plus talking to him, seeking it, handing him the tickets, my help too. 

Speaker 1  (33:38)
Yeah, I agreed, like, let's quote all the different fronts. Do we have Ivan on this call ivanka? Do you be able to help us with that? 

Speaker 4  (33:50)
I'm sure I can submit the chicken ite. 

Speaker 1  (33:53)
So or if you some of the link, I can create it like I have no issue doing that. I just don't have the the process. 

Speaker 4  (33:59)
No, I can't read it. Awesome kids when it's completely in the 

Speaker 5  (34:06)
If there's an existing one too, it'd be good if we had both and we can tackle them both at that. 

Speaker 2  (34:14)
So it changes the sky, sorry. 

Speaker 1  (34:18)
Yeah, the thing is the one that we have right now is for an app registration for the actually yeah. Yeah, so we can actually connect and you know, get the AD information for our policies, so this might be a subscription which is a little bit different, right? Still assured, but it's a little bit different. 

Speaker 4  (34:37)
So you want me to submit a ticket for the subscription or you want me? Submit a ticket for the app registration. 

Speaker 5  (34:45)
There's already one submitted for app registration, so this is a different topic. This is about getting a new Asher subscription. I don't even know if there is a ticket for that. 

Speaker 4  (34:53)
I don't I will. I'll i'll search a bit. I'll let you know. 

Speaker 4  (34:58)
When I find something 

Speaker 2  (35:04)
So I'm changing this to tiger, correct? Sure 

Speaker 6  (35:17)
But to his point, if it's separated as an app registration, and he's doing a subscription, what did you want to split it or make it a subtask or something just thinking out loud? 

Speaker 5  (35:34)
The cloud scanner deployment I don't think, does this need a app registration. Also I don't remember 

Speaker 1  (35:42)
I don't remember I need to go back as the commutation check 

Speaker 5  (35:47)
I think Step 1 is at least getting understanding how to get any subscription. 

Speaker 4  (35:54)
Are you looking to it? Ask her round. 

Speaker 1  (36:02)
I bought this one. What is that docer? The container, let's change the word doctor to Portman. 

Speaker 1  (36:20)
White man. 

Speaker 2  (36:27)
In part, sorry, part one of the one 

Speaker 1  (36:34)
Photosynthei, for 20, no, not for 20 yet, no Yeah, so this is in progress for dip, right? I'm waiting for the final roll to be implemented, so I can actually go out with the deployment I tested it already indoored, it works, it's actually ways to then I was suspecting way easier. And it's scanning. 

Speaker 1  (37:00)
So I would say, you know, in progress, bring the favorite world to finalize steps it up. I could view the firework gold defense require. Thank you Let me just give you there, just give me 1 second. 

Speaker 1  (37:22)
Dave, we know her bags from the firewall guy Graham. 

Speaker 3  (37:27)
So it's not him, it was, it's Mary. Let me tell you, it's That this morning it wasn't because we were still trying to keep it on tonight. Such agenda once Amazon 

Speaker 1  (37:41)
Yeah, and I just realized that being aware all this time, people might think that I'm just having that beer somewhere. Okay, I just paint you. 

Speaker 3  (37:49)
Yeah, that's inking the yeah. 

Speaker 1  (37:52)
I don't really honestly want to put that here. Okay, thank you gotcha. So once pen, if I were rolled, once this is implemented, I will be able to finish the theory. 

Speaker 1  (38:05)
The problem of aggression In depth. 

Speaker 2  (38:34)
Okay, anything else in here? 

Speaker 1  (38:37)
A scanner policies, scanner policies, I think that I won't even call it spontaneous. It should be like AI don't even think we know that we need that. Yeah, we don't need that item because I think this is covered on the ESPN somewhere like a policy or something. 

Speaker 1  (38:55)
Yeah, this is covered already. 

Speaker 2  (38:57)
Yeah, so it looks familiar, okay. 

Speaker 1  (39:01)
Okay. I'm just marking. I still pretend to delete it or cancel or something. 

Speaker 2  (39:11)
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I'll do forget. So I don't even have a cancel Yeah, that's So honestly, there's just so much setup that needs to be done 

Speaker 1  (39:32)
So this kind of integration with Soviet architect, you can probably put in it. Just set it to start in a couple of weeks from now, three weeks from now, because that's what jury is waiting for. Cameroon, hear. 

Speaker 2  (39:47)
Yeah, yeah, okay. 

Speaker 1  (39:50)
And jury will be taking care of that scanning integration with sharepoint, we haven't done that yet. A scanning intuition would like to do the directory. We're still working on that. 

Speaker 1  (40:01)
This plant is in progress. I think at this point So he wanted to make, he's waiting for somebody's selfie back. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (40:12)
Okay, so this is in progress. And when I got back 

Speaker 4  (40:18)
Howard, we got the firewall submitted this plankton, did that I got these 3 pc RM report in, I also talked to Chad, just in case we went through the diagrams, the integration is there migrant and the tremors team was asking for that request for the specific board, but But I just, we just shuddered, and I would talk, and we just submitted another request, so I'm still waiting for that request to be Pun up alpha Pat. As soon as it gets approved, I'll let the team know again. 

Speaker 2  (41:01)
Yeah, I know. And so what I'm going to need to start this. Say I don't know somewhere around here 15th. 

Speaker 1  (41:16)
Say it deem, probably. I think it's my day. Okay, and then I' 

Speaker 2  (41:28)
Do you do we? I did retire okay? And target completes. 

Speaker 1  (41:37)
I'm not sure about that maybe in July. 

Speaker 2  (41:42)
And we're going to change this to diving. Then, with this one I think you said this, this note's starting, d*** joy, okay, anything else in here. 

Speaker 1  (42:02)
No, no really aging deployments, so You could probably put an Oscar in the pile of deployment whilst towards the end of August, which is still within our timelines. And it's being planned right now. 

Speaker 2  (42:21)
Okay, so we actually, we said September 1st. 

Speaker 1  (42:26)
Yeah, so yes, okay, that same thing is okay. So yeah, yeah. Change it to progress because we're planning What kind of hands can please assign it to a guy called mananta tale? 

Speaker 1  (42:41)
Thank you And then so MA and AN you missing an a now H is M Ana NA I think another A. Yeah, I don't know. And I'm Space Patel should be the third person on your list. 

Speaker 1  (43:05)
Yeah, gotcha ishing. 

Speaker 6  (43:08)
Right? Looks like he had him. That's his icon, yeah, right Avatar, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (43:16)
Okay, sorry, the updates, it's in. It's in progress. 

Speaker 1  (43:23)
We took a target day, you know, Ain of August. All right, yeah, I'm going No pilot deploy, I mean plan in queer. Planning in progress on the way out. 

Speaker 1  (43:40)
Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (43:43)
Unemployment in August. Yeah, okay, gotcha. In August. 

Speaker 1  (43:56)
I would like to send November, but I don't think they'd like that. 

Speaker 3  (44:03)
That's the next project we're starting in November. If I'm finished as long as I'm 

Speaker 5  (44:10)
Oh, no, that's when I'm on vacation. 

Speaker 3  (44:13)
Exactly, they should be celebra. I'm going off. Yep, fine-tuning. 

Speaker 3  (44:22)
After October. 

Speaker 1  (44:28)
Training bend, or I hug that still panding, attack or USO A branch is like 2 hand over. Yeah, that's still not started yet. So I think we call it everything. 

Speaker 2  (44:40)
I think we're up-to-date. All right, let's make a quick go. Make it feel like tweaks here and there, but ok, did you do it? 

Speaker 2  (44:53)
George review this or if you think adding might have some time tomorrow, or would you review this with her or do one of reach out? But 

Speaker 1  (45:02)
Teachers have the time to do the work with you tomorrow. Right after the school, I have a tattoo with the rest of the team, I will bring that up and so she's aware, and I like to touch with you on 10 days. 

Speaker 2  (45:15)
Yeah, okay, okay, so perfect. Sweet. That would be perfect. 

Speaker 2  (45:22)
Actually, that'd be that would be really helpful. Yeah Perfect. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (45:26)
Yeah, okay, I think that's it, anything else? 

Speaker 3  (45:33)
Okay, wonderful that's married so so I've sent out meeting invites starting next week for the same slot. I would 

Speaker 1  (45:42)
Sounds good, sounds 

Speaker 3  (45:43)
And then so mayaren will end his meeting series this week, so you'll probably see that update, so 

Speaker 2  (45:48)
Yeah, I'll do that right away. Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (45:52)
So tomorrow if I don't talk to you again, then In happy retirement, it was a nice working with you. 

Speaker 2  (45:58)
Yes, same American to work with everyone. Yeah, thank you. I'm 

Speaker 6  (46:03)
Is this your last meeting? 

Speaker 2  (46:05)
It is, yes, oh yeah, so in all it goes goes fast, tell him Tom. 

Speaker 3  (46:11)
He didn't catch him just nudging austere, Dan showing off. Hey, good luck next week. 

Speaker 6  (46:15)
Well, I realized that's why he poured it on hard. This one I was about to go down. 

Speaker 2  (46:26)
Yeah, so many things I want to say anyway, all right, try to realize that. Have a good one. Take it easy, very close. 

Speaker 1  (46:34)
Thank you so much for getting the ey. 
