
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Irrespective, I was trying to look at the patterns That we 're dealing with, so You know, when I look at the lists here all valid things, something that I've been given a lot of thought to or the self-service And assisted recovery flows Yeah, cause they're h'. They're rather important, you know, some of these, some of these scenarios, right? So you've got them listed above their eyes. 

Speaker 1  (00:36)
What are they going to do or how do you recover right? Right? So ultimately Talk about different scenarios and so on. 

Speaker 1  (00:47)
They're going to fall into hey, I can recover myself or I need someone to assist me. So I'm much less concerned about all of the individual scenarios. I thought, whatever, however, lost that list ends up being. 

Speaker 1  (01:05)
They're gonna fall into either. I can recover myself or I need somebody to help me. 

Speaker 2  (01:12)
So from my understanding, we have 2, you know, we have both a physical recovery. Someone loses their whole key, kind of thing, and the other thing is, someone forgets their credentials. Is that how we would you would describe this thing at a high level, of course, at a high level. 

Speaker 1  (01:33)
Yeah, I forgot. I forgot my. You know I forgot my pin. 

Speaker 1  (01:36)
I forgot my key. Right, I don't have any different variations. There can be of that But these are, these are really the snares. 

Speaker 1  (01:46)
I mean, it stopped working. Okay? Well, that's equivalent to, if I don't have it. 

Speaker 2  (01:52)
Right, I can also see Jeremy just joined A high teremie, if you're tapping or a mute 

Speaker 3  (02:00)
No, I just joined that wasn't talking yet, okay? I will know Anthony that really quick. Like I don't know what everybody else but like, I can't contact switch 30 minutes at a time. 

Speaker 3  (02:19)
What expects and what we're going to need to do is set app an actual working session that it needs a couple of hours for us to be able to go through and And really kind of get hand to end on this, we're not going to be able to do this in 30 minute chunks, and so if the reason why we put 30 minute chunks is because you didn't see calendar swats, we can talk about how to coordinate that. 

Speaker 1  (02:44)
I have, I have figured I've estimated that I am 4 times more effective. When I get quite a touch right, had the and it's very similar. When you do, you Doing a couple hours, because yeah, I'm looking at 10 o'clock. 

Speaker 1  (02:57)
Okay, we gotta talk ebaco, and I couldn't even. I couldn't even start to think about it. 

Speaker 3  (03:05)
I'm coming off a call link from talking about managing mailboxes and entrance that have an active directory, and I'm gonna spend in the next 25 minutes talking about this, and I'm gonna go flip into another call about how we need to rationalize our terraform organization. So as part of the modernization effort that we're doing right like the I can't. I can't even like Brain switch that fast, though. 

Speaker 3  (03:31)
So Anthony like the key things that I want to get out of this call is obviously this is critical, right? I want to make sure that we understand how we are how we move this forward. I believe that we actually are going to need some dedicated workshop time to run through the use cases properly, and get all the things covered, and there's a few actual workshops that we're going to need there's one specific to like our business, functional use cases for retail right, and then we'll have to talk about our offshore back office use cases. 

Speaker 3  (04:05)
So as well, which are kind of separate from each other, right? And then there's a whole other thing that we were discussing in our session on Wednesday that I don't think that you were in around like application use cases as they relate to MF. A. 

Speaker 3  (04:20)
There's a whole lot more there, and that will probably need its own workshop, but like we are going to need some dedicated time to get through this. Otherwise, the SMEs like myself and Jonathan and etc, we just, we won't be able to focus. 

Speaker 2  (04:33)
No, I am good with that. But folks it is your calendar. I cannot. 

Speaker 2  (04:38)
If you look at your calendar yourself, I wasn't surprised we actually got this half an hour today. But. But yeah. 

Speaker 1  (04:47)
Laugh I just laugh when I look at my calendar someday, you know, when I'm quadruple booked, it's like it doesn't even bother me anymore. 

Speaker 2  (04:58)
Because I don't know if this makes sense, but we can go the standard MVP way, we can break our sections into mvps. What do we really need to do within the next 3 months or horizons? I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (05:13)
So people, some of us dislike, calling it horizons, do we need to go with a staggered approach, using horizon or do we need To really lock in 

Speaker 3  (05:32)
The design we need all of the cases, right, like we can't, there is no like let's just take the core use cases like that. That's not being that's not what's needed here. Right? 

Speaker 2  (05:40)
Okay, so we really need a we really want to come out of this with a thorough design. I mean, at least I guess. 

Speaker 3  (05:47)
We want to come out of this with a thorough set of functional and non-functional use cases so that we can influence the design because there's a lot of open items in the design. 

Speaker 2  (06:01)
Yes, but we do know like, you know, just before you you came in. Looking at it from Jonathan's view, he Was very interested in the recovery. Use cases 

Speaker 3  (06:19)
Yes, because that was where we had a lot of question. In our workshop last Tuesday around power recovery would work correctly. And I forgot my pin to I lost my peek. 

Speaker 2  (06:32)
Yes, there was the physical aspect here there was the logical aspect to it, and there'll be a ton more edge cases that will come up. I'm quite sure manager is not available. A brunch gets stolen person moves branches, there's so much mobility in this in these use cases, because these are retail people. 

Speaker 2  (06:54)
And like, I think this was brought up as a as a big point during the discussions and And of course, so I was looking at something I just threw in there. Okay, this is not a hardcore thing. Sure, do we start with New hire, onboarding, like during the session, I know that you're, you know, a big focus of it was on new hire, onboarding, to be worried about them, initially, or do we really talk about something else? 

Speaker 3  (07:37)
Generally, I like to chunk. So if you, if you recall back down on allowing event with td, but If we recall back to kind of how we were Weir. Before we decided to go agile and blow all of that up, right? 

Speaker 3  (07:56)
We really focused on high level, you know, business functional use cases. And then grab technical requirements and then kind of join them together to get to get to like detail requirements, right? Which helped us with things like flows and stuff like that. 

Speaker 3  (08:12)
Right? So it's helpful for us to understand first. What does a day in the life of a retail person look like, look like, right? 

Speaker 3  (08:20)
Like, let's set aside keys for a second, right? And it's like, how does a new hire? And there's fundamental things that we need to understand to help us with the technical requirements, right? 

Speaker 3  (08:31)
So for example, does a new hire start at a branch, or do they start at a training center? Okay, what happens for a blood? Where do they start where they map to like, what location are they mapped to? 

Speaker 3  (08:44)
And how do we know what location they're going to right? What happens when a user, you know, shifts from one branch to another, is that all potentially users from the branch could go from one branch to another, right? Um, so like what is the life cycles? 

Speaker 3  (09:01)
Like what is the business patterns and life cycles of users in retail, right? And then we can start to map Our process to mega. All right, okay, so how do we inject fighter pieces into that mix? 

Speaker 3  (09:14)
What does that look like? What are our technical requirements for that right? If we know that a float teller starts at some Central abstract location in HR, but their real location that they're going to start, as is mentioned to them by their hiring manager. 

Speaker 3  (09:32)
And they're I just started some other branch. We might be shipping a key to the round branch right to how do we handle that? Xi Jinping have to understand Our business functional use cases first. 

Speaker 3  (09:45)
So we can start to influence our requirements for how it's Where we're going to ship keys, replace keys, how we're going to deal with spares, how we're And resets, for spares, etc et cetera, right? We want to start It's like, gonna roll it to all retail branches. How do you handle that Vs the Bau aspect that you just described right? 

Speaker 3  (10:16)
Yeah, yeah, so yeah, there's a microsneft right here, too. 

Speaker 1  (10:18)
It could be completely different like for our migration effort. It could be that we're shipping. You know, bulkys to each location, but for our business as usual, maybe it goes to a personal address right to address that scenario of all the floaters that could be completely different. 

Speaker 1  (10:34)
Yeah, yeah 

Speaker 3  (10:36)
And that kind of again is dictated by our business use cases. Right. So for example, if we're talking to retail and retail tells us that they have 3000 people that are in a different location than the one that they're mapped to in their HR job title. 

Speaker 3  (10:52)
That immediately tells us that we have to solution something we have a requirement there that we're going to have to work around to your point, Jonathan, where we might need to ship keys to people's homes, or we might need to ship unregistered keys and talk about a registration process for existing users, right? 

Speaker 2  (11:10)
Yeah, Jeremy, if you can just stop there, it's good to you, bought that up because you remember during the work session, there is a solution mobile solution by you become, are we even interested in that solution right now, or is that may have or would like to have 

Speaker 3  (11:34)
There are challenges with the ubico mobile solution, as well as far as the concerns that I have around that are usually How we would actually register administrators who would those administrators be? And who would they have access to administrate, right? That to me, seems like an almost insurmountable problem with retail, I think it would be a much more viable solution for us to figure out A different process for that. 

Speaker 3  (12:05)
But like Yeah, II don't know how to solve that, but I'm not trying to solve the underlying problems right now. Anthony, I'm trying to gather functional use cases that we understand what problems we have to begin with, right not like, you jumped, you jumped right into solutioning, which is very cool. 

Speaker 2  (12:24)
I mean, I'm just bringing that up because it was a big part of the. It was a big part of the this session the other day. I think you must spend the whole afternoon on that. 

Speaker 3  (12:36)
The main goal of the takeaway here You're not wrong Anthony, but that was just Jonathan and I spitballing ideas with you because from the design side without having this stuff in place. But I think we recognize that we need to go back and really focus on what problems are what are problems do we actually need to solve? Thank So again, we want to understand the differences between Canadian and US retail, right, and we want to from from a functional use case perspective. 

Speaker 3  (13:10)
We want to understand the difference between the 2 and I know, Mike has been really focused on US retail, but keep in mind, we have Canadian retail here too, that we have to talk to right. So between the 2 areas right? What are our processes? 

Speaker 3  (13:24)
How does it we need someone to walk us through, like, what does a new hire look like today for both areas, right? 

Speaker 2  (13:33)
Do we do we just knock on HR's door and get someone from 

Speaker 3  (13:37)
It's not HR, it's retail and we have retail engaged in the US and we have engagement in us retail, from windows lover, business that we can releverage for this as well. 

Speaker 2  (13:48)
Because there was talk of the US QM right? I mean, I think the US uses an application called usq mq manager and but 

Speaker 3  (13:58)
I don't know what that is. 

Speaker 2  (14:00)
I think that is, I think that is an internal application that retail in the US uses, but anyway, that's a different story. Yeah, there are differences as brought up in the meeting in the session that day, Canada and us kind of have. Big differences. 

Speaker 4  (14:23)
My greatness, I think a lot of the meetings have focused around differences. In relation to mainframe, but not differences in relation to their sort of break their users. Or because this is this is the larger discussion, the mainframe is just a sub case of use within. 

Speaker 4  (14:42)
There's been 

Speaker 3  (14:42)
We're a little bit of mainframe monopolization, in the conversations that have made me very unhappy, because that's a very small piece of what we're trying to solve. 

Speaker 4  (14:49)
Yeah, and it's really much easier, right if you lose, if you have an issue with your ubiquity, and it stops you from longing in the mainframe, and you can still log into your computer. Things are much easier than if you can't log into a computer so I think that's kind of the like, I think that Anthony that that might that I not that one's not one of the common ones, but that may just be referring to a mainframe application, and not a that's something that's really relevant to their their uses. 

Speaker 2  (15:15)
No, I just watered up because it was a topic that came up for a while and I remember saying, okay. 

Speaker 3  (15:24)
Yeah, I think what I'd really like to do Anthony is I'd like to start with business functional use cases, right? So, like understand how does the new user onboard and what happens throughout the lifecycle of a user do that, what happens with user transfer and other like we want to identify the functional use cases of things like New hire, uh U. A floating user user goes on, leave user transfers from one store to another user transfers from a store to a back office. 

Speaker 3  (15:57)
Or from or vice versa, from back office to a store which can happen right? And And make sure that we have jotted down our functional use cases, right? And then we can use that to start basing off our ubk, specific use cases right, like, okay, for new higher onboarding, how do we get them, the key right? 

Speaker 3  (16:17)
And we can start documenting the options for that for getting your device for transferring stores for you know, for losing your pin. Termination transferring between front office and back office or vice versa, right? Like, let's map Let's start to map our phyto, you know our ubique. 

Speaker 3  (16:38)
Use cases against those functional use cases with the end goal, as you have here in the meeting are objective right is to map the end-to-end user journeys. 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
Yeah, no, I'm good with that, but who is the condom? You said we have retail already engaged. 

Speaker 3  (16:56)
There is retail engagement, Mike mentioned that he met with retail yesterday, which I don't understand why he's meeting with retail without us, but Alina apparently were with him and you captured use cases somewhere. 

Speaker 5  (17:09)
Yeah, I took some notes and those over 

Speaker 3  (17:13)
Okay, so they're not in confluence, anywhere they're not, I don't understand I'm gonna ask them like, why are you meeting with retail without Anthony? And without us. That's the whole point. 

Speaker 3  (17:22)
So like I don't understand that, but If you have a use case, that's great, if you have contacts, even better, right? 

Speaker 5  (17:30)
Yeah, there were basically they had mentioned, like the 4 main user scenarios of the shared worklocation, and there was managers that managed like 4 and five different locations that their support personnel that come in. Like for helped us, where you tell support, IBM feel support, so I can share all that over with you. 

Speaker 3  (17:50)
Okay, yeah, and I think that before we even go to retail Anthony, I think that we should, we should define what we want to get from retail, and where we have questions, right? And so I think in our next working session, I don't think we're going to solve it now, because we have 10 minutes. But let's find an extended time to work together, and let's map out what we think the lifecycle use cases are that we need more details from retail, so that we can meet with them, and we can even start to map some of our second stage stuff against that right, like what does Fido. 

Speaker 3  (18:21)
Key, look like for this new user onboarding, etc, like we don't have to do it all sequentially per se, but it would be helpful for us to go through and clearly document like, okay, here are the use cases that we know about so far. And here's where we have questions for retail, so that way, we can have a directed conversation with done, rather than just meeting with them, which is what we've been doing right, is just meeting with them and saying, tell us your use cases, right? We need to kind of dictate that a little bit better too to them. 

Speaker 2  (18:50)
No, I'm good with that. Okay, I mean because to save time, and then I know we won't have an extern today. We today isn' 

Speaker 3  (18:59)
Clock. 

Speaker 2  (19:00)
Okay, you were we wanna block everybody's calendar at. Can everybody block their calendar by Friday 1 o'clock? Folks thumbs up, okay, I'll send the invite. 

Speaker 2  (19:13)
Don't worry, and please block your calendars for 

Speaker 3  (19:18)
I can. I can clear up 1 to 8I don't know if we need that long for this first session, but I can clear up 1 to 3 if needed. 

Speaker 2  (19:26)
Okay, folks, is everybody okay with that? 

Speaker 5  (19:29)
I think Friday's a holiday in the US. 

Speaker 2  (19:32)
Isn't it all right? 

Speaker 5  (19:34)
It's your tweet, yeah, thank you. Is it is it a holiday for everyone? 

Speaker 3  (19:44)
I mean. There's like 3 holidays that aren't optional. Um, if you're taking Juneteenth, that's fine. 

Speaker 5  (19:53)
Everyone here is going to take it. I can go ahead and ask everyone just to make sure oh Mike and I don't I guess he's then. 

Speaker 3  (20:01)
I'm not sure it's a stat holiday. Although I generally don't take most US Holidays except for the like Christmas. So so if it's just because most of my work aligns with Canada, right? 

Speaker 3  (20:18)
So it depends, I know that I've got many other meetings and stuff on that day. So 

Speaker 2  (20:24)
And and 2 and 2 second important thing is where do we house all this? Now what's going to be our parent repository? I know confidence was suggested earlier, because all the stuff that's coming together will have to stay live somewhere. 

Speaker 2  (20:44)
So do we use conference 

Speaker 3  (20:46)
Well, you've got a few options, right? If you're more comfortable working in Excel. Mhm, for this, then, if you want to share it as a OneDrive link at least so it's online that's fine if you're comfortable working in conflicts, we can capture and confluence as well. 

Speaker 2  (21:02)
I'm okay with any. The only thing is I don't like the idea of attaching, you know, tons and tons of attachments and selling emails around the place. 

Speaker 3  (21:14)
No, like we can we again, even if it's the benefit of OneDrive in sharepoint, and stuff online is that you can create a document and share it live, so you're not sending you not sending a document around it's live. It's host in wonder. 

Speaker 2  (21:27)
No, no, that's what I'm okay with any. I just don't want to make it a my personal OneDrive, because if I go on vacation and something happens. 

Speaker 1  (21:37)
You know, things completely so confluences confluences isn' 

Speaker 2  (21:42)
Okay, thank you 

Speaker 3  (21:43)
So I'm happy to share a space and confluence, Anthony and give you right access to it for this project. So let me do that. Now if Friday is so Paula, you are you here Friday or not? 

Speaker 4  (21:58)
I intend to be though I've been trying to confirm with Mike. That's okay, because now there's more intensiveness on the US side, but I'm sure it'll be fine. 

Speaker 3  (22:12)
Jonathan, I don't know what your availability is on Friday. 

Speaker 1  (22:17)
I'm good at 1I might need to pop out a few minutes before 3, but not much like maybe 245, but I'm good, I'm good at 1. 

Speaker 3  (22:26)
Yeah, let's book it and honestly even if it's just Anthony yourself and me and Jonathan at the end of the day, we can still make some progress to like detail emotional stuff that we know. 

Speaker 2  (22:36)
Then, we need just, we just need to kick at it and keep it off as we go I don't think to us, we'll get us everywhere we need to go, but at least, hopefully, then it'll give us a place where we can divide and rule and break it up into smaller chunks. 

Speaker 4  (22:55)
And and the title of this I know we've been focused on retail, because they have their own distinct requirements, but this is this. This Is this intended to cover the enterprise? So it's more than just 

Speaker 3  (23:07)
We are going to have to cover other use cases as well. Yes 

Speaker 4  (23:11)
Like, there's no, you know, single person to talk to about that necessarily I think. 

Speaker 3  (23:15)
I know, but like I've got I've been capturing bdi use cases and test cases with Jonathan and stuff as well. Most of our other use cases are offshore vdi users. 

Speaker 4  (23:28)
Um, okay. So I guess the Joe back office user generally doesn't need this anyway. So right? 

Speaker 3  (23:35)
Because everyone else has wanted to look for business right? 

Speaker 4  (23:38)
Okay, never mind that simplifies that I was just like trying to think there's nobody to talk to. That represents the whole back office area. No, no, for not. 

Speaker 4  (23:46)
This isn't mostly is in the back office case. So okay? 

Speaker 3  (23:50)
This is yes, primarily the 2 main use cases that we 're looking at are vdi. So like or not vdi, but like remote access, user like someone who doesn't have ATD laptop right, and shared desktop, which is primarily just retail. Now, are there a couple of edge cases out there in the environment? 

Speaker 3  (24:11)
Where we have like a male room with a shared desktop, or something, maybe, and we may need to look at that too. 

Speaker 4  (24:17)
Yeah, I was going to say, I don't know if anybody's looked at I know, you know, shared desktops have come up once or twice facility. When gotten like a report on shared desktop or on really a guest desktop computers, right? 

Speaker 3  (24:28)
In our in our brainstorm on Friday, what we should make an attempt to do right is understand the logical use cases for the ones that we are aware of right. So starting with retail, because retailers are by far our largest use case here, right? Our logical use cases for retail, and then we can talk about our logical use cases for remote users, which we have a bunch of those already, and we can brainstorm on some other potential use cases, right? 

Speaker 3  (24:56)
So shared fiber room et, cetera, and we can identify where there's gaps in knowledge that we have to go out and take some action items to go out and solve right? Which could include, I've actually already asked Dave Kleinstein for this, but I know that he forgot about it is, give me a list of back office desktops, and where they are bye, by Um, so that we can understand 

Speaker 4  (25:19)
I have we have the say, I think I have access to reporting that at least tracks that through the users that used them. But that's Right? And this in the sense that that's all part of windows. 

Speaker 4  (25:30)
Hello. For business includes user affinity, reporting and desktop person laptop. So we could squint at that, but obviously their team knows farmer far. 

Speaker 4  (25:38)
Far more about those use cases than we do. 

Speaker 3  (25:41)
Right, and so it's possible that we may have at 1 point need to involve, you know, 1 or 2 folks from employee enablement to kind of like dig into those a little bit right? But those are definitely edge cases, obviously the primary focus for us at the moment is retail. Remote use offshore, you know, vdi type user. 

Speaker 3  (26:07)
Yeah, thank you And we have some of the Bedi use cases captured already Anthony, I actually Jonathan, and I have been capturing use cases. In a confluence already and so I'll share that confluence with you when we craz. 

Speaker 2  (26:25)
As soon as we can all have one view of you know, whatever's out there because I know things are really spread out right now. Like Malina has something you have something. Jonathan has something Paul has something And you know, nobody knows what each other has So if you can just, I'll make an index and I'll keep it there. 

Speaker 2  (26:48)
So at least we have an index 

Speaker 3  (26:51)
And yeah, and I've actually already kind of we had already started to capture some some high level stuff for Which I think we need to rework, but we've already started to capture some super high level items for even phytokey requirements, right? And so obviously these need to be reworked, but we had already started to capture some of that information as well as some like, these are actual non-functional requirements which are Like NFC, reader requirements and stuff right that Jonathan had captured. 

Speaker 3  (27:30)
So but do we need to rework this? Yes, um U. We also have vdi stuff that we've run through for vdi, and the use cases for Vidi, as well, most of this is scratch, bad stuff that I was working on with Jonathan, but we can create some new pages and kind of restructure it into some standardized format. 

Speaker 3  (27:52)
And make sure that we're capturing the right information, right? 

Speaker 2  (27:56)
We don't even have to rebook the page or move it. We just put an index somewhere and say, okay, you know, things are there folks, and we'll need to work on this. 

Speaker 3  (28:06)
I don't know if you have access to this. 

Speaker 2  (28:08)
I think I have, I think you have already shared this. Let me, but Lisa, I think we don't have to have 

Speaker 3  (28:14)
Right access, let me know, and we'll, we'll, we'll do that. 

Speaker 2  (28:19)
I'm excited so we can do that perfect. Yeah, because I even one thing I found out was when you'll be talking laptops. And then some of the people said, not, you know, not all laptops are equal, some of them have USB keys, some of them have usbc keys and That may create a problem to And then some of them have their keys under the desk. 

Speaker 2  (28:47)
What's his laptop desk or something like that? I don't know it just keeps ongoing in circles. 

Speaker 3  (28:53)
Yeah, so that's why we need to kind of break it down into manageable chunks, right? That's why I was saying, like, let's start with, like, how does user work right? And then we can also focus on the other side of that Anthony, which are more the non-functional. 

Speaker 3  (29:05)
Type things like the physical things that are needed. Right. What do we need from the devices where are the devices are they under the desk? 

Speaker 3  (29:13)
Are they on top of the desk? Are they all-in-one devices that are part of the monitor because they have those 2 right, and those things play into it as well, right. We haven't done it, but 

Speaker 2  (29:24)
Renters in the scope for this apprentice, in scope 

Speaker 3  (29:28)
Renters, yeah. There's a printer use case that came up. Jonathan yep. 

Speaker 1  (29:36)
I saw that I respond. I responded to it yeah. 

Speaker 3  (29:40)
That, and I've actually worked with fab soft before. And so I'm somewhat familiar with that. To be honest with you, I don't know that we're going to solve that. 

Speaker 3  (29:50)
Well, I think I saw your response to that which is about the same as my, what my thoughts were. Which were Like it'd be awesome if we could magically consolidate that into one key. But Today, yep, not today. 

Speaker 3  (30:09)
Okay, so Anthony, let me know. 

Speaker 2  (30:11)
Young mother, just go a lanyu Melina, if you could please share whatever you have also. And if anybody else has, so it's time to, we need to, you know, have one view of all this stuff and hopefully a dashboard. Someday folks, it's 30 minutes up, I know, you're a busy and I will set up the Friday 1:00 to 3:00, please clear calendars, and I will also make sure Mike can also attend because he seems to have a lot of information behind the stuff. 

Speaker 3  (30:47)
Okay, Xbox. 

Speaker 2  (31:00)
I lost a little bit 
