
Speaker 1  (00:00)
That would be bad, because there's a reason why they're in the managed, right? So they change every day so that will force us to I have a map process to update everything daily. That is that 

Speaker 2  (00:12)
What do you mean if if the group is called within the list right you would just need to make sure that that ad group is updated. 

Speaker 3  (00:22)
Well. 

Speaker 2  (00:22)
I mean, I don't, I don't know, I'm just I'm just spitballing here. I'm just trying to ski winner, so we have country fudium. 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
I look at that as a possibility as well, and there was no option for any group. This is everything that we have. Okay, let me see it. 

Speaker 3  (00:39)
I mean. 

Speaker 1  (00:41)
If we need to go back to this point, we let's do that like, if you need to reset, that's fine. Maybe we don't spend the time right now unless if we need to do so. Research, I'm okay with 

Speaker 2  (00:53)
Okay, just give me just give me just 1 minute, ok? Yeah 

Speaker 1  (01:05)
I even try looking at fire. 

Speaker 3  (01:07)
The firewood ro. 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
If I can actually create a fireball road that allows me to tap into a specifically group and the conditions where also limited, I couldn't find anything that allows me to tap into an edit group from the firewall perspective. Sorry, this is everything that was that I was getting. In blue receptin, and if you go, for example, in blue center, it's pretty much the same as creating a regular, cruel condition. 

Speaker 2  (01:38)
Yeah, I wonder if that field appears after we make that integration. Because I've seen there should be Yeah, there should be something like Belongs to Yeah, it grew prop. Assignment yeah, so I'm just looking and here Bay, we can come back to it. 

Speaker 2  (02:01)
I mean, this is something that I just had to figure out which field to do this, so I can just send you an email on that. 

Speaker 1  (02:13)
Okay, yeah, but that's fine so Harris. I think one of the questions that was puzzled in the team. For the last couple of days, I'm 

Speaker 3  (02:22)
It is the ability to tap or detect A 

Speaker 1  (02:24)
Asthma protective file. 

Speaker 3  (02:27)
Using the endpoint, the rp 

Speaker 1  (02:31)
I probably 

Speaker 3  (02:33)
Don and. 

Speaker 1  (02:34)
I think back about the what was the 

Speaker 4  (02:38)
Yeah, I have an open screen. Yeah, Jitin, you can just jump in wherever you see fit. I'm doing second main. 

Speaker 4  (02:51)
There's the share buttons. Yeah. 

Speaker 5  (02:52)
And yeah, this is the intra ID 

Speaker 4  (02:55)
I'm a little wearing scream resistance. I'll just scream. 

Speaker 5  (03:01)
Still, the 

Speaker 4  (03:03)
Okay, the beat on so so Harris, they use kings getting us in the svm. We understand like you don't have there's no encrypted file detection, but after the scan runs in the report they might show. File's feeling because they're encrypted or something like that. 

Speaker 4  (03:27)
But we 're also looking 

Speaker 2  (03:29)
I'm so sorry to cut you off, it's just that the Howard's first point I was just looking at something in here, so I'm gonna just come back to you. So Howard, we don't have to go into this break now, but I see that for the group assignments, you have to do in the traditional pod on cloud Admin, we can't do the group assignments via or like through the policy round. So on the traditional pod, you have to do it there so I can send you if we want to get to Don's point I can send you the exact feel on the pod side. 

Speaker 2  (04:01)
That you need to do, but once you set it up on the pod, then you can it'll show up in the it'll show up in the new like udlp policy or outspage it just needs to be created in the pod, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (04:18)
Did you look in size good? No, I didn't look in the pod itself. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (04:23)
Yeah, I see the field. It's sender or recipient belongs to group, so you'll see it in there. 

Speaker 1  (04:30)
Ok, so I need to go to there and then move any chest on the other side, okay, perfect. 

Speaker 2  (04:34)
Yeah, you don't need to move it here you just created over there and it should just sink over here. So All right, Don yeah, my apologies. I was just okay, so I'm sorry, can you can you start from the top? 

Speaker 4  (04:48)
We have been reflect so basically it's about encrypted trial detection, so some background contacts is in our previous conversations. Howard was mentioning that it was confirmed by your side that DSP M doesn 't actually support detection of encrypted files, but when reports are generated after scans are complete. It will show entries for files that couldn't be scanned because they're encrypted. 

Speaker 4  (05:19)
So that's one way of seeing it, but we have other use case. So we were trying to, what we did see is that on the upside. Explore portal side of things, or we can call it the Yeah, our dp sec, we can call the dp sec, the dp sec portal. 

Speaker 4  (05:38)
We notice we can create a condition Because there's a flag here just an identified, we did some tests where we uploaded encrypted files and looked that we dug into the details of the exploration, and we found, he found that action reasons. And we could use this and then encrypted files for these content types, and that was great that we could make this condition. And we could either save it as a rule, but what we really wanted to do 

Speaker 2  (06:09)
Can I can I can? I saw a beer? Can I ask questions? 

Speaker 2  (06:12)
Is this was this working when you tested it like this? Action reasons trigger encrypted file. 

Speaker 4  (06:19)
And now, so so So what I said was we uploaded and encrypted file to try to see in the exploration, what details would be flushed out that would provide us a breadcrumb to start looking for so this is the breadcrumb that we took out of there because it did show actions regans and it showed that about encrypted files, so we took that and made a condition which you could also save as a rule. But what we want to do is we want to We want to have this condition somehow, as part of a detector because detectors we can publish to evaluate always in dspm, and that's the question, can we somehow take the details from that condition I just showed and have it create a custom. 

Speaker 4  (07:18)
A detector here where we can have the flag of Hopefully, I'll hi Always, you know, like, you know, any one of these things? 

Speaker 2  (07:28)
Yeah, so here's the thing on on the detector side, you're not really calling any conditions in the detector right? You're only calling the acifier, so you wouldn't be able to create a detector with just like a condition name because it has those operators like red score. So it's those operators only allow it to read those, you know, either to smart identifier values or the dictionary values, there's no operator in there that would let you call it condition. 

Speaker 2  (08:00)
So, you know, you don't have to put it in here. 

Speaker 4  (08:03)
Yeah, so we saw that we just thought we would ask you to see if there was some way we could, you know, be creative and do that. But it sounds like you're specifically relying on the on those operators, which are just the d*** score, red, score, EDM, score those things. 

Speaker 2  (08:20)
That's exactly right, so on the on the DSP M side. It doesn't give you like how you picked up that action or the content action trigger, that's like, in the content scanning report, it would, you know, it would basically tell you when it fail closed, or you know, if it was just in detection mode, it would just tell you that the file was encrypted. So it didn't perform the content scanning, so there's no similar function in dspm. 

Speaker 2  (08:51)
You're saying I don't work on the dspm side, so I'm not sure. 

Speaker 4  (08:54)
I don't believe we that there is that's and in Howard, in our conversations with the others who, from dspm, that's what he told us, but we're just trying to like, for instance, anflar and yeah, so it would have been like, say this one I don't know. If I go into details and It's soon found this. We saw the resources 

Speaker 6  (09:28)
It wasn't processing. 

Speaker 4  (09:33)
Okay, that's process application. 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
Yeah, I don't think so again, I don't know about the DSP N side, but I know. Yeah, this is this is like, normally how customers would either create like a condition like you did, or create an exploration that just has this action reasons trigger so they can see all of the instances in which the content scanning is not being performed? So 

Speaker 4  (09:59)
You know that you had the endpoint side 

Speaker 2  (10:02)
That would just be on the endpoint side. That that's that's right, yeah. 

Speaker 6  (10:05)
Quick, quick, quick quick question. So in order to link Because from what I understand you can't create separate rules or policies on the dskm side right, the only way your dspm scans work is by connecting the detectors that are set up on the Explorer portal. So from what dawn showed. 

Speaker 6  (10:29)
We can only monitor encrypted files or detect encrypted files through rules right or conditions. We can monitor them through 

Speaker 2  (10:39)
Through the detectors, yeah, you're exactly right, but on the end point you can have that rule on email, you can set up a firewall rule to, you know, basically alert when there's like an encrypted or password protected file on dspm. I'm just, I'm not the right person to ask. Because that's like the one tool I just, I don't know much about, but yeah, I know on the email side on the endpoint side, you have that option, but if hagop had mentioned that it's, you know, that that functionality doesn't exist on the dspm side, then yeah, to answer your question a little bit more directly done, is yeah, there's no way for you to pull in the condition you created into a detector for you to use on the dspm. 

Speaker 4  (11:23)
Okay. We don't go back to you, Howard. 

Speaker 1  (11:28)
Yeah, and just to confirm 

Speaker 3  (11:34)
The way that if you don't you want to go back to that to that policy, when you detect compass or protect it, you want to make sure that it's just the right approach, I would date it, or we should be adjusting our printing on this to look for something else I just want to make. Sure, we have an amazing anything that could be passed or protected or encrypted. 

Speaker 2  (11:52)
Yes, no, that's that's right. I mean, so do you guys have a rule that's just calling that condition in there? Yeah, it should be good now. 

Speaker 2  (12:02)
There's another field. I would just include in that condition, because I've seen sometimes that action. So okay, let me let me show you, can you cancel out of here and just open an exploration like in the workbench and filter for that action reasons, type or action reasons, trigger encrypted mail. 

Speaker 2  (12:31)
Sometimes for some reason, it falls under another field, so it might be good to just, yeah, and you don't even need to have the upload. Yeah, you don't even need to have the upload one in here. So so maybe open it up to like the last few days cause I don't know if you guys pushed any tests in the last day, but 

Speaker 4  (12:50)
Well, I know that that action if we're going to filter and that action. I even forgot what it's called. What is it? 

Speaker 2  (12:57)
So so so go up to the top and go click on change filters. 

Speaker 5  (13:00)
Out from the World War 2. 

Speaker 2  (13:03)
And type in processing here, oh yeah, that's weird, okay. Um, oh God, this is like not rendered properly. Can you can you just refresh the page for like X this out? 

Speaker 2  (13:17)
Because 

Speaker 4  (13:18)
Yeah, you know, let me just let me just 

Speaker 2  (13:25)
No, I think, oh, there we go okay, perfect, so go to processing. And then so do action reasons trigger 

Speaker 4  (13:37)
Yeah, I can't wait well. 

Speaker 2  (13:39)
Oh, I don't think you say yeah, click on this again. 

Speaker 5  (13:42)
Eventually, eventually, you go to the process and come to look like, if we missed part of 3 stories. 

Speaker 4  (13:48)
The picturing isn't trigger, I click on it right 

Speaker 2  (13:51)
I think it's just like the page is. Can you just refresh the page? I think it's just like 

Speaker 4  (13:58)
Thank you. 

Speaker 5  (14:04)
I was able to plan for entertainment like, I think entrepreneur will be a sicker one, because no one nuanced to spread. 

Speaker 4  (14:10)
Okay, so I'll kill this. Kill that make anyone just can double processing. Just go down to the street. 

Speaker 2  (14:21)
There we go. All right, so do you see how there's nothing? There's nothing here. 

Speaker 2  (14:27)
Alright. Do me a favor open it, open it up for like 7 days. 

Speaker 6  (14:32)
Results in the activity something I might show up or no 

Speaker 4  (14:35)
Yeah, I think I clicked something else when I did all fields. 

Speaker 3  (14:40)
So just to clarify what kind of activities are we looking for I would look for email, I would look for anypoint Irish, because we're just an 

Speaker 2  (14:49)
No, I know we're just looking for endpoint. Events that triggered, like the content analyzer to fill because the file was encrypted. 

Speaker 1  (14:56)
Okay, just make it sure. 

Speaker 6  (14:59)
Yeah, I don't go to crowdfloated. 

Speaker 2  (15:02)
Encrypted file proposed, so you guys, you guys haven't even tested it yet. Okay, so here's the then. 

Speaker 4  (15:07)
But we did test it, we that was what we showed you yesterday. We uploaded a file that is encryp. 

Speaker 6  (15:14)
Yes, you're right. Ok, okay. 

Speaker 2  (15:16)
Okay. So now go up, go back up to change filter, that's what my point was this. This, this, for some reason, it doesn't always wander, this one, go down, go to processing, and then instead of clicking on trigger, go to action reasons, type one right above it. 

Speaker 2  (15:34)
And is there an And go to show results of them activities. 

Speaker 4  (15:40)
And that's 0. 

Speaker 2  (15:42)
Yeah, go to go to realm setting, go to realm setting and his own yeah, this one, check it. Yeah, check it and just click done I want to see if this is if this is a cause that trigger, I know that's what it says in the alert. So I know I see how you got to that, but it's not always the field that matches on the rule set. 

Speaker 2  (16:03)
So if you click on this, can we see if these were the activities that happened? 

Speaker 4  (16:06)
Israel, the black one I just showed like when I started the aspiration, but just the upload. This was the exact same activities. 

Speaker 2  (16:13)
Okay, so I would what I would do good then is add add this Activity also to that rule, because you can have multiple activities in there because sometimes it comes under this one, sometimes it comes under the trigger, so I usually just put both 

Speaker 6  (16:29)
I think in the previous, I mean, in the alert that we saw, it showed realm setting, and 

Speaker 2  (16:35)
Bigger type s*** s***. 

Speaker 6  (16:36)
It encrypted Violet raid yeah. Yeah, if we filter on encrypted file, you're saying it won't show up. 

Speaker 2  (16:42)
So go to processing here yeah, encrypted file. I'm saying that this trigger like this field right here, when you use it in a rule it for some reason, it just doesn't always work right. Sometimes it falls into that realm like, sometimes I'm blocking it right here, sometimes you need to trigger for this realm setting, because the encrypted file is like a realm setting that you guys have set up there so I would just include both. 

Speaker 2  (17:08)
I mean it's gonna give you the same, it's gonna give you the same thing, right? But not 

Speaker 6  (17:13)
What if there's something else as a part of your own setting? So we would get that as that would also be captured like, I don't know what realm setting holds, but yeah, there has something more than 

Speaker 2  (17:22)
Yeah, there's like 3 or 4 of them, right? One of them is encrypted file, and they all might be ones that you you might want to keep an eye on right? But it would be like file size so there's a few scenarios in which the content analyzer would fail right? 

Speaker 2  (17:39)
So there's the file size threshold that you guys have set in the realm setting. There's the number of files in bulk. There is the encrypted file. 

Speaker 2  (17:49)
And then, you know, if the content analyzer fails for like any other reason, like a connectivity issue or something like that it will it will by default fail closed. Right. And this gets a little bit odd. 

Speaker 2  (18:05)
But okay, if you have the tool in a detection mode, like you don't have any prevention enabled right when the content analyzer fails, it will, you know, it will just fail open. It'll just tell you in the content scanning report that it failed, there was a connectivity issue, or it was an encrypted file something. Like that, when you have a prevention rule in place, let's say that there's a you have a prevention rule to block web file uploads a certain type of data. 

Speaker 2  (18:37)
When the content analyzer sees that there's like a upload occurring, and that it needs to scan the content, right? It's a content scanning rule, and for some reason it fails, but the action on that rule is a block, it will fail close, which means that it will just like automatically block the user from from doing whatever they're doing So, those are kind of the scenarios that in which the analyzer would fail and kind of what the potential impact would be. I know that's not tied to your exact question around the encrypted files, but the encrypted file is just one of the 4 or 5. 

Speaker 2  (19:16)
Actions that would cause it to fail. 

Speaker 3  (19:23)
Yeah, so d***, this is what I'm thinking and I see where harvest is going with this right so I think we should have one policy or one condition that looks for encrypted files. But what Harry is suggesting we probably want to have it as a separate item, because that will capture things that will fail during processing. Remember how we have something similar with an escob that does a bug that captures everything that fails during processing or fails often or felt close. 

Speaker 3  (19:49)
This is what this is going to account for so if, for example, something falls open, I can take a passion protected file that the condition will pick it app and I'm guessing, based on what you're saying Harris, this will account for anything that felt so open and felt closed. It will be captured as part of that realm of conflict, right? Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (20:07)
Yeah, that's right. 

Speaker 4  (20:09)
I'm glad so just so if there's a great, so it's very hard. Just suggest a reiterate. We would like hires where you were originally saying that we would edit this and add another condition. 

Speaker 2  (20:22)
I would edit this and also add the I mean, Howard had a good point. You can make it separate, right if you want to make a separate condition for the content. The action reasons type and then the realm setting, and that would give you not only the encrypted file but it would give you all of those other realm settings, as well like the different failure points. 

Speaker 4  (20:43)
Okay, yeah, so that's another different detection rule-based on the agent reason type and agent reason trigger. 

Speaker 2  (20:51)
Yeah, I mean, if you want to create a detection rule, you can. Most customers will just have an exploration, unless you guys specifically want to be alerted every time one of these failures occurs like an exploration would probably suffice, right? Just like the saved query of the context at every, you know. 

Speaker 4  (21:10)
She had, I don't know if that would agree, work like. Yeah, so I guess Howard, maybe it would. I just thought you would want these types of things lodged in an alert area. 

Speaker 4  (21:21)
Versus icons, King of the ice Colony 

Speaker 3  (21:26)
Yeah, I would say, let's have an exploration, because that's how we do it when escort to there right? Let's keep consistent. Remember remember the report that we just said where things fail, it will be the same concept as long as somebody's so aware that that exists and that we actually go on an X basis stage and see if there's room for opportunity or try to identify an issue, right and bring it up to the vendor then that should be enough. 

Speaker 3  (21:52)
I don't think we need a role or anything like that for the data. 

Speaker 4  (21:56)
So I'll make an exploration, okay, that's it. 

Speaker 2  (21:58)
Yeah, you could just make 2 explorations done one for the realm setting one for the encrypted file. If that's when you know if that's one that you guys want to like, monitor more closely and just have those saved there. 

Speaker 6  (22:09)
I think the ancryptophile exploration filter wasn't really working when I tried it, but I think the realm setting one gives us the information that we want to see right. 

Speaker 2  (22:21)
Okay, yeah, then you could just add the wrong setting on the ly. Was there was there anything else around this? Like conditions part 

Speaker 6  (22:31)
I had one question, which is sort of interest, so you see how and don't rule you saw content type studies selected right in applications as PDF and whatnot. So I'm assuming that can be matched to like, like, let's say any sort of file type detection right if you hover over that done. So you see, the one for spreadsheet or Excel has something called application and D dot open xml format and like a bunch of other stuff, right if we are trying to Detect specific content types. 

Speaker 6  (23:10)
These few ones were the only I guess. Default options that we can select, like, let's say, if there was I don't know some sort of web Transcript file, or like btt file right? Is that supported in this way, or are these just a few? 

Speaker 6  (23:27)
Options that we can select for Condon types. Does that make sense, so I'm trying to look into like file type detection, right? 

Speaker 2  (23:34)
Yeah, yeah, so let me ask you this. Do you want to see the instances where it failed with all the content types, right? Because this is only gonna give you if it failed with the specific content types, so I would almost just have, you know, get rid of this part at least as part of the that one exploration right? 

Speaker 2  (23:54)
Because I would assume you would want to see all instances of the regardless of the content type when the file is encrypted. You know 

Speaker 6  (24:03)
So, not even literally this rule specifically my question was towards content types, right, let's say, if I want to look for any sort of media files right or media content type how would I know what this option would be called in order for me to insert it right because when we open this option it only gave us, like these 34 things that we got to like, right? Like, how would I know? Ah, sorry. 

Speaker 6  (24:30)
Yeah, like, how would we be able to create one for I don't know, let's say before I is 

Speaker 4  (24:35)
I guess that's another good question like sir Harris is, is that the general principle that we can only when we make these things, can we only select observed values, or can 

Speaker 2  (24:46)
No, no, no, you can. You can add like, if you have the custom values you can so edit this, you should be able to add them directly in there, so click on this. Yeah, just click on this. 

Speaker 2  (24:58)
And just type up like test or something in here. 

Speaker 4  (25:01)
Alright, right? Yeah, I had close. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (25:03)
Yeah, so you should be able to just add it here. And once it's observed, right? It'll, it'll 

Speaker 4  (25:07)
But I guess jitton's point is, this is following like application application like, yeah, what is the format for the media like? What's your, what's your example like? It' 

Speaker 6  (25:19)
Like, if, like, if I also look at excelfels, I would not think to put application and D dot open xml format, - off the stopment right? 

Speaker 3  (25:28)
I can probably dig the Harry, so there is this this page where you can actually can identify every single file type. I don't expect Harry. So the band there to provide that, but you should be able to Google 2 file types, and there are multiple blanks where you can actually see all of them, right and you can just go and grab whatever you need and put an ank 

Speaker 2  (25:54)
So let me ask you this. I think if you I think there's another filter in here that would just give you like the.pdf. 

Speaker 6  (26:03)
So yeah, that was an extension. Yeah, that was extension, which would just be like xls X or PEF right, but in the when I was exploring the alert itself, I didn't see anything specific that said, oh, this would be like a Microsoft Excel file, or this would be Adobe ep file. You know what? 

Speaker 6  (26:22)
I mean, the only thing that I saw was really the closest thing that I saw was content type, which is application PDF or application. 

Speaker 7  (26:36)
Yeah, but you can also add it this part as well, right? You see on the right inside corn and it's just add or input. 

Speaker 4  (26:43)
According to 

Speaker 7  (26:44)
Conversation yesterday, right? I was in encrypted power types. We can have the least of it and just, you know. 

Speaker 3  (26:51)
The least of them are going to be 

Speaker 6  (26:54)
So essentially, file type is not supported. File extension is supported, right? So we can have our use case go through that route. 

Speaker 6  (27:00)
I was just talking about the content type filter, but I guess it makes sense. What we can possibly do Don is we could let's say if I want to look for content type mp, 4, right, we can upload that and then backtrack when the alert on how the alert sees it, and then we can add it into this thing. 

Speaker 4  (27:21)
Yeah, because we go up a blend of that and the true file type thing that a lot of things 

Speaker 2  (27:26)
Yeah, and when you use this content type, it's the mime type. I mean it'll always be like a PDF would be application PDF, where it would be, you know, application, whatever the, you know, from that that's like, a plane types would be a text, image and image so that's how it's identified s***. Yeah? 

Speaker 6  (27:47)
Yeah, okay, that means I get that. Okay, cool, thanks. 

Speaker 4  (27:51)
Right? Like you're right. Stop sharing. 

Speaker 3  (27:57)
Before I continue, I just want to give a few minutes to ask a question for the rest of the team like a Chad, do you have anything to bring to the band there or 

Speaker 2  (28:09)
Can I can I add one thing, Howard? If you don't mind 

Speaker 3  (28:12)
Sure, go ahead and go, ahe. 

Speaker 2  (28:16)
So there's also a field where you can filter by and again, just my recommendation for you guys to have an exploration saved for this, but you can also that realm setting filter that we discussed, that's not gonna show you when the content analyzer fails due to some issue, maybe on our end, right? Like a connectivity error or something like that, I would recommend you also have some tracking for when just just for you know, the agent health, the content analyzer health, you have an exploration saved, where you are also looking at all of The Times that the content scanner fails due to like an internal error I would also recommend having something. 

Speaker 2  (29:02)
Like that so you guys can track it and make sure there's not too many instances where the content analyzer is just failing for. You know, no reason at all. Otherwise we're going to have nothing good for that one. 

Speaker 4  (29:11)
That's a good point. Harris, denying to cut you off, I was just going to see a sense right here. Should we just do that? 

Speaker 4  (29:19)
Because Yeah, yes. 

Speaker 2  (29:22)
Easy enough. So, if you want to save this exploration, if you want to give it a different name, and just do internal content, scanning errors or something like that, I think it's saved us like web upload right now. Yeah 

Speaker 4  (29:35)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (29:35)
Yeah, if you want to just put like internal or internal content, scanning errors like and then parentheses like, fail bye by. 

Speaker 6  (29:43)
Well, I think this will override the Web applode. Why you can script the webload on that's fine. 

Speaker 4  (29:48)
Yeah, you know. 

Speaker 2  (29:49)
Or even created, you won, I mean, whatever whatever season or yeah, just do it without Steven. Yeah 

Speaker 4  (29:55)
Okay, we'll do 7 days. 

Speaker 2  (30:03)
So it's probably not going to show anything now, but you can still add the field if you type in params value. So par am S Yeah, so do that events, Param value, and if you go to observed value, that's not going to show anything. I assume that it's not like it hasn't failed yet, but you will see, like connectivity error there's like a couple different error codes. 

Speaker 2  (30:29)
So this this, if you just save this right. And you could check back, this will show you the instances where there's like a 4000 error or any type of error here, right? So this should actually show Z oh well. 

Speaker 2  (30:44)
Yeah, this is just showing all for now. Okay, do me a favor open this filter again. Okay, yeah, edit this filter and go to observe values. 

Speaker 2  (31:00)
Oh, it doesn't even let you add the 

Speaker 4  (31:03)
Values, letters here, type text in toddfield values. 

Speaker 2  (31:07)
Yeah, well, once it's observed, it'll show up here, but usually there's a button that will allow you to do like show values that okay, it's not been observed. Go to change filter. I wonder if there's one under the yeah, type that in again, params, there might be a parame's key there. 

Speaker 2  (31:23)
Yeah, do a pairam's key. Does that let you add events that haven't been seen yet? Oh, yeah, okay. 

Speaker 2  (31:31)
So it would be like, yeah, this is gonna be tough. So you keep an eye on this, and once it does fail, right, click on click on the message one I just want to see what that is the analyzer. That's the encrypted file. 

Speaker 2  (31:45)
That's fine. You know, we already have something separate to monitor that one, but if you go to, yeah, click done here. I want to see what this one is. 

Speaker 2  (31:54)
Is this the same thing? Is it just showing the message? 

Speaker 6  (31:58)
I think it'll be the 

Speaker 2  (32:01)
Yeah, so that's an amazing day of this for now, we need to see an incidence of the analyzer, failing, which it will inevitably do at some point, right, it's not often, but there's gonna be like a point where there's like a connectivity or something like that, it'll fail. So once it fails, there'll be an observed value there, done that will show you like connectivity error like there's a there's a couple different errors that will show up there. So once those 

Speaker 4  (32:29)
Should I save it like this? But this params key, instead of value. 

Speaker 2  (32:33)
Yeah, you could, I think they basically show the same, but go to value. It's a more readable format. When you put it in value, you can't select any custom value. 

Speaker 2  (32:41)
So it's just gonna show all there. 

Speaker 6  (32:45)
Also, if you like Oh, sorry, gon. 

Speaker 8  (32:49)
Sorry, don't drop. How have you tried the events type? 

Speaker 1  (32:53)
Under intern. 

Speaker 2  (32:55)
I've tried that events type that one just like hasn't always worked. 

Speaker 3  (33:03)
The way 

Speaker 8  (33:04)
I think if we check the absorbed values under there, we might be able to find those that we are looking for. 

Speaker 2  (33:11)
Oh, just as like a non observed value. Okay, yeah, let's let's check it out, so if you wanna change the filter to the yeah, change it to that. And see if we can add those So edited this filter again, though. 

Speaker 4  (33:25)
If we're just gonna make a new one okay? 

Speaker 2  (33:29)
And the field is actions, reason actions type. She gave 

Speaker 8  (33:36)
So yeah, if you click on that and type internal 

Speaker 4  (33:39)
In terms of analysts, X Okay? So I am 

Speaker 8  (33:45)
Yeah, go to topdam. Go to events type 

Speaker 1  (33:48)
He believes it's 

Speaker 2  (33:52)
And okay to go to show, do show results with no activities on the left, right under results. Here. 

Speaker 8  (34:05)
Yeah, so you might be able to drill down 

Speaker 2  (34:11)
Type an error here. Yeah, there we go okay. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (34:20)
So yeah, we can. Yeah, we can. I mean, you can basically select all of these errors here. 

Speaker 2  (34:27)
Like the content scanning error when that actually happens, there will be different error codes within the little window itself. That shows you, and there's a corresponding document that has like a description of all of those error codes. So yeah, this is just something to keep an eye on, I doubt you'll see anything here in like the near future, but just a recommendation, I do like to set this up for customers just so they can monitor when stuff is failing right? 

Speaker 2  (34:53)
Because you guys have a lot of licenses. So Not having a dedicated like save to the fails, is there's really no other indicator that's going to tell you unless you're looking at all the activities, right? So yeah. 

Speaker 2  (35:08)
Okay. Okay. Yeah, so I'll make a note of this done. 

Speaker 2  (35:11)
Maybe we can, you know, revisit this in like a couple weeks and see if anything populated in here? Okay. Thank you, all right, sorry, Howard. 

Speaker 2  (35:20)
You had something or I meant. 

Speaker 4  (35:26)
All right, if you wanna take over the screenshot I can't. The control is disappeared premiere. 

Speaker 3  (35:31)
No, it wasn't. I wasn't in a chair. A couple of things Harry's. 

Speaker 3  (35:37)
If you can send me the lease of the IPS that we talk about earlier this week for the splank stuff that we need right. I don't know if you train something I haven't received yet or I haven't seen it yeah. Yeah, the other question that we have for you, we are getting ready to move from Pat, sorry from depth to path. 

Speaker 3  (36:01)
The question that we have, is you guys mentioned at some point that you guys will be able to migrate what we have in one tenant to another tenant. What will it take for you guys to initiate the migration of everything that is custom, in the QA environment to path we're talking about, you know, detectors, data classifiers. Well, I want it to take to make that happen. 

Speaker 3  (36:27)
How long will it take? 

Speaker 2  (36:28)
So there's really nothing you guys need to do for that. It's just really, whenever you guys are ready to start that there's like a script we can run in the back end that will just move everything over. So I guess like once everything's built out and you let us know. 

Speaker 2  (36:44)
I don't know if you've worked with Mike golden but he wrote the script to migrate all this stuff over. So I know you mentioned this early on. So we met with him, we made sure that the script is gonna work, how you guys needed to, and it's going to move everything over so that's just a matter of you, letting us know when you're ready, and we'll discordinate with Mike and either he can do it. 

Speaker 2  (37:03)
In the back end, you know, on his own, or if you guys, you know, want to set up a call and do it live with him. You know, we could do that as well, but it's nothing that you guys would need to do, Howard, you guys would just need to make sure everything is that in your you know, in the test tenant, obviously you can create more once you get to the on the new tenant, but yeah, whenever you guys are ready, just let us know. 

Speaker 3  (37:26)
Okay, so let me ask you this question, let's say we do an update next week, and then we keep working on debt on the debt environment, can we rerun the scripts? So all the new dates from debt can actually get moved to bad. The reason why I'm asking is because, right now, we? 

Speaker 3  (37:42)
Don 't have email in Deb right and what we have in path is not enough for us to actually conduct all the email tests, right. So I would like to get all this data classifiers, and take the system of the past so I can actually conduct all the stuff that I need to do on. The email side, while the guys finalized the policies, the empire policies on the debt side. 

Speaker 3  (38:07)
Yeah, is that an option that we can actually do that the first sink, and then we just do another sink in the future to sing, whatever updates they made. 

Speaker 2  (38:16)
I mean, the thing I don't see why I don't see why it wouldn't be right. I mean I know there is some effort on his hand like just some data he needs to pull from the back end on your tenant to run the script, but I don't imagine that would you know, be an issue you're saying, if we migrate everything. Now you guys continue to work in, Dev, you add some stuff that's that's new. 

Speaker 2  (38:38)
If we could just rerun the script for you and move everything over again. Yeah, let me double-check on that. I don't just from, you know, top of mind, I don't see why that would be an issue. 

Speaker 2  (38:49)
But yeah, I mean I could I can confirm 

Speaker 3  (38:52)
Okay, perfect. So if it's possible, I would like to have a single done next week. The thermal, so you can need a ticket from me or but it's So, can you say that again? 

Speaker 2  (39:07)
But he said, you want to have the stuff moved over next week. 

Speaker 3  (39:11)
Yes, if it's possible. 

Speaker 2  (39:13)
Okay, let me I don't wanna commit to that just now Howard, because I know July 4th next week, like a lot of people are out of office so I just need to confirm that he's gonna be here and that he'll be able to do it. But I mean, if not next week, I think the week after should be fine. 

Speaker 3  (39:29)
I put that perfect. Yeah, not like some pressure, but 

Speaker 2  (39:35)
Yeah, let me, let me reach out to him and talk to him and see, like, what is availability? Availability? Looks like, and when I mean, I'll let him know like that, you know, as soon as possible, essentially. 

Speaker 2  (39:46)
But let me get back to you on that just because it's another resource who's not on the call, and you know, I don't know what his schedule is like off the top of my mind. So either next week, or the week, after, I think should be good. 

Speaker 3  (39:58)
Okay, perfect. And I don't want to put that additional pressure, but we're thinking of going into a pile of more in August, right so any any any any additional time that we can get to test that would be great right? But if we have to be a week or 2, it is what it is. 

Speaker 3  (40:16)
Right? I know the question. We, as you know, we also working on the email side right? 

Speaker 3  (40:25)
Did you have the ability to also migrate? What we're doing on the email side to to the to the production pod, or do we have to do that manually? 

Speaker 9  (40:38)
Harriet Harris is awesome talk to Dan Wheeler. The other consultant that's doing the threat protection or coordinating with Daniel, and Anya, we can migrate the rules. 

Speaker 2  (40:53)
The DLP rules nev or 

Speaker 9  (40:56)
Everything everything from the yeah, so there's only a similar process for the the sag. They'll make sense that they also do the dlp side. So okay, okay? 

Speaker 3  (41:11)
So I'm guessing, because Yeah, we're trying to do certain things in a different way, but based on my understanding of how the pots work, we actually hearkening IPS, like what we allow when we actually redirect traffic at those platies are going to probably pass empty when we move when you get from the sink, or there will be moved with the paddy. E! Parameters are something we will have to make the judgments once the information gets moved. 

Speaker 9  (41:43)
Any right, there's going to be constraints like we'll be able to migrate the rules, but you may need to, you will need to rules that reference, like IP addresses that are specific for Pat, you'll need to modify it, so the rules themselves structure, the rules will be there, but you'll definitely need to go back and update your policy routes update like, you know, also I would imagine like the group names will be different, so it's there's still effort, but at least some of the structure of the rules will be able to be migrated over. 

Speaker 3  (42:17)
Okay, perfect another question around the email we noticed that when the emails, so let's say I have an email policy and I send an email to the user saying, hey, we block you, right, I noticed that the email basically is coming from a proof point email, and it's being flagged as an external email. Between that banner, can we change the email that it gets used? Okay? 

Speaker 3  (42:46)
Yeah, and 

Speaker 9  (42:49)
It wind up being obvious, you have to do the classic interface. There's S MP profiles, and you could change the from address and so forth. But yeah, you have to log into the classic interface to do it. 

Speaker 9  (43:02)
Hygienic s*** perfectly quickly. 

Speaker 3  (43:06)
Perfect. Yeah, if you could do that, it's not going to affect anything else from the running perspective, or anything else that we look at the emos suspicious that we're aware of one thing. I Don' 

Speaker 9  (43:16)
I want you to discuss is let's say a notification message is generated on dlp. It can be configured to send a notification message back directly from dlp, or should it go through like the to the gateway and back at round so that's like some to discuss what Daniel on how notification messages should flow, like, for example, today you have like a seg on Prem right should I go? Should the seg on Prem accept messages from dlp or do they prefer that dlp? 

Speaker 9  (43:54)
Send the message to the seg like the pod seg and then back through 

Speaker 3  (44:01)
Yeah, we need to have a conversation because that's the other thing that I notice, right? The images are being flagged as an external, and it has that big, ugly banner, that we have right saying, this is this. 

Speaker 1  (44:12)
To see from the outside 

Speaker 3  (44:13)
And people will look at their suspicions. Just ignore a complaint 

Speaker 1  (44:17)
Lilly's right. 

Speaker 3  (44:18)
Pizza, I know. 

Speaker 9  (44:21)
Go ahead, sir. No, no, if you go that path, obviously we could, we would. We would disable the banner, like propoid has its own banner. 

Speaker 9  (44:27)
We would not. We would have like a policy route to Bypass the Banner For Messages Coming from That Source. So if either path works, it's just what's your preference? 

Speaker 1  (44:39)
Okay, perfect, so I'll check to Daniel about and see how we wanna do this. Another thing that I want to show you is when I was configuring the pod, I got rid of the feeds. I got rid of a whole bunch of stuff, and I tried setting up one of those. 

Speaker 1  (44:56)
Disclosures, or banners, when somebody log in and the formatting that I'm getting on the screen is not the graders, and then trying to share my screen in a second. I was wondering how you guys deal with this, or what sort of recommendations in your second? Can I turn the screen? 

Speaker 1  (45:17)
Maybe Chair, so you see how it turned off everything like you guys used to have a feet on everything here turned it off and then I put a message here, but you see doesn't do the greatest like I will probably have. I would like to have this somewhere around here like I using this section of the screen. But it's basically puts everything here at the bottom, and people doesn't see that right. 

Speaker 1  (45:41)
And it's like a you know, that great bridge color instead of wait to actually customize this, it shows in a different place, and it shows like a in red. 

Speaker 9  (45:53)
No, but one of the things that you probably saw is you could do the banner when you get in to be a different color I think right now it's green, that is in our feet and keep in mind too, we are looking at moving away from this interface. So yeah, so then I don't see much traction in this this, that our feet 

Speaker 4  (46:19)
It heard, did you just paste this as text or was it like HTML? 

Speaker 1  (46:24)
I was tax. 

Speaker 4  (46:26)
Okay. I was thinking of as an HTML. You could use the tags for color or something, but I guess not. 

Speaker 1  (46:33)
Yeah, I didn't try that. I didn't know if he supports hdl code or anything like that. Hi, I could give it a bit a try, but I maybe play with a formatting, but, you know, I see that big space right here, that's what I want you to hear. 

Speaker 4  (46:49)
Right? Yeah? 

Speaker 9  (46:50)
We usually have announcements, which is weird, you don't see it? You usually, yeah, that'll be like RSS faith for like our updates, so we use that space. 

Speaker 1  (47:02)
Yeah, but I drink that often again, nope by letting to see that and ham and I am, this is good. All right, let me ask another question. How do we restrict this interface to to the I? 

Speaker 1  (47:16)
Ps. Or what's your recommendation like, how we log this down? So all the people from the outside doesn't get to this login screen. 

Speaker 9  (47:27)
You can't under a host firewall. There is a setting to uh U block it down, let me 

Speaker 1  (47:38)
I aint a lot of kids looking in the second yeah, I mean, I mean I cannot say. 

Speaker 1  (47:57)
Oh, before I forget, we found a big issue. When the messaging guys are Logan, to the new interface, I mean, they're performing the come, even though they're restricted with the role not to see Delp stuff, they're able to. I'm I don't know if because they have um U. 

Speaker 1  (48:19)
Man that when he fly. 

Speaker 9  (48:21)
So deep in mind, encryption is done here, so they can see the information protection tab, but they won't see the rules. 

Speaker 1  (48:32)
No, they were able to see everything I actually jump on a call with Danny and he was able to see every single day. 

Speaker 2  (48:37)
Alright, I'm just in a face or art. 

Speaker 9  (48:40)
For the cloud Admin and the cloud Admin, we could talk about that one. 

Speaker 1  (48:44)
He was a cloud at me, he was able to see everything. 

Speaker 9  (48:46)
From the weak, we could fix that that that's something that maybe Daniel could bring up in the next working session, or we can, I can go through that with how to fix it. But here, if they click on information protection, they'll only see encryption, which is what's expected. Yeah, I' 

Speaker 1  (49:03)
Yeah, from the other console, they can see everything they have a drop down. They know they can click on awkward. 

Speaker 3  (49:07)
On our pod, or I would tend to 

Speaker 1  (49:09)
And then you can click on everything every single thing, even though don't destrict it. Yeah, seen it. Yeah Hi, going back to the restriction on the council. 

Speaker 1  (49:21)
So And I'm guessing, I'm going to system then settings 

Speaker 4  (49:27)
Oh, it's 

Speaker 9  (49:28)
Admins, maybe they move right, okay, I see the mind interface. 

Speaker 1  (49:41)
Yeah, because ID went over this section right like this, you can see this is where I put a stuff here I'll address it, so I'm guessing it's there. 

Speaker 9  (49:50)
How are they lost specifically? 

Speaker 1  (49:54)
Do you know if they support rankes? Or 

Speaker 9  (49:59)
But II believe they do. You should be able to put like A Yeah, sorry location. 

Speaker 3  (50:11)
Okay, so I just need to get all the piece from the proof point. Sorry, from the next cup guys, I'm dumping here and that should do it for us. 

Speaker 9  (50:18)
Yeah, because check with Daniel, I assume they probably have already done this, so just check what they've already put. 

Speaker 1  (50:25)
Ok. 

Speaker 2  (50:26)
All right, so we're just at about time here Howard, so I gotta jump here to another call, but I just wanted to let you know, that AV exclusion justifications that you requested. I know, it was a little you've been waiting a little bit for those, but we do have like an updated response. From our product and engineering team, so we will share that with you and I also brought up the safe list for the IPS, I'm just bringing it to the top of your mailbox here and I'll send it to you in a minute. 

Speaker 1  (51:00)
Okay, perfect, thank you, appreci. 

Speaker 2  (51:03)
Yeah, absolutely. All right, guys, I'm I think yeah, I think we we have next week canceled, but I'll be in office on Wednesday and Thursday, I do have some calls. But I mean, if anybody is working. 

Speaker 2  (51:20)
Oh I think you guys are well, you guys are off on Wednesday. Well, anyway, if you guys have questions, reach out to the team and uh, U. We'll go back to you. 

Speaker 3  (51:28)
Yeah, definitely, I will have some questions because I'm planning to try to get the integration done within the next and the following week, right? And I do want to try some of these indie groups so I might have some questions around the policy and exclusions and compound conditions and stuff. 

Speaker 2  (51:47)
All right, sounds a good hour. All right, guys, have a good weekend bye bye. 

Speaker 1  (51:51)
Hi, thank you guys again. Thank you 

Speaker 6  (51:54)
Yeah, I' 

Speaker 10  (54:05)
America with Bossa and Zelda qat 

Speaker 10  (01:00:02)
I'm 

Speaker 10  (01:00:41)
Yeah, I' 
