
Speaker 1  (00:11)
All right. Good afternoon, everyone. So I'm sharing the screen, and so I guess, do you wanna start from top to bottom bottom to top middle to whatever. 

Speaker 2  (00:29)
Yeah, I' 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
Oh, yeah, all right. Do you have notes key, just sending your notes, Howard? 

Speaker 2  (00:34)
Um, there's no more subjugation, a lot of people work. I can tell you that all the altitude breakers are completed, right? Ok, okay. 

Speaker 2  (00:42)
Okay, cool, all right, I can tell you that we set up the EDM server. We went around on firewall rules to be completed so that we're starting, we get some sessions with the ESPN so we didn't move much with the ESPN side we found more issues then solutions Okay, okay? So okay. 

Speaker 2  (01:06)
And we continue the policy work. We studied the policies on the ESPN side and with a little bit of push. And this is just my selfish goal. 

Speaker 2  (01:18)
We're hoping that we will complete all the policies in that next Friday. That's my third selfish goal. So Okay? 

Speaker 2  (01:27)
But I mean That's what I have, unfortunately. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
No, that's good. Okay. All right, I made note of all that. 

Speaker 1  (01:34)
So why don't we maybe just do a quick rundown and just to make sure that we're, I guess everybody's in sync, and With the varying goals while we can finish up in 30 minutes today. Okay, so the ther the terrors are done anything over here with architecture chat. I added from last week, added the threat model story. 

Speaker 3  (01:58)
Yeah, chart model is still in progress. So I just haven't wrapped it, because like the Azure stuff is still in there, and it's just not totally wrapped app and kind of just giving it a little bit more time, but no worries, there, it'll be it'll be done when we need it done. 

Speaker 1  (02:12)
Okay, so the so this is in fact in progress. Yeah All right. Let me just change that. 

Speaker 1  (02:17)
Come on. Okay, here we go in progress. And I put it a start date of last week. 

Speaker 1  (02:26)
Any any any due date or Not important right now. 

Speaker 3  (02:33)
I Don'. 

Speaker 1  (02:34)
Okay, and I put a note in here from last week as well. In regards to I mentioned That That if your architecture design was issued the certificate, however, it's not published pending the scale process. Yeah, okay, good, all right, so that's architecture. 

Speaker 1  (02:55)
Nta, yeah, go. 

Speaker 2  (02:57)
Yeah, so just one question about that this scale process, what's the next step with that sorry? 

Speaker 1  (03:06)
Good, can we Dave's going to join in a few minutes? Maybe we can 

Speaker 2  (03:10)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (03:12)
Yep, yeah, not norse. Well, I got that flag to bring up to Dave. Okay, so I'll mark the L2 records as done as you mentioned Howard. 

Speaker 1  (03:23)
I can't remember if we, if we put any evidence in the last one or we just 

Speaker 2  (03:30)
I will put evidence I have, so I will catch the same. Yeah, working work Okay, sounds good. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (03:38)
And I think the next step after they helped to records is go through the nti process, which basically is going to give us that certification right? 

Speaker 1  (03:47)
Yeah, yeah, and there's a whole bunch of Stories and tasks to do in that Do you want to set? Do you want me to set app a session to go through some of the stuff or We made some other stuff that was probably done right. The internet I don't think maybe the suburb intake requests might have been done already. 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
This is definitely The 1B risk mark oh actually no not true. We have diesel, but 

Speaker 2  (04:15)
We didn't, we didn't went into this risk marketplace stuff. Yeah, I would say it will require the call, so we can just focus on the ntii attempts and update what it was needed. But I don't think we should have next week, like I really want to focus on the solution next week like I Don'. 

Speaker 2  (04:34)
Right, like I want to move, I stop all the skulls and actually focus on work. So um yeah. So I would say, no, no, no next week. 

Speaker 2  (04:42)
Please 

Speaker 1  (04:43)
Yeah, no worries. So Yeah, no I hear you. We could spend a lot of time on process. 

Speaker 1  (04:51)
Okay, scale, we'll circle back to scale. Again, when this shows up policies, I think 

Speaker 2  (05:02)
That's still part of the same scale process, right? So let's keep this for now. 

Speaker 1  (05:06)
Yeah, okay, sure, should I move this into a story then within the scale process, I think that was my question here. 

Speaker 2  (05:14)
I would say so, but until we get confirmation, just like we hear like, we need to have a formal confirmation of what scale is going to do better. 

Speaker 1  (05:22)
Oh, okay, alright. So 

Speaker 2  (05:23)
It doesn't hardly keep it. 

Speaker 1  (05:25)
Dear all right, well, we won't lose sight of it here. That's for sure. Okay, external blobs storage configuration. 

Speaker 1  (05:33)
Okay, that's all part of 

Speaker 2  (05:37)
The differential, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (05:38)
Yeah, chance that's there, okay, this one here, so this had to do I guess with The Peter conversation the other day. So It sounds like we had the design, at least as far as it's going to go. And then the next steps Are the I believe the eyebrows have happen? 

Speaker 1  (05:59)
I looked at you're probably more familiar with this process. 

Speaker 2  (06:09)
I'm not sure if it's sound lead or architect. 

Speaker 1  (06:14)
Now, I was told by Dixon, he gets he gets involved I believe. That estimation. 

Speaker 2  (06:23)
I'll give the spot in the I bone process, okay. Okay? 

Speaker 3  (06:27)
Yeah, there's call today, right? This was with Peter. Like a Pant, and all that, and then pig leads to ibumbl. 

Speaker 2  (06:37)
Okay, so if they did sign like, that's, that's Peter, okay, perfect opec. 

Speaker 1  (06:40)
Okay, well, what's a what's AD ER? His name? 

Speaker 2  (06:46)
I think that's where they go unapproved, they design, whatever he comes up with, don't ask me what it means, but he has to go to their approval and to look at the diagrams and everything, and make sure he makes sense. And that's where H design something radio, yeah. So I don't know what they use for. 

Speaker 1  (07:02)
Okay, mount norres, so after the eye bomb that the thist Does it go through like purchasing procurement type thing or 

Speaker 2  (07:12)
No, I think that's the bill after there is a proof it goes into bill, and then they pull everything from another I bomb configuration if I'm mistaking. 

Speaker 1  (07:24)
Okay, okay, cause it's all virtual, yes, correct, right? Oh yeah, okay, okay, okay. Okay, just curious, all right, I'm not sure if I have the order in here, but we have Well, they're the ARE that's That's if it's required by the P DL. 

Speaker 1  (07:54)
And there's a checklist for the pdl engagement. Howard, I think I forward that to you. So I think somewhat well at the price start looking at that the next week or 2, right? 

Speaker 2  (08:06)
But don't we have arrayed somebody from the I team, or do we still regret at the L? My understanding was that if we have a problem manager, we Don 't need AP. B. 

Speaker 2  (08:15)
L. I'm not sure yeah, I would normally go to pdl away if I don't have a prod going that was my understanding, but uh yeah. And I'll see these ways 

Speaker 1  (08:32)
Okay, yeah, so we do have we do have somebody who's engaged Dixon? Which was yeah, part of that chat that we did today yesterday? Yeah, so he's looking for that. 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
That's right. He's using, he's looking for that information to I guess gauge himself for 

Speaker 2  (08:46)
Famous, what he's eating at, so we don't eat this. Or we can just update 

Speaker 1  (08:52)
And if we need, I think we need to checklist, though, right? Yeah, yes, yeah, yeah 

Speaker 2  (08:57)
Okay, he's gonna come back with some estimate Lagarde, like a brown dollar, so type of thing, and we just add into this, and how much it's going to cost them to come out with all the different setups, and how they're going to help us. 

Speaker 1  (09:10)
Yeah, and so So I'd sent you this list here, and this is the I couldn' He used a splunk as a sample. I don't know if you've opened it yet or not but ugh. 

Speaker 2  (09:25)
Yeah, I remember you and I talking about these sorry. Yeah. All right, go ahead. 

Speaker 2  (09:39)
Hope the dogs are okay. 

Speaker 1  (09:42)
Yeah, okay. Yeah, so Yeah, unfortunately, we don't have sprints to flag this for you, but um, yeah, yeah, I' Okay, so we've got that in your queue, right? I do. 

Speaker 1  (09:59)
Yeah, okay. Okay, I'm not sure about all these steps, and you can help me with the order a bit, and then I added the Pat the Dr. and the F. 

Speaker 1  (10:15)
It was jet net provided that But at the moment, we're okay with the way this stands and sure I'm 

Speaker 2  (10:26)
Yes, it's fine. The only Trinity matter is just in fact also the end of the day. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 1  (10:33)
All right. Anything on this Fernando needs to update on it. 

Speaker 4  (10:49)
So at the moment, so I have to lower my microphone. Yes, I submitted the request. I work with tall where it created a change request, and And so many others are requested as W I'm team to promote this to Pat. 

Speaker 4  (11:05)
I'm They will be working on it. Hopefully this weekend mid next week, so it should be done by mid next week. 

Speaker 1  (11:16)
Okay, answer requires a change of cross. Second we've got mid next week. Okay, so there's really no up, okay? 

Speaker 1  (11:22)
So the updates and here are fine, correct? 

Speaker 4  (11:26)
Process requires a change request. 

Speaker 1  (11:28)
Okay, so that was okay. Yeah, okay, so change for change requests made it during 

Speaker 4  (11:33)
Change regards a minute. Yeah. I'm waiting for work to be completed. 

Speaker 4  (11:39)
From the whimt team 

Speaker 4  (11:56)
Okay? And you can put another thing. Maybe another line once the change is completed, I will validate the second reproduction second will validate the integration and test. 

Speaker 4  (12:14)
The symbolic behavior integration 

Speaker 2  (12:35)
Ice cream sticking. 

Speaker 1  (12:40)
It doesn't matter. Go back later. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (12:45)
It's funny. He doesn't pick up spelling mistakes, okay? Thank you, and this one here. 

Speaker 1  (13:00)
Not started yet, quite for EPS pn. 

Speaker 4  (13:05)
We have not started that, because I think we're going to go to with the unified piece here. Because dspm and dp DPE ML. They all use a unify, sso. 

Speaker 4  (13:24)
Or are we going to go with t The individual for the ESPN. And db eml Oh, sorry, I might think I Don'. 

Speaker 2  (13:34)
I think you're mixed, so in a fire will be 

Speaker 4  (13:38)
I was looking at the 460, aint. 

Speaker 2  (13:42)
468, so 468, is emails itself, so that's gonna be unified. If 

Speaker 4  (13:49)
So we're very dependent on we have to work with the email team as well, right? It's not just us. 

Speaker 2  (13:56)
That is correct, so that's just because that integration, and you know how we actually did that set up the other day when things can move to the new Admin, that when they come, because that's part of the unifying setup. So that's We have to use that email would be the only thing that's going to unify everything else should be. We should be able to recycle the same as the circumfiguration that we did for death. 

Speaker 4  (14:20)
Yeah, so is that technically the only one that is going to use the individualist? Dp sec, right. 

Speaker 2  (14:28)
No, no, the peml does only say one that's going to be just unify. Everything else should be going through that is source, that's right. 

Speaker 4  (14:37)
Okay, so I'll okay. Ok? DBS PMS So having started there. 

Speaker 4  (14:57)
I'll start working on it tomorrow. 

Speaker 1  (14:59)
Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (15:00)
It's right to say dspm itm and dp sec, all have independent, like ssl individual 

Speaker 2  (15:09)
No, no, no, they're gonna be just in the singer. It's the same registration, the sends it up and it's gonna be checked among the 3 apps. And that's what the guy was telling us, Brian dudle. 

Speaker 2  (15:21)
So we don't have to go and sit up separate as itself for each of them, like these, the same groups. It's the same people, right? We just keep adding more. 

Speaker 4  (15:30)
That's great, great memory, Howard, yes We're going to add it, we're going to use, we're going to recycle the same. Uh U. And try the application Written are different carburols for the different applications and we use the same enterprise application. 

Speaker 4  (15:47)
Yes There will be individual integrations. There won't be used in the unified, but yes, that's correct. 

Speaker 3  (15:59)
They're individual, but they have a shared component. 

Speaker 4  (16:03)
Actually, a component and the share anddr.ID application 

Speaker 1  (16:06)
Okay, that's exactly 

Speaker 3  (16:08)
Then, the pp email is separate, that's on its own, that's on its own. Yes, using what they call the unified way. But that's the only one to unify, correct. 

Speaker 3  (16:18)
F*** cool, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (16:28)
So I think you mentioned At the ESPN Policy is this one is a dp sacred, or is it today we need another 

Speaker 2  (16:39)
Yeah, we probably need one for the ESPN. 

Speaker 1  (16:42)
Ok, alright, so just copy it from From B.P sec or whatever, yeah. Yeah, okay, let me just have a look to see what's wrong then. Okay, so it'd just be these 2 stories, and both of them are done for The ESPN correct. 

Speaker 2  (17:06)
Plus some other policies go back, and then policy migration jumped up exactly. 

Speaker 1  (17:10)
Okay, all right, I'll take care of that. Okay, EDM, I think you mentioned that EDM servers are set up. Yep, so the so that's done here, okay. 

Speaker 2  (17:25)
Pending, a firewall implementation, okay. I could give you the firework roll. Now if you if you if you liked it. 

Speaker 2  (17:40)
Sorry, trying to look for that master fornasio. You won the number. There are a few kids who bring it. 

Speaker 4  (17:50)
I'll throw it in the chat here. 

Speaker 2  (17:57)
And maybe we want to be specific, this isn't that right? We haven't done pad yet, we just this is 

Speaker 1  (18:03)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I made that assumption. 

Speaker 2  (18:07)
Awesome, thank you, okay. 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
By the way, are you okay doing a market done 

Speaker 2  (18:15)
Otherwise I Don' 

Speaker 1  (18:18)
Yeah, okay, cool, cool. Cool. All right, so I'll just change the date until next week. 

Speaker 2  (18:25)
So Chad, now that we're talking about data, let me, I don't know if you've read the commutation, so dcdm requires us, we pass a specific seal, like man and we actually pass credential, Disneyland password. 

Speaker 4  (18:42)
And plain tax. 

Speaker 3  (18:46)
What's that the thing I saw that email about the Amo? Boards that haven't really been 

Speaker 2  (18:53)
I'm not sure what it's saying, but we've been complaining, I have a lot of stuff, but one of those many minutes isn'. Yeah, but it's simply takes, and what I was telling the guys in the previous call is that We could probably kind of mask the glaciers and decode them at AR. As we draw on the command very, like, if we can probably set up the job to have this in like I don't know, encode it with X basically 4 or whatever, but technically, that's just a false sense of security. 

Speaker 2  (19:18)
Right? Be, they cut it easily, right? I don't know how he's going to look for the security perspective. 

Speaker 2  (19:25)
We're going to give a slide. But over the next, you know, somebody needs to be aware of this, but letting you know, when they get this appropriate. Unfortunately, this, after wrong, we need to go. 

Speaker 2  (19:36)
Clarijis and a new batchwork. 

Speaker 3  (19:38)
Just so I make like, I don't want to get confused because there's so many things going on is there do you have like a link to their doc like a like, whatever this specific topic is that I can catch up 

Speaker 2  (19:47)
Make sure I got the dog out. I'll send it to you right now. 

Speaker 4  (19:55)
Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (19:57)
Okay, I was gonna be into hinting, so I wouldn't say well. 

Speaker 4  (20:01)
Oh, just throw it out. Joining this chat right again. 

Speaker 2  (20:06)
I'm going to try the chat, hang on in a second. What was the name of my faults? Or Bitcoin EDM client. 

Speaker 3  (20:18)
Before you know, apply, just letting me know myself. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (20:23)
Okay, so I was going in the chart now. So don't let me stop if we can move to the next item wall. I send this to the guy so yeah. 

Speaker 2  (20:32)
So yeah. Okay, you should get a chat now. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (20:36)
So actually, we do have the DSP M It's like, yeah, okay. Yeah, it was there so 

Speaker 3  (20:47)
It started. 

Speaker 2  (20:49)
Policy dragon is completed is done I already signed people now it's been an implementation. 

Speaker 1  (20:58)
Okay, so it's done up till 391. 

Speaker 2  (21:05)
No, no, no, there's no setup configuration tracker, right? So police tracker is just documenting and doing things. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (21:15)
Maybe this part we will fix it the next time. But I'm 

Speaker 1  (21:21)
Parking clean enough. Now I just I can change this to documentation, and this one is initially set up in testing which you've done right, that's so 3 92 3 92 is done. 

Speaker 2  (21:32)
No train editors were spending the documentation and the tracking of the commentation is gone okay, track 

Speaker 1  (21:40)
So why don't I just I just changed the stand. I'll take a second. Okay, so see. 

Speaker 1  (21:49)
So I can get rid of these things here, and I just say tracking Ain'. 

Speaker 2  (21:56)
It's augmentation, and want to do that so Chad, the documentation of the synthetic about you name a batchword through the cli we figured out, as we were running the test that requires authentication, but basically from page at least 6 or 7, we say the inclined tool, you're going to see the commands, right and that's where we had to pass the credentials. 

Speaker 3  (22:26)
And when you put them in, it saves them into a file. No 

Speaker 2  (22:29)
Now it just stays out on the screen, you don't have anything you could just see them as part of the seal. Like man 

Speaker 4  (22:37)
I just wonder how has that been transmitted? Weather Honestly, however, I like to understand how it's how is that being passed if it's using a coral command. I'm with the - H. 

Speaker 4  (22:54)
Meaning that it's fascinating the header, because it's fascinating in the header doesn't know now, how is that being transmitted to proof point, because I know it's bhtps, so that's going to be encrypted at the time of issuing the command so I just want to do. We have a wire shark on those on those machines. That we can take a quick capture, take a basket capture, and I understand and that way, I can understand how is that, how is that being transmitted on the wire? 

Speaker 4  (23:26)
Because yeah, you do. You The only piece I'm worried about is that the automation piece, the wrong come Fick. It does ask you to store the username and password. 

Speaker 4  (23:39)
But again, you can limit that welcome fake Not do specific users, not not not a specific group. That can read that correct. So we can secure it that way, right? 

Speaker 4  (23:57)
But in terms of the of the CI They see the cli needs to be around manually, right? 

Speaker 2  (24:07)
Hi, it could be scripted as well, right? But you have to have all the conditions in place which chat if it fit the right purpose? 

Speaker 4  (24:14)
If you ascript it, then we can really, we can't really script this, because you're gonna have to put the username in A It's part of the script on plane text. Is that what you're calling out, correct? 

Speaker 3  (24:26)
If you have more metric, there that may account for it because then you can limit even if someone's loved into the server, they have to be in the right group to view that file like to decrypt it and read it so potentially, there's an option there of like allowing the right, but there's some work to do, and then that's only problem one and you're right. The problem 2 is now that you've given it the password, how is it transmitting all that stuff over the wire? Is it? 

Speaker 3  (24:52)
Yeah, so okay, let me read up on that. I'll see if I can plant Al. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (25:01)
What we can say is I run, run wire shots server and and look at the lyr. At the package and figure out how they're doing. 

Speaker 2  (25:13)
Yeah, sumida, and I hope Rick worse to To have the software guys to push wiretag to the server, and then you can run it from mexic. 

Speaker 4  (25:25)
Another thing we can use fiddler. 

Speaker 2  (25:29)
But it needs to be built to rise for the bank, right? I don't think they do it. That's why I'm interested 

Speaker 4  (25:34)
Or okay, fiddler, I think fiddler is art. 

Speaker 1  (25:40)
Yeah, it is that's why I was recommending because I remember um yeah. 

Speaker 4  (25:44)
I work with Don on using vitler right when I started at the bank. 

Speaker 2  (25:51)
Okay, yeah, Dan just to meet one of those requests, and I provide the server names, and they can push it over to yay. Yeah. 

Speaker 4  (26:01)
To the server, I mean, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's fine. 

Speaker 1  (26:07)
So I put these dates in, Howard, show me a changed them. 

Speaker 2  (26:12)
Well, yeah, targeting date. I think then the site is completed. This is there. 

Speaker 1  (26:17)
Yeah, and I just put last week's start. I'm not sure what when you started, but that's okay, we went something else. 

Speaker 2  (26:25)
That's fine. That's fine, okay. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 1  (26:29)
Okay, okay, so next It's next next Okay, so that's that. To put that, okay, so if you want to talk about the rest of these items, or if you want to skip over to scale. 

Speaker 2  (26:50)
Yeah, we can probably escape a lot of this stuff like that because they know that really something that we're working on right now. So the camp is kept, they discovered that integration again, this is what the band they go on, as teams are lovely. Our stuff. 

Speaker 2  (27:03)
Yeah, we got Mel yeah. Scanning infrastructure, it's kind of infrastructure I can tell you that we probably need to fast track some of these the placement. And all the stuff, there's a coaster up for later today, with Paul vancouster or something like that. 

Speaker 2  (27:21)
We need to see how soon we can get something in debt set up like there are some required. So there are some additional requirements now, like we need to have a storage canceled out and uh and Again, we're going back to the semicheri that we have with the other guys, but it seems that This might be a little bit more flexible, so I'm Let's see, but this might become another risk. If they have to have one of those bombing connections Well, we'll figure it out one together. 

Speaker 1  (27:58)
Should I put Devin here? I think that's 

Speaker 2  (28:02)
I just wish. 

Speaker 5  (28:10)
For the the, you were just talking about the scanner. Infrastructure, and the beating we have today with Paul, but they're also the cloud engine that's in there. So I don't know that they actually gave us the green light. 

Speaker 5  (28:25)
To actually Go forward with this subscription because they had their hesitations about the sidecar, and all that so I think we're just continuing the discussion, so is it It's like, is there permission or there green light, something that It highlights a you know, a possible barrier. 

Speaker 2  (28:51)
Yeah, but to be Frank, it's everything, a great area, at least for me, every now, but we only gathered that email from the very understanding this is possible. You need to have this and that right? I personally don't know what it takes to make it happen, right like a permission wise or anything like that, it seems to be really straightforward. 

Speaker 2  (29:11)
It just gives us create a subscription for us and then create a storage scam, and we connect to it. 

Speaker 5  (29:18)
Yeah, I get up there and I was like more, but like, I guess. Chad, you remember in our umbrella? Last call, with you, where we joined the call today is a continuation of that. 

Speaker 5  (29:30)
Where it didn't seem like we got a green light from cloud engineering. 

Speaker 3  (29:36)
Yeah, well, Julia, like they don't have full cloud interrupts on that last call. So Julia, should be on this one, and we're bringing Boris and he's also in cloud edge, so we should get a better answer today, 430, right? 

Speaker 5  (29:51)
But there is a risk that they might 

Speaker 2  (29:59)
Hey, Charlie, gonna try the fact that Drift point. Shall we do us today to set up these so they start with the ESPN is also one of those storage account that needs to be set up just for your awareness, the only breath is up early this week. Just because we find out that skinners are crashing, and they say, oh, yes, we had appendency on this. 

Speaker 3  (30:22)
So a big so DSP M needs a storage account also. 

Speaker 4  (30:28)
The store snippet. 

Speaker 3  (30:30)
And yeah, okay, we were on that call earlier. And you were saying that you thought that they stored that already, so sort of like, why are we doing it also frightening, right? 

Speaker 2  (30:45)
And I'm going to lie that we still have to go under and off every single global AI classifier, or detector to see if that allows to actually continue and enhance him to store the data. But we're talking about a 184 configurations that we have to multiply manually, right? So all till I'm done with that, I will assume It is a storage account that that's how it can go well. 

Speaker 4  (31:09)
And how are if I remember correctly? They have mentioned something about. We don't store any of your data, not even snip it at the beginning. 

Speaker 4  (31:20)
They did. I'm just going through my notes here and because 

Speaker 2  (31:27)
So they explained them to run and range accentuate and Jim, that's where we bring them for 

Speaker 1  (31:31)
All right, right. 

Speaker 4  (31:33)
So they basically, they, once you click Be a mass or be, or you or you disable that tactic, they basically fetch the data from the source and the sources are AWS. 

Speaker 3  (31:51)
Storage order or Usher block ok, what things from that earlier is that they were talking about the AI classifiers, kept managing AI AI AI and it's like doing some learning based on They stunned a 100 and whatever things it's my understanding. Whenever there's like, I mean, I'm sorry to say the model risk management team probably needs to be engaged to review the AI aspects of the 2 point stuff like whatever new isn't. But how that is handled usually is I mean, it takes months to get approved to use AI features from a vendor because they need to understand but they do this thing like if you're going to turn them all off, that's fine, but they still need to give you the thumbs app that it's okay to go forward with the things off and that doesn't take as long that's usually a much shorter process, and then you like a wave too, where you go back to mlm later on, if you ever do want to turn that stuff back on 

Speaker 2  (32:55)
Correct witch, and isn't. It's the easier than I asked me to go into the whole process those on boarding errors. I definitely get going. 

Speaker 2  (33:00)
Yeah, I remember that. 

Speaker 6  (33:02)
Yeah, do we have? Do we have any intext here for that, or we submitted that to say we want to turn them off? 

Speaker 2  (33:09)
I don't think we need an intake to turn them off. We just do it right, but I don't 

Speaker 6  (33:15)
Early assessment travel is talking about because like we were particularly careful not to flag anything with AI because then it would have brought up MRI, and all those assessments would have started like, you know, 2 months ago. 

Speaker 3  (33:30)
A diverse tool has the so okay black height was recently deployed in td, it had tons of AI features, but they did not want to use any of them, they still engaged MRM and after a month MRM came back and said you are approved to go live as long as the features are turned off and they did everything by the book for that right. So if there is AI features at all, it's better to just engage them and then yeah, yeah 

Speaker 6  (33:53)
Chadwick, he went offline and threw it again. You know, get get that going. We'll let you know if we need anything from you for Fur. 

Speaker 3  (34:02)
Yeah, I just, I Don' 

Speaker 2  (34:04)
Dung and I know somebody because dung and I were involved in that MRM in the past that didn't wait long, so we have a contact, but some will figure it out. Yeah, okay, good. 

Speaker 6  (34:16)
I'm scared, I keep it on my radar. Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (34:19)
I was from Mike, remember then. 

Speaker 5  (34:21)
Yeah, I'm trying to remember his last name and remind me of it again. 

Speaker 6  (34:25)
Yeah, I grew up. Yeah, okay. 

Speaker 3  (34:27)
He is the guy I'm like, I can'. 

Speaker 1  (34:35)
And any comments from this one here at the endpoint agent set up in testing the same Okay, clear it is there. Yeah, okay, throwing this sign in or 

Speaker 6  (34:48)
I'll tell you when you're ready to start packaging and testing. Because that that is that That involves some guys from the other side that you're working with. Now Employing a government, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (34:57)
Yeah, sign it to maname Patel. Yeah, the same guy that you have about sure, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (35:06)
Okay, and the date you want to. Did you want to put a comment in there or something neat? I'm flowing in outwardly, somewhe. 

Speaker 6  (35:12)
Degrees on integ requests with That's going to be Dave Klein's team. For buckaging intake with packaging team, so we'll work on that next week. 

Speaker 2  (35:35)
Thank you, just trying to figure out that a missing call with somebody else. 

Speaker 6  (35:45)
Nonetheless, I was involved with 

Speaker 1  (35:51)
Should occur in a story for that teve. 

Speaker 6  (35:54)
I would think so, yeah. Because we have, but what night a story under it is a pilot, a story already. 

Speaker 1  (36:01)
Oh, we have set up. 

Speaker 6  (36:02)
So you have it there, you have it that set a package packaging one below it. That's it, that's one below it. Oh, packaging, test again, okay. 

Speaker 1  (36:09)
In the wrong place, then okay Okay, I'll fix that, Dave. I think that the team want to talk about the scale. 

Speaker 6  (36:23)
Okay, what about scale guys? We got started, we got past the cga. They were saying it's a requirement so that What's a certain name, Christel clarified, that that's not a gate. 

Speaker 6  (36:37)
Whoever they're asking for the other lovely one, they're clothed. Test tragedy. They're asking for I must say, I'm going to see some of the 

Speaker 2  (36:52)
I don't so bad so you are actually having active conversation with these guys like the reason why I was asking is because I haven't been involved in it any other day, so I want to make sure that it was moving. 

Speaker 6  (37:02)
You know, I follow every week, and I think this, yeah, this this week, particularly I wanted to, uh U because I had gone to it and then they were saying, oh, you know, we need cgs and I'm saying, you know, we need we need you to give us permission first before we can even get to. The cgs like a chicken and egg thing, so Christel said no, no, there's no cga requirements. We gotta want to, but I saw The key guy figured I look I know for saying he needed something more for the data for the data. 

Speaker 6  (37:33)
In the security assessment, 1 second looking for the emails 

Speaker 2  (37:37)
So we got a note contradicting, but crystal is saying 

Speaker 6  (37:40)
Love course, what Christel kind of told him that I was due that was different. And so that's I'd say so that's I have to keep on top of it, because, you know, we go into an expectation. And then the assessments are saying, you know, they're looking at the whole sheet or back of their mind, we need all these. 

Speaker 6  (37:57)
And that's a nice part for them. If it works well, you, you trop a number of things and Most people aren't come back for the next month, right? 

Speaker 2  (38:06)
Yeah, but I at this pace it's not like forever like a we've been done. 

Speaker 6  (38:09)
When I talk to twice, I always have to be on top of it, because I have one thing. They're asking us, so I'm just looking for the email. He's saying we need all threat modeling. 

Speaker 6  (38:20)
Is that on the radar for you guys? 

Speaker 3  (38:22)
Yeah, I'm doing that excellent progress. 

Speaker 6  (38:24)
Okay, good song, that's what I told him. Just give me a link with something that's in progress. Chad, okay, I stole involved in what that Let's see what goes okay. 

Speaker 2  (38:35)
Where can I see the status of all the different items that we need? Is there is some sort of checklist that I can take a look and see where we are and what's going 

Speaker 6  (38:44)
For the tickets? Yeah, for sure, all the tickets are Have you been, and we've been in the conference page? I can send to them your honor. 

Speaker 2  (38:55)
Yeah, if you don't mind so they and that's like another segue. For this, you see this link that you have here Myron, could you copy this link on this page and send it to me like a this is the view that I'm trying to give, but you sent me the last time gives me a weird view and I honestly hate going through this and navigating like, okay, this one, so why did you have? Oh, it seems like 

Speaker 1  (39:16)
Yeah, so II put it in the 

Speaker 6  (39:19)
I didn't invite every time yeah. 

Speaker 1  (39:21)
Yeah, so he can just, yeah, and just go into the invite to get one, give it a shot, a sho. Yeah, I can say that, but it's really, really And yeah, sure, I can note the other one. 

Speaker 2  (39:33)
So based on where you had you yeah, Claire G. Now this may on my comment, you can tell that I only joined the course I click when the Papa comes up. 

Speaker 6  (39:44)
Most people, as well as pain. 

Speaker 1  (39:46)
Yeah, and that's why that's why I put in the meeting and by yesterday. 

Speaker 2  (39:50)
Okay. So can you tell me what I'm doing wrong? Am I police and not a you're a guy or something like that? 

Speaker 2  (39:57)
If you don't mind, can I just take away the chair? And for a second, sure, look like it. Uh, sorry. 

Speaker 2  (40:04)
Let's know. Okay. Let me just roll stuff around when I click on the link. 

Speaker 2  (40:07)
This is what I'm getting. Oh, I don't see the same view that you have that 

Speaker 1  (40:12)
Okay, so I'm on the very I can't. I can't make the screen a bit larger. Oh, yes, so that's it's the way your Jira is set up your you're, you don't have So you got hierarchy at the top. 

Speaker 1  (40:29)
You should have accident. Yeah, you should have like a little like an arrow beside the feature that will drop that will drop down all the abdomens and stories. 

Speaker 4  (40:41)
Go to the top right? Where cell view and it says basic. Maybe you changed your basic view to I don't know sprint capacity or sprin or the other ones, no dependency management or top-level planning. 

Speaker 4  (40:58)
No proud 

Speaker 2  (41:02)
I don't know if I can do that. It's okay, I can take it offline with you admirer, and maybe you can give me some Pointers, I just this is where I haven't been able to play things because when I go here like I start looking around and I just go nowhere. 

Speaker 4  (41:19)
Right? Right? Unfortunately, by the way, I see the same thing as Hugh Howard. 

Speaker 2  (41:23)
Oh, yeah, okay, you know, when we, when we 

Speaker 1  (41:25)
I have for those that are interested. I can set up a session and we can try to work through it. So for example It could be like in here right? 

Speaker 1  (41:36)
So it configure, and it could be any of these. We can caperation, as sequential signs 

Speaker 2  (41:45)
Let me make a stranger, if so, you don't have to I can purchase a fly if you want a little bit of A Yeah, that's the same okay. Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (41:58)
Uh, uh, the other one could be. Uh ugh, it's just sources safety distributions to 

Speaker 1  (42:18)
Brexit, not a bittersp. You shouldn't have that, I'm yeah, I' Do that. Can you grab this the ordinary? 

Speaker 1  (42:35)
This feature to subtask See the other one. 

Speaker 5  (42:56)
Ah, thank you, I am. Did you just hit Cher Myron like the 

Speaker 6  (43:07)
The option next 

Speaker 5  (43:08)
To export to like, get this link or is that what you did when you assured it? I like I copied him. From the top action, I wonder if this 

Speaker 4  (43:25)
Yeah, I Don. 

Speaker 4  (43:36)
Trying to try. 

Speaker 4  (43:46)
You're in the world. 

Speaker 1  (43:49)
Can you can you edit? 

Speaker 4  (43:50)
No, no Smith, let's read on the Em. 

Speaker 1  (43:57)
Can we share with him? Oh, my gosh? Yeah, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (44:03)
Why, why, why, why? Why 

Speaker 4  (44:13)
I am man, at least we have the view right? We don't need to wrap the update the targets. I started saying that day we can actually go into the different items and not update the different items. 

Speaker 1  (44:26)
Oh, yeah, individually, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (44:28)
Granted that we had the access to modify. Oh yeah, it takes you to Greta. 

Speaker 4  (44:32)
For sure, it takes a tour a decision at dashboard. However 

Speaker 1  (44:38)
Right, so how about how about how about these settings here in review? Sorry, let's just go back. View settings. 

Speaker 2  (44:51)
No, I don't think that's going to change our information, though, then no, no I don't. I don't mean the permission. 

Speaker 1  (44:56)
I mean, from the original view we only had. We only saw this The care eat you you only had the you only had this this year before, but you didn't have this arrow rang, right? Yeah? 

Speaker 1  (45:09)
Which implies to me, that this hierarchy view and so that I would think that you're set for feature feature to feature, but I'm not sure if this You have to set the setting 

Speaker 2  (45:22)
No, that's what I have right now. And I Don' Even with the with the link that you share right? I don't see that error it's just like the main thing with a whole bunch of items under right like the air is not there at all, even with the left snake. 

Speaker 2  (45:38)
So it's not like a we can collapse, it, it's just all the eye to sunder. 

Speaker 6  (45:42)
I see, it Hower. 

Speaker 2  (45:44)
I don't 

Speaker 4  (45:45)
Let me share my screen for a minute, hmm. 

Speaker 2  (45:49)
I still do the term unless they had the blind spot that I have my eyes covering that. But 

Speaker 4  (45:55)
We're reviewing it. The arrows right there. 

Speaker 1  (46:04)
Yes, so if you hit that it shouldn't, yeah 

Speaker 4  (46:09)
Yeah, Dr. Kay. 

Speaker 1  (46:10)
So 

Speaker 4  (46:13)
The arrows right there. I've got it with your with your other eye. 

Speaker 2  (46:21)
This is my year. I don't have to 

Speaker 1  (46:25)
I'm sorry, sharing. 

Speaker 4  (46:26)
Oh, you're doing the read-only though. 

Speaker 1  (46:29)
Yeah, good go back to the original link that's in that we go back to the original link. Yes. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (46:35)
Sorry, I'm talking, I didn't get that part. 

Speaker 2  (46:41)
I Don'. This is a different call from course it is You're most likely just happening in The Bronx screen, of course, during to put it back in the chatter. Okay, there you go. 

Speaker 2  (47:04)
Okay, okay, now it's floating. Nope, so there it's not there. So I'm so you have a feature to stop that. 

Speaker 4  (47:17)
Yeah, snow, they're there, I guess it. 

Speaker 2  (47:27)
That's okay. I have a new holiday. 

Speaker 4  (47:32)
Hover over the there's an error but it's is white. However 

Speaker 1  (47:36)
All I could, oh yeah? Cause you're oh yeah, look at that there you go oh, my goodness, it's because it's because you're using your background, okay as well. Yeah, yeah, oh, good eye, wow, Fernando. 

Speaker 4  (47:51)
I'm big glasses. I have my good glasses on today. That's what it's like to be say. 

Speaker 2  (47:56)
For good blasphemy. So I didn't see that at all quite all-in-one of 

Speaker 1  (48:02)
No, it's a knit of a suck, caught up. That's cool. I rain. 

Speaker 1  (48:06)
Thank you for Nat chat. Just put a link in regards to the threat model for poor po. 

Speaker 6  (48:11)
We're all the markers, I don't know exactly that I'm here, so we get so if we have a few sign ups and away from the data security. Assess us, so those are done. Just It's kind of pardon the other guys to get Got there challenge going wrong, yeah? 

Speaker 6  (48:31)
Over the next couple of days, we've been sitting with them in a flip, everything into attention required, trying to see what they need. 

Speaker 2  (48:41)
Are you guys having like a weekly session? Or this is just half of the episode ses. 

Speaker 6  (48:46)
We did our recastion so the condition for them is whatever, when they did write inside their what they need like great noise saying he needed CJ, and so I addressed that he went in on Monday, I need CJ for everybody so he addressed that, and so then he was able to close out a couple of them. I'm the next thing they need is one guy that you're asking for fan. And as architecture designer, give him the same link again. 

Speaker 6  (49:14)
Cloud quality plan test plan, are you guys aware that that's something I'm gonna send you a link to. It's a that is just at a test plant, so sure that you plan to test and hope. If the template, if it did, it is it 

Speaker 2  (49:29)
I haven't done it personally, but I know some of the guys have actually went over the process for their application. So I gotta say, no, we will rely on that experience too. So here's the thing 

Speaker 6  (49:41)
Hanya's doing one We should look the same way for the same profile sasamania, different anesthesia testing, but as shared as you guys as well. Yeah 

Speaker 2  (49:51)
It will be similar, but no descent remembers remember. 

Speaker 6  (49:53)
Exactly. Yeah. The Buddhists first started, so these guys are not gonna read it. 

Speaker 6  (49:58)
You want to assess, analyze every line you put in there, it doesn't need to know that one exists, and then the gist of it is you're testing from perm band but back I already destroy a lot of the components that you're going to have unpairment, or you're going to be testing what it connects to another, or what you're going to be testing for it, use cases, and all that I might have to list. 

Speaker 5  (50:23)
Dave, you mentioned that you were chatting with crystal about the artifacts you required, and you're just going through them right now, so you just mentioned the cloud thing, did she say anything about sticks? 

Speaker 6  (50:35)
You have to submit a request for that. 

Speaker 5  (50:38)
So did she say that we actually need sticks and C? AC? 

Speaker 6  (50:43)
Policies. This product is they cut policies that come from a state grade, right? 

Speaker 5  (50:52)
In hand in hand 

Speaker 6  (50:53)
Yes, you need to submit an intake for the stick assessment. 

Speaker 5  (50:56)
Oh, but say she didn't tell you whether you don't need it or not. Right Or she did say you need sticks. 

Speaker 6  (51:03)
He needed so proud. You need it. Forget the products that for sure for us to get to Patt. 

Speaker 5  (51:09)
Myron had an entry in here that I was talking about, you know yeah. 

Speaker 6  (51:13)
Yeah, it's applicable and take me to try and get to stick tea for that and they work. It's going to be John bachinkin and Yeah, so what is updated? These guys are okay. 

Speaker 6  (51:27)
It is what they're looking for is that you've started that process 

Speaker 5  (51:35)
I was just checking to see if she waved waved whether you need that or not. 

Speaker 6  (51:39)
The CJ was the one that they had an open, and in the fairly punished that in our 8 or 9 right there, so that was something that we had to address. 

Speaker 2  (51:53)
Yeah, sorry, what was the name of the person John john? 

Speaker 5  (51:56)
John weirkin du. Balkan balkan, I see, how are we did the MS DLP II had the the link I shared it with you guys, I can share it again, the intake group. 

Speaker 2  (52:08)
Yeah, in my book, in a session done. So we can complete that together. Sure, I haven't done it, right. 

Speaker 2  (52:13)
So I was thinking to die on you, and I'm bred, since you guys went over that process, sure, sure, sure Okay, perfect, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (52:29)
Okay, so they should actually circle with you in regards to the steak. 

Speaker 6  (52:35)
Yes, sure it is so that you, because why should I engage? John, cause these guys just need to know that kind of getting into there. Johnny's working on it. 

Speaker 1  (52:43)
Okay, so so right now, right now, I have it as a as a as an affect, that was kind of we just kind of flagged it. We So I'll get the details from you and then we'll convert that to a story. Okay, just one more thing. 

Speaker 1  (52:56)
So on Monday, we had a placeholder for pid review with Peter. I can counsel that correct. 

Speaker 2  (53:07)
No, I think he's the one that calls us who they will get that direction. And I kind of ask a few things right there, right? So let's keep it going until he basically says millimeter anymore. 

Speaker 2  (53:16)
If you guess, okay? 

Speaker 1  (53:17)
Okay, nope, nope, no, no, no worries. I wasn't sure that way that call I needed to kind of quickly. Okay, cool. 

Speaker 1  (53:24)
Alright. So I'll just we'll keep that okay. All right, I think that's it for former me 

Speaker 6  (53:31)
Hey requested for Chad chad orders, the upset The scanning work our assessment Is that? Something that comes 

Speaker 3  (53:41)
Normally there's a team that comes on that, you talk with and go through a whole checklist with them. A lot of The Times it's processed and for a vendor. It's usually kind of like you go through the process, but they kind of just think, well, and you can't do this type of testing. 

Speaker 3  (53:56)
You can't simply descope a lot of it. 

Speaker 6  (53:58)
But either way, I want to tell that to a new brother just needed to be official, and I need that case here. But do we engage them, or do we engage those teams? 

Speaker 3  (54:10)
You know, I'm sorry. 

Speaker 6  (54:11)
I like I can find out. I think I talked only about that as well upset. All right. 

Speaker 6  (54:18)
Let me read that little tomorrow. And so this one So it's track modeling, is it's okay? 

Speaker 3  (54:30)
Aiming for like Tuesday or Wednesday for the f***. 

Speaker 6  (54:33)
Because I kind of check-in with them like twice a week cause, then then then as soon as they move so they flip them back to sometimes they flip them back to attention required. And then said, what so Cause I am I I'm a watcher and all the time, so soon as I touch it, I know. But like I like. 

Speaker 6  (54:53)
Like, you know, I shared that s*** there with you, Howard. Turn on that front, you can't click from that to Find all of them. 

Speaker 2  (55:01)
Perfect, thank you so yeah, I led it to my tracker and tried to keep keep an eye on the task, right? So in the way we just being proacted by them reacting with those guys, you're looking at an update, we just Stop pin them and figure it out, wasn't active. I really want to get this paperwork for you for 

Speaker 6  (55:19)
So yes, yes. 

Speaker 2  (55:20)
Then, it got tight. Yes. Too many calls, honestly. 

Speaker 6  (55:23)
Yeah, because we can't point and we can't connect to anything without it right exactly, so that's what I used as a cg guy that says we need to connect for the cga to be done, and we need you to allow us to connect so we welcom. We can't get a cjograph. Christopher said yeah, that's true, got it up, yeah? 

Speaker 6  (55:43)
On the airport, all 

Speaker 2  (55:53)
Alright, thank you so much. And we should have 

Speaker 1  (55:55)
Great, have a great afternoon. Thank you. Thank you, everyone. 

Speaker 2  (55:58)
Thank you, thank you, folks. 
