
Speaker 1  (00:00)
That's what we said, right. 

Speaker 2  (00:01)
Friday mornings. 

Speaker 1  (00:02)
Or Thursday morning, whatever 

Speaker 3  (00:05)
I remember that clearly saying that's out. 

Speaker 1  (00:09)
Yeah, I mean, it's still a concern, but not for this specific. 

Speaker 2  (00:15)
I'm in a minute here they are going to drink. 

Speaker 1  (00:16)
Try to get off of shared accounts right? And they're putting it in the rfp, which hasn't been Yeah, some doubt yet. 

Speaker 4  (00:25)
So gay, that was the difference with core Vs Eagle funding, Jonathan, that when they were talking about that on that call, that's the funding, they're supposed to be using to remediate that type of work on their end. 

Speaker 2  (00:39)
Bye, bye. 

Speaker 1  (00:41)
I mean they, I don't see how that plays out. I mean that they're Their cash machines, the hardware is end-of-life, has to be replaced. 

Speaker 4  (00:53)
So it's odd for them to replace that. Yeah, but a new solution, not us. 

Speaker 1  (00:58)
That's right. Thank 

Speaker 3  (01:01)
Yeah, I don't think we should discuss it really that much. You know, I'll just go back to what we were doing on Friday. 

Speaker 4  (01:10)
And capturing the use cases Anthony, just for your awareness, we don't need to capture use cases about what the app teams need to do to their apps that makes sense. 

Speaker 3  (01:22)
A app is yet to be decided, we have a sticky for it. We are not going to be deciding talking about apps right now. And 

Speaker 5  (01:34)
First, I'm like 

Speaker 3  (01:36)
It's okay. We were just about to break into lost, stolen and broken. So I tried putting everything into a table so that It's like a one line of things, and we do have a lot of pain points, so I think we should focus on the pain points. 

Speaker 3  (02:04)
Today, at least and maybe assign it to someone to investigate or maybe even poce it, I don't know But something needs to be done about those pain points. Wow Your opinion then. 

Speaker 2  (02:25)
I'm so these pain points, I'm not sure they're things that you came up with. Because the shipping are key Vs the shooting a local spare. If someone can't log into their computer. 

Speaker 2  (02:35)
Keeping a kid's not an option for branches like that. They can't log into their computer, so they're going to need something faster than shipping, drop shipping. 

Speaker 3  (02:46)
I mean, the baby cases where branches may run out of spare keys or you know, not all branches may have sufficient spakeies. Well then, I don't think we need to go so deep, you know, we can reject the paths. We Don 't need right now, I just try to gather all the parts that I could think of you don't need people. 

Speaker 2  (03:12)
And it's fair to say like we can't rely on it's fair to document we can't rely on shipping for tactical replacement for somebody who requires it for desktop logging or maintain. Frame access, right anything that's core to their job function has to be faster than 

Speaker 5  (03:29)
Drop shipping is not an option today, so just say right? No, but hang on, I'm i'm We were already going down this path in compluence, decimating the cons and pros, as well as the flow itself, right, and so where we left off is that we're going to continue that With some additional questions for Jonathan, an option to In our next call, which is now right? Yes, so should we 

Speaker 3  (04:06)
Continue here. Yep, maybe we can. I think you have merely captured everything on both the options unless you have another option in mind, because that's how I got all the pain points from basically, okay. 

Speaker 5  (04:21)
I mean, I have some. I have some additional opening. 

Speaker 3  (04:24)
Yeah, sure, go. You can edit it. You have it. 

Speaker 3  (04:26)
Do you want me to say the link? 

Speaker 5  (04:29)
I know I've got it, I've got it open. I'll 

Speaker 3  (04:33)
I have a feeling it's nearly completed. Yeah, there'll be some few. There'll be most some things because I got all the information from this. 

Speaker 3  (04:43)
Whatever I whatever I tabled in there 

Speaker 5  (04:52)
Okay, so I actually had a couple of I was thinking about looking at this, and I had a couple of questions for Jonathan. Okay, the the the submitting of What I noticed is that what we were talking about, like, they show up at the branch without a usable phytokey, right? Yeah, um, um, and then you were mentioning that we needed to, even though we weren't going to Have you become dropship, a new key? 

Speaker 5  (05:25)
We were still going to have to do the requested ServiceNow to get the new key, and I wanted to understand that a little bit more because you were like, we have to put in a request and ServiceNow even if the manager's going to take a spare from the safe and give it to them. We still have to initiate the request and ServiceNow, and I didn't really understand that like, why can't the manager just take the spare? Oh oh I know why uh U. 

Speaker 5  (05:47)
Not the reason why we had to do it for this one enough, or this one is because we don't want the manager to just be able to issue a random key to anyone. 

Speaker 1  (05:58)
Yeah, and that was specifically in the specific conversation. There was around if you were using that uben roll app. 

Speaker 5  (06:06)
Right, cause that supposed scenario, it does not need it, and this scenario is not needed, because they would just the user would be setting it up under their own. It would be an unregistered key, and they'd be setting it up under their own login, so the managerization of being anything okay. 

Speaker 1  (06:22)
Yeah, so the way the way I had I mentioned this a few meetings ago, but right now the way I'm thinking of it is full self-service recovery. So that's, you know the one you just said you just had to manage our hands-on the key and then goes through it so full self-service. Versus assistant. 

Speaker 1  (06:45)
And the city, yeah. 

Speaker 5  (06:48)
What option do we have for full self-service? Because nothing that I've seen so far enables full self-service unless we have a kiosk. 

Speaker 1  (06:54)
Yeah, we're gonna need. We're gonna need a device in some form. I had to do to do the self-service 

Speaker 3  (07:05)
Don't the US retail team have a chaos application? They currently use 

Speaker 1  (07:11)
But we said, kiosk, been, I mean, we've talked about this a few times just some secure device. 

Speaker 5  (07:19)
Yeah, I like this right here right proposing. A component that are created restricted private browser. But this is what you More of a main line? 

Speaker 5  (07:30)
Yeah, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (07:32)
Yeah, I mean, there's not, but I mean. There's just not going to be some 

Speaker 2  (07:37)
Something a bit different, I would say that's a different option, right? It's a sort of a variant that optional, yeah, it's a different option, right? But they need a keys set up in the brick room or something right? 

Speaker 2  (07:49)
Or A I don't know some kind of AA like an application. That's accessible. But at the windows, long end screen or something right? 

Speaker 2  (08:01)
But that's all of that is like, what are the security holes that might how do we properly control that I guess are we trying to avoid the, you know, accessibility, shortcut hack equivalents on desktops. 

Speaker 2  (08:24)
Yeah, well, it's good. 

Speaker 1  (08:26)
Yeah, I don't think we should be doing anything that that requires that accessibility hack. 

Speaker 5  (08:33)
Well then yeah, that's the other challenge. Right. So, but option 3 would basically be Provide a kiosk. 

Speaker 5  (08:44)
Style. Device um U. But what's pound, on that one for a minute, Jonathan, cause I can see how that can work in target state. 

Speaker 5  (08:56)
But I'm not positive how that would work in interim state. Because how would they log in like, how do they prove that they're them from a self-service perspective? To then be able to to register their Fido, keep 

Speaker 2  (09:12)
But if it has a restricted browser, then it's basically like the one like what we had done previously. Right, there's the kiosk mode doesn't have any desktop functionality or Connectivity, other than to the M365 

Speaker 5  (09:26)
Or what is it running? What is the kiosk running? Is it running windows? 

Speaker 5  (09:30)
Does it have to be signed into? How is it being signed into windows? 

Speaker 2  (09:37)
Not to the user account because the user can't do that, or I guess it's a or you could let them use their password only, but then have it. That have a very restricted desktop functionality set 

Speaker 5  (09:49)
Can I make a suggestion Jonathan? 

Speaker 1  (09:53)
Yeah, by our way. 

Speaker 5  (09:56)
Is there an option here? Where we can create an early version of the onboarding portal that is externally accessible that the youth the employee can get to from their own mobile phone. 

Speaker 1  (10:07)
Yeah, that's one of the the 

Speaker 5  (10:09)
Allows for a security registration with a verification now, understanding that we have an identity proofing, this would be a much better way. But even in lieu of identity proving, if we were able to leverage our tactical verification process, perhaps where we would use their provided information through ServiceNow and to sale point to issue them, an OTP, or something. To their email, which would then validate that they are, who they say they are, they would have to enter it in within a certain time frame. 

Speaker 5  (10:41)
And if they entered in within a certain timeframe, then we allow them to then proceed through to create. How is that 

Speaker 2  (10:51)
Instead, give it to their eat personal email or their work eating. 

Speaker 5  (10:54)
Yeah, personally, you don't. 

Speaker 1  (10:57)
Yeah, so all of these self-service ones have You know, challenges with them, right? Whether it's the verification. Yeah, so the verification. 

Speaker 1  (11:08)
Why would we go 

Speaker 5  (11:09)
Prior to education on the path 

Speaker 1  (11:11)
Right, so that's that's certainly targets. Target state. And You know, when I have recently been been a proponent of You know, thinking through keys for everyone. 

Speaker 1  (11:28)
Right? Uh U. It's a different, it's different for someone like you and me Vs that teller person. 

Speaker 5  (11:37)
Absolutely. Yeah, I' But the challenge that I was the reason why I was thinking about some sort of onboarding portal In advance of us having full identity proofing breaks, right Although honestly Jonathan, we should move forward as aggressively as possible on identity. Proofing is really the right answer, right? 

Speaker 5  (12:00)
And we need to get off the ground on that and just spiraling nowhere and W I'm and getting nowhere right? But the the That the issue with Um, um, with a kiosk itself. Is that no one's going to pay for it? 

Speaker 5  (12:15)
Jonathan, that's the problem. It's absolutely the fact that it's tactical, like we won't meet it anymore once we have identity. Perfect 

Speaker 1  (12:23)
Yeah, well, I think what we had kind of been leaning towards, or I thought everybody was leaning towards was if we have to do something in a branch then That having like a manager. Be able to launch, you know, a secure window within that 

Speaker 5  (12:42)
Which is this option right here? 

Speaker 1  (12:44)
Yeah, something that something like that. 

Speaker 2  (12:46)
That's just an order of tennis or and I don't think it can really restrict it to the manager. 

Speaker 5  (12:54)
So do we want to discount? Do we want to just discount the kiosks device right now, right out of the gate just because we don't think that it's financially. And Administratively, feasible, like, like, logistically, I think that it's, it's, it's out like Unless you think that we can actually deploy a kiosk device to every retail branch, I mean, if we also talk a little bit about that Chromebook, Jonathan, we're still looking at what a couple 100 bucks for a Chromebook times 3000 locations plus the delivery of that and the setup, and like all of those things and the software development and everything else like 

Speaker 1  (13:32)
I wasn't thinking of a dedicated device here, something that could be reused if we have to go down that path. Ideally, they're able to recover themselves from their mobile phone. 

Speaker 2  (13:49)
We have an online mining option that wants them to do that. Have we farewell? What's the op? 

Speaker 1  (13:55)
Just from a self from a self-service perspective. Right, they need to do identity verification. Well how you're going to do it, ideally you'd be doing it via your phone. 

Speaker 2  (14:05)
No, I mean, how are we going to do it the real world, not It's like, target state. I guess that's what I'm talking about unless we're not, oh. 

Speaker 1  (14:13)
Can we do it with what we have today? 

Speaker 5  (14:16)
All right, let's change option 3 to onboarding. For like self-service external facing onboarding, provide Self-service onboarding, portal. 

Speaker 5  (14:41)
Our balladays set up There are security restrictions. Okay, so here's technically how we can do this now, right? I Don' Let me run through this and then we can poke holes in it. 

Speaker 5  (15:03)
Okay, so first step would be awk. They sell the brands so that are useful. Fight, okay, for where whatever it is right, and then they they take a Fidel key from the spare cash with manager approval. 

Speaker 5  (15:17)
From that point, user Launches. ATD onboarding, portal application from They're mobile device. And it might be, it might be url, not a web, not an actual app, though it's making a mobile app would be super cool, but I don't think that we're going to be that far along so url from the role models. 

Speaker 2  (15:44)
Full device right? It has something you know roughly wanted but like I had an unmanaged browser, we can't assume the managed browser because we can't assume the yod. 

Speaker 5  (15:55)
And it doesn't this is not assuming BYOD at all. 

Speaker 2  (16:02)
The surpasses the CA changes and stuff, so that it's an unmanaged browser. I was just saying that because it affects like a right, a secur. 

Speaker 5  (16:11)
I wasn't note, I guess I have BYOD we actually have better options for them, and maybe we can call out the difference there, right? 

Speaker 2  (16:19)
But we're assuming worst case scenario I guess right now, which is that they don't have that. Yeah 

Speaker 5  (16:25)
Have we confirmed, actually Paul? That through the TV edge managed browser, we can actually get to security registration. Do we know if we have if we can even do that? 

Speaker 5  (16:35)
Because if they haven't, that's 

Speaker 2  (16:38)
What's up worry now, that that's only a look subset of you that's only a subset. 

Speaker 5  (16:42)
So I know, I know it's, it's great 

Speaker 2  (16:46)
Yeah, it's planned for big 

Speaker 5  (16:47)
I still think it's useful broader, Paul hear It's useful for us, broader than retail. To understand whether or not someone from a TV byd device can get to security registration through the edge managed browser. 

Speaker 2  (17:06)
I mean, and you mean sort of into a tunnel or just through the edge management browser without the internet tunnel? 

Speaker 5  (17:12)
During the in tune tunnel? Okay, there's 

Speaker 2  (17:17)
But I saw I don't see why not, but yeah, yeah 

Speaker 5  (17:20)
Okay, side point and that that opens the door for some other use cases for byd users. But uhm Okay, so they launched the onboarding portal url from their managed browser. Now We have an option here. 

Speaker 5  (17:34)
Right? Cause if they've set up authenticator which we're gonna have them, do post their Fido, key log into their device, ideally, right? If they've set up a tenacator theoretically, I um We have a couple. 

Speaker 5  (17:50)
Well, we actually technically have a couple of options, right? One We can have them authenticate to the onboarding portal with and try deathenication. Using their authenticator for multifactors, so we could actually have them connect to the to the onboarding portal with multifactor if we wanted to So that that is an option, right? 

Speaker 5  (18:13)
Like a user Logs into onboarding portal, and this can be an option on the onboarding portal, and we'll talk about what the broader usage of the onboarding portal is, as we get into this right, but let's say that they, the user, let's say, clicks. On option for Mfa, recovery or whatever right or phytokey, recovery or mfa, reset, or uh U. Not for managem. 

Speaker 5  (18:44)
Multifactor options, or something right? We'll rename this multifactor options and it is prompted. I Don'. 

Speaker 5  (18:57)
Again, with td credential. Us, and as authenticator. 

Speaker 4  (19:06)
So are you talking about, like a certain ServiceNow form acting as the onboarding portal or like something like that nopepe, nope. 

Speaker 5  (19:15)
So what I'm serviced now at all. 

Speaker 4  (19:17)
The TDR boarding portal is the URL that can you, can you access that externally? 

Speaker 5  (19:23)
Yes, that's the intent of it. 

Speaker 2  (19:25)
Or this is an imaginary service. Well, there's it's like this is 

Speaker 5  (19:32)
But it's just, this is a planned portal. That is part of our identity proving work stream. 

Speaker 4  (19:41)
Okay, so this is over on their ID proofs. 

Speaker 5  (19:44)
I think we're considering, yes, okay. And what I'm talking about is opening up some of the options with that portal and prioritizing them to be done sooner. 

Speaker 2  (19:54)
Yeah, and now I'm trying to understand how this even works because of the revolt, okay? 

Speaker 5  (20:03)
So they passed their mfa, right? Now, we have a couple options at this point. We've always said Jonathan that like we need to do another layer of proofing other than just them logging in and passing an mfa, prompt. 

Speaker 5  (20:18)
So one of the options that we have, we could choose to say, you know what, this is good enough, let's just let them get right into the security registration portal with mfa M as authenticator of mfa and reset their methods. But I don't know that this is going to fly, so let's let's Add the keep going down this path, right? So User Uh, uh, uh U. 

Speaker 5  (20:45)
It is prompted. Bye, bye, the I have a size, I pass A And OTP. A verification check. 

Speaker 5  (21:00)
Uh, using their personal email, uh, uh, U. Not ah, and we'll have a time boxed. OTP generated VP. 

Speaker 5  (21:18)
I sailed mine. And sent to there Email from a workday User enters the code into the browser. I'm Uh, to confirm uh. 

Speaker 5  (21:46)
I did right now this process right here is available in sale point, it is being enabled right now for the service desk we've been working on this as part of the identity proofing workstream, this is the interim identity proofing mechanism that is being made available to the organization and HR is going out to the workforce to prompt people to update and make sure that their home email addresses are correct for this purpose. So when they call the service desk moving forward, they are going to be prompted by the service desk to confirm an OTP against their personal email. 

Speaker 5  (22:21)
Well, the service desire likes to be able to do it. Against their work email, if they need something where they have access to their computer or BYOD, and if not, then they'll go to their personal email and it'll be secure sent to their personal email. So that way they can get the code and it'll be time boxed. 

Speaker 5  (22:37)
So this mechanism is already available? We just have to hook into it, okay. Yeah, user and just the coding to their browser reform identity right right On boarding, portal? 

Speaker 5  (22:49)
Bye byes them with a tap um um um yeah. And directs them 2, uh U. Not ms. 

Speaker 5  (22:59)
Security registration page. 

Speaker 2  (23:02)
So we're gonna allow so the CA changes we're gonna have to allow, I think we don't allow this right now, but we probably have to allow this for the administrative portal anyways off that we're security information registration while using it by via tap. 

Speaker 5  (23:17)
Or make that out, and so make sense, it's a bootstrap. I guess so. This the reason why we're doing the bootstrapping here. 

Speaker 5  (23:25)
Is that this gives us another verification? Check that is accepted right now from an audit perspective, right? And restricts them from going directly to the portal with just multifactor they would need a tap to get in from outside, which is what we've been discussing, Paul right So this is how we they get there. 

Speaker 5  (23:44)
And then from there right user register spider key, and they can register this from their whole phone, right? 

Speaker 1  (23:53)
They, they can. And that's what I've been, you know, doing some testing with over the past few weeks. And basically NFC is a bit flaky, thank 

Speaker 2  (24:08)
I was going to ask if that works well well then I see as otherwise they need to have a compatible port. 

Speaker 1  (24:13)
It works like it works, you know, I was able to do it, but you need to be very Very particular about where you're holding that key Right? And Android is right in the bat, the middle back Of the phone, apple is right at the very top of the phone, and so It's a bit flaky NFC was a bit flaky. Now doing the the key insertion Works nicely. 

Speaker 5  (24:47)
Nay, xyz, most phones, most recent phones Mac and Android are going to have a USB. C. 

Speaker 1  (24:54)
Recent ones. Yeah 

Speaker 5  (24:56)
Raising Mac raise in apple right firms. 

Speaker 1  (25:02)
Yeah, so an example is usbc. I could insert the key upside. That both ways up or down didn 't matter, and it would work. 

Speaker 1  (25:15)
For my apple with the lightning port, the key had to be inserted in one way only. Right now, here's the here's the thing, those keys that we're going to deploy for retail. They're just NFC plus you know one Method, whether we'll be USB C that USAR EC It would have to be C right? 

Speaker 1  (25:46)
It would have to be have to be C. So for Android or you know, the latest IPhone model, they could insert it. 

Speaker 5  (25:56)
Besides, in the late iPhone model, there, like several iterations down USB C now, right? So uh U. I think it was skeptician that started it at far back, okay? 

Speaker 1  (26:07)
But what whatever whatever I'm AI have a 12, right? So I'm 

Speaker 5  (26:14)
Come on, man, you're supposed to be peacher, peacher, forward. 

Speaker 1  (26:18)
Hey, it works fine and I replaced my battery. You know, in the in the fall, and it's like new, so It was was well worth well worth a 125 bucks or whatever it was, instead of spending a 1000 

Speaker 2  (26:38)
I think that we got good guy. 

Speaker 5  (26:41)
In this method, right? They'll be able to register their phytokey, and then be able to just turn around and sign into a computer. 

Speaker 1  (26:50)
Yes, yeah, immediately, yes. 

Speaker 5  (27:08)
Um. The problem with this method, one of the things that we're going to have to talk about with this method, is that this method in comparison to the other methods In particular means that if the user doesn't have a mobile device, or they don't have. So relies, I'm gonna say relies on several possible break points. 

Speaker 5  (27:33)
Uh, we're, which would I stopped the user if Conditions aren't met right? Okay, most of the common settle. It really needs to be combined with one of the other options. 

Speaker 5  (27:47)
Right? So, this is a self-service option, you know, in addition to one of these other options. I think right, this doesn't replace anything, right? 

Speaker 5  (27:56)
Because user MPs. They may not have mobile phone. It isn A mobile smartphone. 

Speaker 2  (28:09)
Well, the eyes that there are there. 

Speaker 5  (28:11)
May not be registered for authenticator. 

Speaker 2  (28:15)
So when I was interrupted and didn't work if they don't have their phone, then they need a tap from the desk basically so maybe that needs to be a flow to And then the tower 

Speaker 5  (28:27)
I'm from batdesk, what do you mean? 

Speaker 2  (28:28)
But if they don't have a phone, they can't meet the mfa requirements out of the country. 

Speaker 5  (28:32)
Have a phone that can use option 3 at all. 

Speaker 2  (28:34)
Right, and they cannot also can't use option one I was just slagging that I forgot a plan because I mean either yeah, I mean it's Waiting to clarify something called backgroun. And that's probably helped us to use a tap, especially Gary. And then they registered on the desktop in this special private prowess. 

Speaker 2  (29:02)
It's sort of an option, 1A1A or 1B or something like that. 

Speaker 1  (29:18)
Yeah, so for that long list of scenarios. That's why, you know, if we can do oneself, service and want assisted. We probably could capture all the scenarios 

Speaker 5  (29:39)
Alright, so like these three things. We'd block them from this process. 

Speaker 2  (29:46)
Right? Yeah, I would say that may not be registered for authenticator if we could say or authentic registration is stale because they don't have to use it because they're using their fidop normally. And then if we make them do it, it'll, if we don't make them use it. 

Speaker 5  (30:02)
Jonathan and I have long talked about something that I think becomes more relevant, as we move forward Jonathan, and that is, is I'd love to explore. I wanna take this as a sidebar, and maybe Anthony, we can put this in a sticky note somewhere that we can track We need to explore an option that periodically prompts people. To validate their authenticator their msathenicator MF. 

Speaker 5  (30:28)
A. Yeah, thank you Yeah, and I can think of a few ways that we can potentially do that. And I think that we need to explore that, I think that it's a necessary thing, and I actually love to kind of do a little bit of research, Jonathan to figure out like if Microsoft just heard about this from folks, if somebody else has already kind of figured out an approach for that I can think of a few ways that we potentially could do that, but I'd like to see what other companies are doing. 

Speaker 5  (30:54)
Because I have to imagine that this is not unique to us. 

Speaker 2  (30:58)
Is that built-in one caress, PR? But I don't know if we want to use that. 

Speaker 5  (31:03)
What do you mean as a built-in one 

Speaker 2  (31:07)
Oh, yeah, thank Yeah, but it's weirdly only tied to sspr. It didn't seem like a general functionality, but it's 

Speaker 1  (31:15)
I don't think any of those registration campaign type features are. I don't think we can turn any of them on. Oh, and I found the I mentioned about sspr changing Let me put the Q the And they put the link link in the chat here 

Speaker 2  (31:41)
Any return, and the changes you're talking about is just knocking off some of the worst options right or yeah, that's right, better in any way. Okay, then it's just a yeah, it's It's becoming more constrained when it was already not particularly great, so 

Speaker 5  (31:57)
The same way John I'd like to just step Backed option, 2 per a second So they they open the I just, we never finished this John thing, because he had to drop mm M. Alright, then I'm not familiar with the ub en roll app, so I'm not clear on like what the process is for that. 

Speaker 1  (32:15)
Yeah, I know, I know much more now, I think I think I can. I think I can explain it because I was confused about a couple aspects like, like, how does this thing work? If the ubian roll app is connected to the ubi cloud right, like it's out how does that work? 

Speaker 1  (32:36)
So I spoke with Shaquille and And Ken chant and Ken Chan is I don't know if to call her an architect, but she will be like Yeah, yeah, yeah, like whoever whoever's going to be doing the, you know, the build for us will work directly with her, right? They like they sell so any anyways, they walked me through it. And a few things, so we did say, in our last meeting. 

Speaker 1  (33:13)
Okay, there's there's polling like, we've got the phyto connector it's going to poll the ubico cloud. And the ubico, the cloud console, there. It's kind of broken into two things. 

Speaker 1  (33:25)
It's the old school portion where you're doing the consignment shipping. Simon consolidated shipping writes of the bulk stuff, and then the prereg stuff Right, so those go into those go into a queue and the in the cloud. And then, once the it's fulfilled in the cloud, it changes the flag, and then the phyto connector is going to pull that every whatever we configure, I think no faster than 15 minutes. 

Speaker 1  (33:59)
I think that's the lowest denominator that you can do So when you think about the uben roll app To put this all together That that initial request to be able to provision somebody a key, it needs to get to the ubico cloud. So there's the reason for 

Speaker 5  (34:17)
And that goes to Nicole connector to get to the cloud from 

Speaker 1  (34:20)
That's right, so now it's in the now it's in the queue, the ubion roll app connects to that cloud. It sees that it's there in the Q and And then you can go ahead and And start the registration process, so from a user perspective, when that key is, you know, inserted into the phone tapped on the phone, it appears to be fully registered, but in reality that polling period needs to occur, so it's going to take A Up to 15 minutes before that key is actually active. 

Speaker 5  (34:57)
Okay, so slot on for a second so I gaped this yeah, sorry, yeah, so we can so serve you. The submitted recustom ServiceNow service now sends it to the EV connector UV connector makes a request to EV go cloud to issue a key which goes into a key. 

Speaker 2  (35:11)
Yeah, but to issue a specific keep, maybe that's where I was confused because the human connector is usually for issuing a specific key to a specific person. 

Speaker 5  (35:21)
How I'm confused about this is like, we would need some option in ServiceNow to tell you, because like we're requesting a new key. But don't just immediately ship a key out the door to an address. We're just requesting a new key that's going to go into the queue, and then we're going to issue it from our spare cool, like there has to be some sort of a difference. 

Speaker 5  (35:37)
I assume when it goes to ebitco cloud. 

Speaker 2  (35:40)
And then otherwise it might 

Speaker 5  (35:42)
It's going to be telling it to ship a key somewhere. 

Speaker 1  (35:45)
Yeah, that's right. 

Speaker 2  (35:46)
Yes, so they're locking the registration for a specific user. And that's where I was like, say, but the key It doesn't know about the key until it's inserted into the app, right? 

Speaker 4  (36:05)
Yeah, and till you insert it, it won't doubt 

Speaker 2  (36:08)
But this is just all of this permutation, is only to Unlock the user for registration from the app by that manager, right? 

Speaker 5  (36:20)
Yes, it's to unlock the registration. I don't know, so then. So once the ubico connected once the ubic connector makes the key to ubico, cloud to issue a key or get it into the cube. 

Speaker 5  (36:32)
The branch manager opens up EV enrollable app, and then does what they can see the cue, so then they can issue a key to fulfill that key item. 

Speaker 1  (36:41)
That's right. So instead of like, think think of instead of that key coming from, you know, the ubico factory and then the ubico factory. You know, puts that information into the cloud portal. 

Speaker 1  (36:59)
Which the phyto connector then picks up instead of it being the factory that's provisioning, it, it's being provisioned via that ubi, enroll app. 

Speaker 5  (37:09)
Ok, so they they they recruit, they select, they request for they select the request for the worker from the queue and they they, they either tap the key or insert it. And the key gets provisioned, yes. 

Speaker 1  (37:24)
Yeah, so it's not a 100% provision because it's not provisioned on intra. Right, so it's exactly right, and it's exactly 

Speaker 5  (37:31)
Yeah, so it sort of taps the key to provision it, which is what creates the key material and stuff, right? Yeah, and generates the pin. Yeah, ematerial and yeah, and yeah It generates hanging. 

Speaker 5  (37:48)
Right? And then youby connector. Checks into ubiko cloud. 

Speaker 5  (37:57)
Yeah, I' On, it's necklace. NE. Next polling interval. 

Speaker 5  (38:07)
And sees the fulfilled request. And register or and uploads I'm the public he tontra. ID. 

Speaker 5  (38:27)
Setting up. Elliot a** that said uneasers account bye by Yeah, now what it also does during this time is it also then I assume follows whatever process we define which we've talked about, like, sending the pin to the user's email or etc, because now the other thing is, is that we have to actually issue the pin unless in the ubn roll app. They can enter the pin at that time. 

Speaker 5  (38:59)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (39:00)
The intent is that the manager would hand the phone to the employee, and they would set their pin, so that's how it is right now. 

Speaker 5  (39:08)
Our roll wrap supports that. 

Speaker 1  (39:10)
Yeah, it does okay. They're not, they're not keen on doing that forever. They really want to change it. 

Speaker 1  (39:19)
So that the manager has no chance whatsoever. Of knowing the pen That's what the current Iteration is doing 

Speaker 5  (39:35)
So it's not even an htp, long poll. If it can take up to 15 minutes, this is like a scheduled task run, yeah, like a cronjab type run. 

Speaker 2  (39:44)
We're a bank. Everything's a bad job, right? 

Speaker 5  (39:50)
Okay, subtle, and then once that happens. Once S method is registered in the Inn. Entra, user can use the Fido key Okay, so I'm signed back into desktop teams. 

Speaker 5  (40:12)
Okay, so like that's all of the fun there so cons to this approach. There's a feed 

Speaker 2  (40:18)
Authorization model for the manager like administrator 

Speaker 5  (40:24)
Travel and requires energy to be airplane. 

Speaker 1  (40:27)
Manager to be there, yeah, or delicate. Yeah, or delegate, like somebody 

Speaker 2  (40:32)
Yeah, that's maintaining a list not only of managers, which at least have some information in workday, but of delegates, which was presumably a more flexible Designation. Unless there's some branch already branch. HR thing that could be used as a proxy like manager, deputy or something. 

Speaker 1  (40:58)
Canchan. Just said that everything that the ub and roll app is doing is available via SDK, and we could build, we could build our own app. I Don' Because, like, you know, we talked about that being part of the 

Speaker 5  (41:18)
Interesting, right, like we could require the manager to have BYOD, and we could register it as a BYOD app. So that way, it wouldn't be available on a personal perspective. Yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 4  (41:28)
The outside sagana, thinking what you're thinking with this onboarding portal is a sort of Something the manager or whoever we decide through the use cases to be actor in that situation could access. If not You know to yeah, a new high 

Speaker 5  (41:43)
So the benefit for the the benefit of the onboarding portal is that it's more self-service for the user themselves, and it doesn't require us to have some sort of manager model, because the problem with the manager model like is like qe, how do we know like the manager like we have? We have managers, for example. That float between 5 branches. 

Speaker 5  (42:04)
Right, so if they're not physically in the branch, the workers screwed out of luck unless there's a delegate that's physically in the branch. 

Speaker 4  (42:11)
But also because of the team brands 

Speaker 5  (42:14)
As for the US for example, have extended hours like really long extended hours, so the user, the worker might be in at 7, the authorized parties that might have this may not be in until 10 because there is an opener that's in at 7 right? 

Speaker 4  (42:28)
So we need to follow-up discovery session with Jan Wilkinson, or whoever that Isabella, or whoever that person is, it sounds like in that meeting I didn't get. We ended there before we got too deep into it. They weren't. 

Speaker 4  (42:41)
But it doesn't sound like, okay, the branch manager is aware of the new hire, the new hire coming onboard. But it's not a new new hire, though, but any employee, though Paul, it sounds like they're not the only one handling the management of his people. Like there's a team that we can contact Jeremy, that handles this for the kind of stuff on the one. 

Speaker 4  (43:07)
Like Paul doesn't sound like it's the model we have. We're like every approval you send has to go to me, right, like it seems like there's because of that for all Jeremy. It sounded like there's other people involved in personnel matters. 

Speaker 4  (43:22)
The problem 

Speaker 2  (43:25)
That they need to have a physical presence as well, like, even if there's other people involved with personnel matters from other perspectives, like I don't know that anymore specifically. 

Speaker 5  (43:33)
They won't be able to do any of this okinaw. Okay, they're all remote. All right? 

Speaker 5  (43:38)
That's the problem right there, like I guess they have the branch Admin team right that handles and facilitates brands. 

Speaker 4  (43:43)
Yes, yes, but they didn'. 

Speaker 5  (43:45)
They're sitting in a back office, right? And they're not any of the retail branches, so they're not, they're not in physical presence, so they can't issue a key to people, because and handle a spare pool for us, because TV's branches are spread across from, you know, Nova Scotia down to Whatever the whatever the province is on the theater. Above Washington, not blanket up British Columbia, there we go. 

Speaker 1  (44:15)
Probably north, we're probably in the Northwest Territories, too I would, I would ask him that 

Speaker 5  (44:19)
And then in the US we're between Maine and Florida, right? So like There's just no chance that there's some centralized Admin group that's going to handle this, because it requires the whole point of this is that it requires physical presence. And so that's where, like, we either have to have a robust cell service option, or we get really complicated, real fast when it comes to like making sure that there is always an authorized person. 

Speaker 5  (44:46)
Who can do some sort of issuance, which is why I'm not sure. The this is actually ever going to be a viable option to I honestly feel like The options are going to be So option 3, with a fallback to option one 

Speaker 4  (45:08)
For I picked me into, have a conversation Jeremy with Shaquille and TED and see how are other branches doing this? Yes, and yeah. 

Speaker 5  (45:15)
Yeah, you know, I agree. I agree. Like Bank of America is way bigger than we are. 

Speaker 5  (45:18)
They have way more educ. 

Speaker 4  (45:20)
Wells Fargo are using them now too, so clearly they're getting around that are doing something to meet these. So 

Speaker 5  (45:27)
I would like to have that conversation with TED and team 

Speaker 1  (45:31)
Yeah, yeah, sounds like manual. There's a lot of manual work going on. 

Speaker 2  (45:37)
It wouldn't be surprised if some people use the kiosk option does seem like I wouldn't be surprised if that's somewhat 

Speaker 1  (45:44)
X approaches data, and in regard to listen, do you be in rule I mean, I've said it multiple times and I don't think it's going to be practical. I don't think it's going to meet our current timelines, right? This is the potential future future state thing. 

Speaker 2  (45:59)
But with the physical Answer restrictions, I don't. I mean those will be true regardless of how the app is configured unless That's the whole like managing manager telling it. I guess that seems like an Admin overhead. 

Speaker 2  (46:11)
No matter what state the application is in. I don't know that they can fix that administrative complexity Unless it's unless it becomes self-service, I guess I'm But how do you wait, can it is there some option for the ub en roll, where it could become self-service? I'm holly. 

Speaker 1  (46:34)
You do it for yourself. 

Speaker 2  (46:37)
Yeah, because I am trying to think of this and it's 

Speaker 5  (46:40)
So there's a permit on that monophyde opens app the Q so that I mean, if it's something that like we could log in with a td credential, and then only have access to our request in the Q. Like the user would only have access to their, that would be an interesting way to use this Jonathan. 

Speaker 2  (46:59)
Is the queue always wide open, or are there options to restrict the queue open? 

Speaker 1  (47:03)
Well, there's no restrictions right now. So you know, shakile is, I don't know if he did, but he was gonna submit a couple enhancement requests, just based upon all of these discussions that we've had over the past. Past few weeks, Xi. 

Speaker 1  (47:19)
Right? Cause they were asking for this. Everybody would be needing something like this. 

Speaker 2  (47:26)
Hey, you and I I'm trying to think so, but you also said that they have like SDK right? That's where it's open. So if we like, like, maybe almost what Mike was saying, right, can you So by that, do they mean like we could even intermediate? 

Speaker 2  (47:43)
The UBQ registration requests, like process, the physical key information through our onboarding, portal and registered Q. 

Speaker 5  (47:51)
Vertically, right? We could actually register right through the onboarding portal that would be like a like a variant of option 3 or maybe it would be its own option option 4, which would kind of be a combination of option, 2 and option 3. 

Speaker 2  (48:05)
We don't have to expose ms security registration. Publicly, then and that 

Speaker 5  (48:12)
We wouldn't be able to, yeah, we wouldn't have to Say let me capture it. So option 4 is leverage Are UV enroll S decay through the td onboarding roll? To verify and then register Fido, key or user directly rather than Exposing ms, security registration portal, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (48:57)
This one's pretty interesting. 

Speaker 2  (48:59)
Definitely a bit more in development. Work than just 

Speaker 5  (49:03)
Yeah, it's a kind of better option. Option then 2 and 3 by themselves, though, um Just really quick. I'm just gonna divert from this for a second, we're almost at time again. 

Speaker 5  (49:17)
And just go back, I wanted to actually discuss a guardrail for this use case. I believe that for any of the options One of the pending conversations that we've had for this is that we should consider if they've lost stolen, broken their phytokey, I believe, that the act of registering a new one, as part of that process. We should be taking on an effort to delete their old method. 

Speaker 5  (49:47)
Or kill the old Fido key method. 

Speaker 2  (49:52)
By the onboarding portal that becomes potentially possible, but I or but the option one, we Don 't guess. 

Speaker 5  (50:02)
Correct, and so with the option one, we end up having to solve this through another process, which would be something like some sort of an external cleanup process. But I want to capture it as a guardrail, because I think that it's, it's warranted here, right, like, if they lose a Fido key, and it's still available as an option on their off, menistation that is a security risk to td, absolutely yeah. Right, so if someone is as indicated that they've lost their phytoky, we need a mechanism that should play into what option we choose right is that we need a mechanism to ensure that we are clearing that registration, right? 

Speaker 2  (50:41)
And option one right option one actually could have them use the onboarding portal from internal instead of using the ms, right? The authentication 

Speaker 5  (50:51)
There's an option, but I don't think that it solves our problem with The fact that they're leveraging an open workstation that someone else has signed in 10 yeah. All right, and we can get all kinds of complicated with that Paul, and we can force a sign in, right? Rather than taking the ss or the currently established ss token, we can force a sign and we know how to do that with cyberark. 

Speaker 2  (51:19)
Well, no, you improvate browsers. The only way to fully isolate you from like the PRT but yeah, which has money. 

Speaker 5  (51:24)
Submit him parallel right now. Whatever 

Speaker 2  (51:27)
We would be talking about a separate browser session anyway, so we'll talk about some protected variant of in private. I think That that blocks access to the local prt, so you can't use local anything, and it also doesn't pollute the session outside of that browser. So I think it's Required for that approach 

Speaker 3  (52:13)
Hello, is there anybody there? 

Speaker 5  (52:16)
Yeah, we're here. 

Speaker 3  (52:18)
Okay, because everybody went so quite suddenly. But have we figured out if we do have a private browser in TV, or is it? A Tobi vyache. 

Speaker 2  (52:30)
We don't allow it right now, we don't allow the default, right, so it would have to be a custom custom private browser S set up. I actually don't remember if you can do it like the isolation I did or brunt band did we weep. People were messing around with for the windows. 

Speaker 2  (52:48)
Hello, alternate login stuff that's only that only isolates it from an 80 perspective, and that does not isolate it from a like. Local prt perspective, and I actually couldn't figure out a command. In line to do that, so it'll be a little bit of tinkering and maybe development work to sort of I mean, it'll definitely be some development work to build a customer. 

Speaker 2  (53:11)
Nathan browser that is isolated from the local sessions. And that is that That is locked down. Because we don't want to, if you isolate it, and it's in private, presumably, you don't want people to be able to do arbitrary things with it. 

Speaker 2  (53:25)
So it's rather Heavily customized browser potentially for option one Or you have to deal with well, make sure the user doesn't sign in and then sign out and then make sure the other user logs out so that from a certain person who's on that system. And mfad, applications on behalf of someone else etc, no Upset when the big testimony More than any of our current thousands 

Speaker 3  (54:01)
I think using the SDK is a good option. Because it reminds me of business theme registrations. I don't know if you've ever done business name registrations, but I have registered a couple of businesses. 

Speaker 3  (54:21)
And it uses a bag, it uses a patchwater SDK, and it does all this for you, you know, it registers the business, it checks for any nuances. If there are errors, it points them out. And then And it does the same for cancel a business name. 

Speaker 2  (54:43)
Yeah, it's just I don't know lately. We haven't looked at there after assuming that's 

Speaker 3  (54:46)
Yeah, but that's yeah, I mean, you know, this, in the whale, we're talking about reminding me of business team registrations. 

Speaker 5  (54:58)
An hour was at time. I'm i'm pretty comfortable with the 4 options that we've well, all of them have challenges, but I'm i'm I'm comfortable with what we've documented to the point where I think that we can explain this better now and we can actually draw up some diagrams for this Anthony. Or we can argue and generate some really easily with mermaid, or something based on what we've written down and we can tighten it up a little bit. 

Speaker 5  (55:26)
But I'll throw in a little bit of verbiage for option 4I think I understand what needs to be done there so I'll just throw in the steps for this. And then I think that we should in our next session, start to move on to some of the other workflows, unless folks want to have other items to talk about for this particular use case. 

Speaker 3  (55:48)
I think this this workflow forms a good baseline for the workflows. 

Speaker 2  (55:55)
If something's if certain we, I don't Unify, certain things is required to fulfill this workflow, then other simpler workflows, we can just say, well, you just gotta use that thing we design, we set up for. For this workflow. 

Speaker 3  (56:07)
If you make this a bit modular, I think the others will just piggyback of it. Okay, alright, well, thanks folks, very good. Okay, tomorrow is this? 

Speaker 3  (56:30)
Do we need one. No, should we have one on Thursday? I'm not sure if you're on vacation, but I know Fridays. 

Speaker 4  (56:37)
I think a lot of people out Jonathan, I don't know, are you coming back in? 

Speaker 1  (56:42)
No, no. I'm off Thursday and Friday, and that you guys are off Fri. 

Speaker 4  (56:46)
Yeah, yeah, and I'm off tomorrow or Thursday Friday, so 

Speaker 1  (56:49)
And next 

Speaker 3  (56:50)
When next week Tuesday next Tuesday? Okay, folks next 

Speaker 5  (56:53)
Yes, there's the I won't be here Tuesday to Thursday next week. 

Speaker 4  (56:58)
Anthony I can still meet with you to catch up on things so 

Speaker 3  (57:02)
We keep the drawings ready in the meantime. And when Jeremy gets back, we can tweak them as needed. 

Speaker 4  (57:12)
I don't think a planned. Okay, thank you 

Speaker 3  (57:36)
I'm 
