
Speaker 1  (00:01)
You wanna make the rest of ours look bad by working any day off? 

Speaker 2  (00:08)
I just, yeah, anyway, I'm 

Speaker 1  (00:09)
And I just 

Speaker 3  (00:14)
I'm guilty of one of them. 

Speaker 2  (00:18)
Yeah, I Don'. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
What does it do? 

Speaker 2  (00:20)
It's about taking it some other day. 

Speaker 1  (00:23)
Our Manish, wise, Paul here, tell us what you did to make this happen for the man. 

Speaker 3  (00:29)
I detent key Herbert. I didn't know it was a day of or it was an idiot mistake on my retinal ey. 

Speaker 1  (00:45)
Is there like a is something on fire? 

Speaker 3  (00:48)
No, nothing is on fire. It's just one of those related the process document we need to go. Or with the im team to get them final blessings, so we can close off one of those tickets. 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
It's a this one with the CSP or something else. 

Speaker 3  (01:03)
No, no, the CSP 1 CSP 1I had to reschedule. It was also scheduled for this morning at the front of But I had to reschedule because you all was tentative and Johnny was not available either, so I had to reschedule. 

Speaker 1  (01:15)
I'm a bad guesser. Which one of these tickets will it resolve for you? 

Speaker 3  (01:20)
It is the atmosphere unit, the 195 

Speaker 1  (01:24)
That would have probably been my second-guess I mean, like, oh, come on. All right, keep fighting the good fighter. It would be nice to see that one die eventually considering how long it's been taking, but 

Speaker 3  (01:36)
Yeah, I'm doing it, hopefully I can just kill it. 

Speaker 1  (01:38)
Okay, I love it. I would be very happy to see it in the Dun pile. What else is going on? 

Speaker 3  (01:46)
And so there's something from Andrew that there is supposed to be a story created Paul. If you remember that 2 days ago that he was talking about, that, we need to like while you were off on a sick that there should be ticket tracked in one of the epics for the documentation part. 

Speaker 1  (02:09)
Oklahoma. What are the chances? This is somewhere in my team's mess or it's possible. 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
When you've ever been done, then from Andrew 

Speaker 3  (02:22)
Find my notes too on that. 

Speaker 2  (02:26)
Nor it could have been just mentioned as an aside at 1 of the meetings last week. 

Speaker 3  (02:30)
Yeah, that we were supposed to talk to morale about it, so cause he's not allowed to create stories on our app. Yes, please, because you harassed him. 

Speaker 1  (02:40)
I was actually very scared about it, but I did make it pretty clear, and I just don't, but that's 

Speaker 3  (02:46)
Whenever it works. So 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
I use my charm which is mostly threats but it works as well. 

Speaker 3  (02:55)
Apologists or the story that I was saying, I will help out with the creating a document for is that the process document, or is that like how to document, how to request the like, how to implement that app? Raj Visa is using the new process. Because I'm just not unclear on that now. 

Speaker 3  (03:15)
After yesterday's call 

Speaker 2  (03:18)
The one that you had taken that I had previously had but was not really working on, and there's it was because it was Going to those gsdws, things That that Andrew's, using, attract track. I'm planning a representatives, but they don't show up on anybody's boards. That that one was representing The internal team process documentation that it's like, how yeah, how to actually, you know, end-to-end deliver. 

Speaker 2  (04:03)
Much, much more, well No, it's like focused on like somebody who actually needs to fulfill the request that other one's more like 

Speaker 3  (04:15)
So it's like AS3 mode of amount 

Speaker 2  (04:18)
And literally, just for the people doing delivery, it's not intended for anybody else to consume, it doesn't have to be no request or ever needs to read it et. Cetera, that's the version of the documentation, which there's a bunch of little bits and pieces that represent parts of the process that are sitting out there and some of those could be just like the overall process document says, go here for this step, but then like do XYZ and that's the part that we don't have is that there's like, how do you do it end-to-end from you get an intake through it is like fully deployed in the environment, and like, what are the things you do in between just something that links it all together and provides some of the gaps in the process that like in the delivery land people just find out because, you know, the other delivery people told them to do that. 

Speaker 2  (05:11)
That was entirely missing. 

Speaker 3  (05:15)
So we need a story for that I'm not sure what that would be. What 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
Oh, so this is the, you know, photo documentation thing we're talking about, yeah? 

Speaker 2  (05:24)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (05:24)
And that's not this, because So I had 2 takeaways, I know of from my discussions with Andrew one of them was fixing whatever hot mess this thing is. 

Speaker 2  (05:36)
Yeah, I think if it does, it's square. This particular item that we are talking about right now squarely belongs this epoch, but oh my gosh, this, this epic is a little bit right, is a kind of historical thing. 

Speaker 1  (05:51)
Can I just say how proud I am, for figuring about part up for myself without having to ask you guys. All right, that was one of my takeaways. So that is the same thing that Andrew brought up. 

Speaker 2  (06:02)
Or is that there's a bench of Android where they discuss the one we're talking about right now. Isn't this one okay? 

Speaker 1  (06:09)
There's that, and then this is the other one that I took away with. Andrew is like, what is this? 

Speaker 2  (06:17)
II but I told him II just wanted, I should spin up a story with this and put it in a sprint, rather than just having it, Andrew hanging over expecting it, but me, not really paying much attention, mostly all the week. So 

Speaker 1  (06:31)
If you are right with it, I'm gonna keep you guys after class shortly, but first check-in with more and make sure he's good and he does not need to sit around for the like, unless you feel like, we should be aware of this, in which case we're going to hang out too or Warren, how's your sequel database? Angela deployment thing coming along. 

Speaker 2  (06:53)
Hello, world. 

Speaker 4  (06:55)
Second, basically finish. I just need to climb in to do the actual sequence database itself. But I might as well, just clone that ticket and end. 

Speaker 4  (07:03)
And Bobby's a good fit. 

Speaker 1  (07:05)
I like that. 

Speaker 4  (07:07)
I did too tick if you had the next ticket is also 2, so I didn't want to make this one5, so I was created the ticket. 

Speaker 1  (07:13)
Speaking music to my ears, the last part, you need to tell me to make a non cacophonic, is that if you are clothing something and adding to this sprint, that it will be done by next Tuesday. 

Speaker 4  (07:26)
So and then let's go for it. Yeah Yeah, you think I think so okay. 

Speaker 1  (07:33)
In which case, I'm good to lead you on your long and you'll clone it, and do all the things, or do you need my help? I'm good at it either. 

Speaker 4  (07:38)
Yeah, I'm good thanks. 

Speaker 1  (07:40)
Okay, then rock and roll any other knowledge that we need to drop on Warren before we let him go on his way. Doesn't look that way that's good. Toxin. 

Speaker 1  (07:59)
All right, let's sort the 2 of you out and okay, so this is our Onboarding and design and training epic, which is, yeah, like my least favorite epic. Because for starters, why the f*** is weighing here? What are we doing here? 

Speaker 1  (08:20)
Um, you mentioned you need to put together like a single document. All are you going to put together multiple ones or yeah, tell me what you're doing or what you think? You shouldn't. 

Speaker 2  (08:33)
President, there's a few things I guess I would say so here one story wait and I thought i1 second. Let me bring up a chat. I mean created The story Related to this, I put it in the wrong epic. 

Speaker 2  (08:48)
Of course, 1 second, let me say I have 2 stories I created on our last 

Speaker 3  (08:56)
Or they, the one that depends on the last 

Speaker 2  (08:59)
The more they put on the last If they roll out here here ugh, yeah So never mind, I didn't do this once, so okay. So for this one, I'm gonna Hey? So the sorry I mean, I thought I thought there was a story you kind of took, oh no, sorry it was gsd, ws, 395 that we wanted to convert to something that you were going to help with. 

Speaker 2  (09:30)
But that also, because you don't run this process really needs the delivery team to walk. You through, and I was suggesting that they had a little bit ago was that they also have like they have some interns. So like it could be a situation where like, you know, the delivery team is walking through one of these requests with the interns, and you and like work they're kind of everybody's documenting the exactly what steps towards 

Speaker 3  (10:00)
Is it already working progress document for this, or did you creating a strong scratch on 

Speaker 2  (10:05)
Like I was saying, there's there's parts of it are documented in different places, but the like whole process itself is not documented anywhere. And there's like, you know, feath. 

Speaker 3  (10:18)
We're from Maya and I just said, well Sorry, just remind me, thanks so me as alob comes to service delivery for new app registration through the sender second intake. Now I need to basically say document how the services literary or wim team will fulfill that request basically either running some sort of a individuald job or running a script. 

Speaker 2  (10:44)
No, it's only the adp GT job we're not dealing with other versions of the process, right? This is going to be a very like, this is the process you use to deliver this, and this is the details around exactly what steps you need to do who you might need to get approvals from and talk to blah blah blah, it's very much focused around how do they fulfill a specific kind of request which is this sso onboarding because there's like a lot of other if you know, if an app registration is for purpose X or for purpose, Y then you use process X or then you use process Y it's like we want to create a much more simplified version of all of the service delivery documentation that exists for the for like that that's supposed to cover, like 10 different use cases, but only to cover what you do for one use case and in doing so be much more straightforward than the 4 list of like subcrogination, right? 

Speaker 3  (11:45)
Warren daddy, I expect it, was this going to be complicated, I thought it was going to be one of those easy how to documentation, but that's fine. 

Speaker 1  (11:53)
And also, we are somewhat running out of time, because all 3 of us need to be on Andrew's, mfa, onboarding, blah, blah blah, meaning that starts at 10 o'clock, then I've got a 10th 30, can we reconvene at 11 and Bang this thing out? Okay, you're actually going to take some time off good for you. 

Speaker 2  (12:14)
No, no I have a 2 hour meeting start. 

Speaker 1  (12:16)
Go after that. That's why I was in force. 

Speaker 3  (12:19)
2 hours. 

Speaker 1  (12:20)
Who's who now? Why declin's? 

Speaker 2  (12:23)
I'm sorry, Howard, and that one's only an hour and a 1. 

Speaker 1  (12:27)
That's still terrible. Alrighty, I'm hesitant to say 1 o'clock. I don't have a problem with that, but it's a Friday afternoon in the summer, so you guys are 

Speaker 2  (12:40)
And what would that get to that either from 1 to 3050 

Speaker 1  (12:46)
You're really earning legends. 

Speaker 3  (12:47)
That's Anthony's meeting. 

Speaker 2  (12:49)
Ed one. 

Speaker 1  (12:52)
Why don't we reconvene on Monday and sort this out? I'll at least get that on our calendar, or I'm sure you're all booked up on Monday to why don't we reconvene when both of you are free at some point in the earlier half of next week, and we'll sort this stuff out. 

Speaker 3  (13:08)
Yeah, I want to get this done as soon as possible, because I know, the vds, that's going to come heavily. Then I'll be very busy, so I don't know how much time I'll be able to put in afterwards, so I just want to get it done as soon as I can like while I have sometimes cycles. 

Speaker 1  (13:22)
What is coming up? 

Speaker 3  (13:24)
The video edited. 

Speaker 1  (13:25)
Oh, VD I'm sorry I heard VDS for some reason, but ok, okay? 

Speaker 2  (13:29)
And it's going to make you just want to help with it, right? I'm not saying for this, that one, it is going to be a lot on, because you don't know the process, you're just hoping right, you can just be free to coordinate the delivery team doing it to some extent. I mean, I like 

Speaker 3  (13:45)
And then what I like to do like what exactly needs to be done right, like the way you have it planned out in your head, for example, right, if I know that then at least I can ask someone of Stevie, and they're also swamped, so it's very hard for me to ask them to do it. 

Speaker 1  (14:04)
Doctor I mean, do you know where this story should live? When it is on is that our epic 

Speaker 3  (14:11)
We don't have an epic, so I think that's what Paul was saying, 395 should be converted to one of our epic just to resolve that document, I think right. 

Speaker 2  (14:19)
What does that do? Then if you're looking at right now 

Speaker 1  (14:22)
I sorry, I worked up and I'm And this is the other random story that you were just hanging out with Paul for X right trid. Yeah, and try idea pick that's on the go. 

Speaker 2  (14:33)
I don't this, is, I you can put it in the module and process improvements as kind of the closest, but it's really not. It doesn't fit in any of the boxes, necessarily it's made by somewhere it's somewhere between module and process improvements and the custom claims provider, but it's not the custom claims provider, so otherwise 

Speaker 1  (14:54)
They're worrying, okay, we'll, we'll just move it over to our lb requested work from there. 

Speaker 2  (15:02)
Don't move it to modular practice improvements. It's closer to notice. 

Speaker 1  (15:06)
They can use module and processing prudent, that's one of our stuff. Still, one of our Bau epics, right? I think it's one we never use. 

Speaker 2  (15:14)
No, that's, that's got a bunch of stuff in it that I it's the one that So split was split between me and Brandon for a while. 

Speaker 1  (15:25)
Oh, oh, that guy, that guy, the red epic, I know. That's how I know it, okay. Yeah, I'll move it to the red epic. 

Speaker 1  (15:33)
Cool beams, let's go talk to Andrew. I'll let you know when that's cleaned up. 

Speaker 2  (15:37)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (15:38)
But it's more because battalion 
