
Speaker 1  (00:00)
I'm flying, but yeah, yeah. See how it goes. 

Speaker 2  (00:08)
So it was good to have 

Speaker 1  (00:15)
Alright, then thank you. So I'd like to you guys are late, we're done. 

Speaker 2  (00:29)
We don't 

Speaker 1  (00:34)
Oh, this is kidding. It's kind of funny because I went on to calls when somebody says something like that. 

Speaker 3  (00:43)
Neither governor. 

Speaker 1  (00:48)
Yeah, I'm I know people are good. Yeah, yeah. Okay, let me just And this is the pit for dp, second idea, right? 

Speaker 1  (01:07)
Actually, maybe what we were so Peter, are we doing with the with the Peta, we actually breaking down things in basal malcodo is just going to be one forward dp's second idea, since we are part of the same agent, how we're doing this? 

Speaker 2  (01:24)
I haven't really done any movement on the page. Part I think we discussed this with being like 4 more codes right? This one, let me say a bit do I mix it up with another project, or maybe, okay. 

Speaker 2  (01:41)
It is one sdp, right? Let me take a look, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (01:46)
We could, technically, it's the same agent, it's going to capture in the same data. It's just the same aging basically In the eigenfunctionality, right? But everything else is exactly the same, there's no difference. 

Speaker 1  (02:02)
I mean, if you had to duplicate this and just say, this is for im, that's fine, too. Just, we just can't answer the questions called Yeah, let me know, okay. Yes. 

Speaker 1  (02:17)
I Don', hey, Todd, good afternoon. 

Speaker 2  (02:22)
Alright, so this is the better the drafted together for this project. Now let me see if I can represent presentation models, right? So I really haven't imag. 

Speaker 2  (02:33)
I was kind of you know, I was kind of Looking in the morning around like what's new here? What's like? Are we doing any trend? 

Speaker 2  (02:43)
Do we have any changes and so on? So, so Still, the draft I put together? If I remember correctly, we set this one video crab picture there. 

Speaker 2  (02:56)
This won't be like different model codes, and I should do a different bits for the mark calls. I can either bundle them together into one demand or I can clone and create several copies of the demand but from my side, the difference is like deployment right? You want to deploy everything together. 

Speaker 2  (03:16)
Then when the money is fine, if you want to do it in sequences, or don't have the idea about the timeline yet, and it's probably better to spread it in a couple of demands, but that's just, you know, bureaucracy, paperwork right or another. 

Speaker 1  (03:35)
Yeah, so it was interrupted. If you asked me, I would, I would say that if you could probably bundle it M and dB sec right, just because there's no additional components being deployed as part of the ITM right, all the components are being deployed as part of the besides, so it shouldn't impact, where ipm is doing like, technically, itm relies on everything that we do on the dp 6 side. They have abundant dust together. 

Speaker 1  (04:00)
That should be fine unless somebody has a handsome, sir. 

Speaker 2  (04:05)
Find me, you guys tell me what you want to do, right? So as I said, doesn't really matter to me, it's, it has only packed where I see it's down during the deployment, right? So yeah, that's it. 

Speaker 1  (04:17)
I think she had a government. Yeah 

Speaker 4  (04:19)
The society has, I mean, on this diagram, even it has the servers on the left, and then the cloud, like the potential blob storage on the right, I think potential. We should maybe take that out like the Azure stuff. Of this demand ticket and just work on the servers, because those are very clear, like it's clear what's needed. 

Speaker 4  (04:38)
There's no confusion and they need to get built. And the ITM so Peter, there's no I don't think there's any servers being built under itm, right? I mean I Don' 

Speaker 2  (04:58)
If I put it on hold since we last I had quite a lot of the blob, right so 

Speaker 4  (05:05)
In the ad, there's nothing. There's no servers in scope for icm. I'm just confirmed, like so Howard and Fernando and team if anything's changed, but I think that's still correct, right? 

Speaker 2  (05:17)
You know, so people go ahead. 

Speaker 4  (05:19)
The only thing that lithium stone is potentially that integration with Azure, the same way dp sec would integrate with Azure, for storing in the long-term data, but if we descope the Azure stuff from this conversation, then we don't even need to talk about PPI, tm right. Now because it's there's nothing going on with the cli 

Speaker 2  (05:37)
No, sir. But 

Speaker 3  (05:39)
If we include art They Usher is on their dp sac. The same data is going to be pushed to that same data bucket, right? 

Speaker 4  (05:52)
The reason I'm suggesting to separate is because if we just do the server build for dp sec here, then they'll get built based up right, because it's very straightforward standard built. If you include the Azure blob storage that's going to be months before they finalize whether that we're going forward with that or not, and that'll slow down your server bill. 

Speaker 1  (06:14)
Ok, so you're tacking over from the logistics, and then we add the shortest as an additional component or a modification of the design. 

Speaker 2  (06:24)
In addition to this design right like, we had a few more set of letters, so we can add whatever components here later. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (06:35)
I agree with that, because we don't know when we're going to be able to set up that part right, so it might take a year for now. We don't know, so I agree. 

Speaker 2  (06:45)
Okay, so let's show tpi, tms, it doesn't really have any other components. Honestly, I don't have to do any bit for that, right? The chorus from my point of view, it's basically black box sitting in the sauce side right? 

Speaker 2  (07:01)
How you guys connected, it's pretty mature problem. As long as you don't need any servers, then we don't really have to do any pit there or any integration. We don't, if any integration, we don't Prem like authentication is required for this, then we have to do paid for that. 

Speaker 3  (07:19)
Ok, yeah, so PPI TM and DP sector they're basically the same size con, so So if you can connect those 2 by a line that will represent AI guess. The connection between them 

Speaker 4  (07:35)
So Peter, you would mean, like, if it's doing an entrastole, like that type of line, you would want to see 

Speaker 2  (07:42)
Yeah, well, whatever he's coming from PPA team, pretty much to ALL prim, right? So what's happening here in the theater? You know, orange box, whatever. 

Speaker 2  (07:53)
I don't really care right because this is outside of our day, infrastructure, right? This is SARS, whether they communicate together or not, tighten, really have to show that 

Speaker 4  (08:04)
Okay, then maybe the only thing or the two things is the agent, so they share an agent that is deployed on endpoints, and both of those agents would be sending a feedback to both like out 2 lines 1 to each app code. 

Speaker 2  (08:20)
So you mean this one, this line there is A No, no, no, yeah, Joseph, the age inside the windows for us to serve or is to workstation the windows all laptops. This would be always too right? Components, and this would be Some office I software or something right, all of these, so you are saying they are sending to dpc as well as to PPA TM. 

Speaker 4  (08:53)
The ones that can be, I just double-checking this. Okay, so the 03W11 is Windows 11, so that's fine. I think that makes sense the OS and S2 is Mac OS so that also fine. 

Speaker 4  (09:09)
Oh, 36PP is office 365 pro. Plunthe. And Howard and team does the does the endpoint agent interact with office on the devices? 

Speaker 4  (09:21)
I think it's, I think the answer is no I think semantic did but I don't know if proof point does. 

Speaker 1  (09:27)
Yes, that' it does pull the identification, it does pull information about the use of what I believe does, but the Logan process, right? It doesn't interact directly with the platforms, it just does it as the user's slugging and captures that information. 

Speaker 4  (09:42)
Yeah, so I don't think, but that actually goes as part of the ancient communications so that one can go out and then the PEOI 

Speaker 2  (09:50)
That would be erect windows, a right workstation. Anyway, physical connectivity between windows workstation and this one or whatever runs like the office, 365 on that and the pwp, a local agent right from a windows right, okay. 

Speaker 4  (10:06)
The window doesn't macwood, have the local ingent in the cover with monitoring. Whatever's on those Queen. The PEP relay is the email relay for sending outbound email. 

Speaker 4  (10:18)
And I don't think The dp email talks to that one so Correct? Yeah, so that one should be separated. Probably. 

Speaker 4  (10:27)
And 

Speaker 2  (10:28)
That's fine. Yes, yes. 

Speaker 4  (10:32)
Okay, now now that box. Yes, now that box can have a line to PPI tm also. Alright. 

Speaker 4  (10:42)
Yeah, and then the only other thing that maybe is not shown here is the single sign on so that it's talking to entre ID for both of these. Unless it's somewhere in my mind. 

Speaker 2  (10:56)
Do you have a model called food act? 

Speaker 4  (10:59)
Oh, 3A. A. D. 

Speaker 2  (11:01)
Okay. Yeah, so much for now. Here, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (11:13)
Alright, okay, let me pull the stops. Hey Microsoft is your active director so I will keep it here. Yeah, on the bottom now what about this M? 

Speaker 2  (11:36)
F? T? T do we still need to use it? 

Speaker 2  (11:38)
Or what is the For now it's out of scope, or we don't use it at all. 

Speaker 4  (11:44)
I think this is needed this Penguin, that's been 

Speaker 2  (11:47)
Maybe we just try to jot it last time. When we try to move the foils from 

Speaker 4  (11:54)
So this goes to the EDM indexer, which is, which, what is ADP sec I think they will check Indexer, yes, so Hey, I want you to hear you. Yeah, it's in the table shows. 

Speaker 2  (12:20)
And so yeah, this is the stuff I was using right on 311, and I know I seeks to relay, hire an email. And of a 65, yeah, all right, sorry, I was staying with those okay. 

Speaker 4  (12:36)
Yeah, this cmd MDM dmd is not listed there yet. I mean I have a note at the updated diagram, but it should point to the dp security, so Server, one of the servers which I would point to The non database survey 

Speaker 2  (13:00)
Yeah, of course. Right. So we are saying that, okay, can you say it one more time? 

Speaker 2  (13:06)
Which one goes to where I mean it goes to server? But from where 

Speaker 4  (13:10)
Link from mftt because the cmdb is sending the cmu. Whatever that is sending to the Non device, the windows 

Speaker 2  (13:21)
Just 2022. How are we going to do the delivery? It is deteriority pro to MFTT to pull it from mailbox, or do we want MFTT to drop it somewhere? 

Speaker 4  (13:31)
Yeah, it hasn't been finalized, but it's probably gonna be dropped. Either independently on all 4 servers or on a share. 

Speaker 2  (13:40)
So if we have to introduce share, it will be a nightmare, and we have to do pretty much for the service. For that like first-hand cluster, arrange this specific category 2 alright. I might be able to do not. 

Speaker 4  (13:54)
It's not a bit of A 

Speaker 1  (13:57)
So are you talking about the Adm stuff? 

Speaker 4  (14:01)
This is the exact data match, the file app yeah. 

Speaker 1  (14:07)
The way we want to design it is like we want to have the fast bin dropping in the 3 or four different locations where we're going to be working right. Our plan is to have that folder because the folds are just, they're just going to leave for a short period of time, right? But what we're thinking is just because we know there are some challenges about, you know, what kind of data it is and all the stuff our applying is that we kind of create a folder, and then we're going to get that folder, encrypted, we were metric, right, so it's protecting. 

Speaker 1  (14:36)
We don't have to go and fetch any other device or anything like that, right? Once the data is indexed, then our jobs should be able to delete the phone from the server. That's the whole that's what we will foresee this work here. 

Speaker 2  (14:49)
Yeah, but how hard remember this is rating? I want to write, so we basically have to have fireshare, cluster, we have to have that folder on a Coster desk connected to claustrop, and we have to have like Tr frail over cluster. My tree can do, but that would be for a supplied service here. 

Speaker 1  (15:15)
But I 'm trying to understand why we'll have to be that the case because this is a father's just going to be living on the surface for one, like less than an hour right? Can I can I just go and create a mini fart just for the evm, where the rating is lower and right? And And avoiders in the coast, are there 

Speaker 2  (15:34)
$200 in artificial institute of extraordinary articles like a lot of artwork, a good example. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you have 5 or four separates right now, so we have, if you create a coast. If you create a folder on one to serve it, right. 

Speaker 2  (15:44)
It's that particular server fails. You. You lost the data, right? 

Speaker 2  (15:48)
So already, it's 

Speaker 1  (15:50)
No, because this is not data that is going to be leaving on the server that this is, the data gets the same to the server. And we just once indexed, and that's, it's gone. Delete it from serve it, we don't need to keep the data That's alright, so let us show a period of time once it goes to the SaaS, we don't need any one of the server. 

Speaker 2  (16:17)
The program is the short period of time between the history, but then it's processed, right, if you sit in the time that for that moment, that should be automatic favor mechanism, if you lose that particular server, which, because you are 18 extensive and so on, then you have that 

Speaker 4  (16:35)
They asked so the idea was, there's 4 servers land this to all 4 either directly, so it's 4 independent copies or a share so that it's the same copy but shared a mountain on all 4, right that we ask the vendor if there's any smart, like logic in the tool. So that if one server goes down will another one automatically take over and handle the job answers. No, but it can be manually done. 

Speaker 4  (17:00)
So if the server goes offline, someone has to go manually, select another server to do the same task as long as it has the same file landed right so again it could be independent. It could be a share. I don't really think it needs to be a share yet. 

Speaker 2  (17:15)
No, it doesn't have it, please. Have you guys checked that? Tipcock can deliver it to all locations in the same time. 

Speaker 1  (17:23)
Yes, okay. We're joined into that this is not new for us, right. We're doing this transfer, we're doing it with Samantha today, right? 

Speaker 1  (17:29)
So we have a number of servers where we drop the fuzz, and there's only one active doing the indexing, and for whatever reason, we get an alert from our application saying that the index felt, and we take a look, and then if something's happening with the surface, we just kick it off. From the next one 

Speaker 2  (17:47)
Okay, but how do you manage the files on the other service right? So if the process, if the server let's say, server one processes the processes the file right, you still have 3 other copies of this same file, right? So how do you manage that? 

Speaker 1  (18:04)
They sat, they said job that goes in the meet. The data after the induction process is complete. Okay, okay, yeah, if the indexing joke fails right, then operations get a notification right and the file is still sitting on the server ones that infects whatever, then the lesion job Browns have to be completed. 

Speaker 2  (18:32)
All right, I will put a note about that here. But it just told me that they were 2 or fourth places and job running on one server with 3 other breakup copies of the far and eventually in case of failure it's processed from the deck observer, and there is also a job that handles the managed to find out the copies of the file okay, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (18:58)
Alright, I can live in that X yeah, and I think what they're doing the overlapping the overlapping the scripts. So if one fails, right, the only ones will be delayed. The deletion job is not going to kick off right, so it shouldn't be an issue, but we can always play with the jobs. 

Speaker 1  (19:14)
Schedules and make the happening in a neckling way. 

Speaker 2  (19:18)
They are the only thing, it's been, my need to get some risk attendance for that because Pata, you are waiting extensive, you expect everything for the automotive, and this is like Manuel jobs, so we may need to get some risk acceptance that is not built. This particular mechanism is not up to the highest level. It's required. 

Speaker 4  (19:40)
Yeah, that's the limitation of the Vanderbilt, because ideally, even if all 4 indexers received the same file and passed the same data down to the sax, like in a perfect world, the SAS would sort out duplicates and clean out any issues, and then it would just continue with a cleans unified list, but they don't have that function right now, or some others, right? 

Speaker 2  (20:05)
Hit the That would be okay for now, right? So I see if somebody pushed back hearing that he's an approval. Alright, so we have low ball on servers here. 

Speaker 2  (20:20)
In the And instead of ascendo to the psa, it should be fine. Yeah, secret database here is set 500 gigs. I have here, is that correct, or is it number I just plugged it in. 

Speaker 4  (20:42)
Actually, we didn't discuss that we have the CPU and Ram, sizing, but I don't have a document at the disk size. 

Speaker 2  (20:52)
So you guys need to tell me what Not this size, but what volume of data are you expecting right? The disks will be generated based on the requested audio motor this is finally So we will ask the core database. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (21:18)
A rough number give us AI can just need to log into So now I can move on. So we have something similar so that we listen to the rb. I just need to see why. 

Speaker 1  (21:31)
What's the capacity right now? What are they going to do? Are the specifications that those boxes? 

Speaker 1  (21:38)
So molecule stuff S and BLPM will suck. And this is SQL, where equal XY So now you are looking at the specific functionality or the servers, all of them running to the 2 GB in collection right now. So we got the 2 GB, we're looking at probably Give me 1 sec 32 giga. 

Speaker 4  (22:13)
Fight, this is a not round disk. 

Speaker 1  (22:17)
Yeah, yes, they have to scam. Yeah, thank you 1 second. 

Speaker 2  (22:20)
6 or you are saying, 6 qual has started 2 gig. 

Speaker 1  (22:26)
I don't like Tony too, because sequel is memory hunger, but we can always increase that, right? It's running a cpus, so you know, logical cpus, a with one core H. And let me take a look at the drive. 

Speaker 1  (22:40)
And with this so 

Speaker 2  (22:47)
It isn't the op. Yes, as Sunday. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (22:52)
Yeah, you know, second try to find a part that shows me that this on the server. Since they're a little nowhere, but I can tell you that when I request this server, most of them had only 250 GB partitions. 

Speaker 2  (23:08)
Okay, let me take care of how much they have today. I think we should be able to find out. Do you know the 7 airlines? 

Speaker 1  (23:14)
I can give you a wine, but I think they all set up the same way, so I'm looking at why right now, if 250 GB, that's what it has. 

Speaker 2  (23:22)
250 only. 

Speaker 1  (23:23)
Yeah, it has 3 partitions. C is a 100 GB, but we don't actually add E has 

Speaker 2  (23:29)
I think it's G or something. 

Speaker 1  (23:32)
That's what I'm looking at. He has 250 GB. 

Speaker 2  (23:35)
Okay, so you send us San Diego P. 

Speaker 3  (23:39)
Yeah, and there weren't Howard. They wouldn't give us more anyways. 

Speaker 2  (23:43)
200000 portals and art, ultimately, I don't know if the ultimate ability is capturing the ultimate 

Speaker 3  (23:46)
With the initial request 

Speaker 1  (23:49)
Yeah, the thing is, you do have to justify widening more right? So the way we tackle this is like especially with rabbi, we just got this and then we submit a capacity, increased ticket, and they bump it up as needed. But yeah, no, you can pick any server, like, I don't remember which is the secret server, but you can see the 

Speaker 2  (24:10)
Hey PPP, right, so that would be application server right? Send the app would be application that should be db in the name. I believe Let me feel drowned the R. 

Speaker 2  (24:24)
P. You have them on windows 22 or is it all windows, 2019? 

Speaker 1  (24:34)
You did that for us. 

Speaker 2  (24:40)
Okay, I also traveled nonprofit stuff. Okay, so here is the production. All of them look like up. 

Speaker 2  (24:47)
This looks like database. Okay, so let's take a look to this one. Database equal, okay, so here we go and this persistence, we have here, so you have 500 gigs. 

Speaker 2  (25:11)
On that one. Allocated, consumable, it's 421 that's 20 here unless I'm looking to the wrong, but it looks like, yeah, this is sequel. 

Speaker 1  (25:23)
The world that that's probably right, because we have these derimination program, and this is a thing called fulcrum running on this thing. So possibly, yes 

Speaker 2  (25:34)
Okay, so it has 421B giga any use to? We want to provision more 600 700 or to accommodate a growth or are we okay with what 

Speaker 1  (25:46)
Right now, I'm okay, I'm okay with this, because remember these are older applications running and I will share with we're not going to allow that on these servers, right? So this should be just us by landmittelling. All right, I only will say to 15 letters synchronous capacities, because maybe somebody's gonna complain saying what you need if I Andre, right, but 

Speaker 2  (26:09)
They will complain about memory right? The problem right now. Okay Yeah, I'm in a spine ahead and even if they complain about 500 will show I will show them this one right. 

Speaker 2  (26:23)
Consume a blow of 421 gig. I know what I can really say we are overcurrying it right now. Ok, okay. 

Speaker 2  (26:32)
Okay, so if I want to get this fine, I would say, let's proceed if 500 okay. And when I have this server open, how much memory it has to up to this one has only 16 gigabaran. 

Speaker 1  (26:47)
Yeah, that's one of the old servers. I think the new 1 has 22, so let's listen to 22 if you come on. 

Speaker 4  (26:57)
The ad, we marked it as 24. I'm not sure where the 24 came from, but this is our chance to Excellent adjustments right now is this is the 

Speaker 2  (27:06)
Sounds the taste question is whether we will get that right. So even we try to get, they are giving us a hard time to give us one extra gigabyte of memory, so yeah. Same thing if I can prove like we will they will look into like performance of corresponding servers I have. 

Speaker 2  (27:24)
They see like you have 24, it doesn't use more than 12. They will have very hard time to use 32 to ask to get 32, right, it will try to say yeah. 

Speaker 1  (27:35)
Yeah, and I think we have most conversation before. That's why we actually know we have before, if any mistaken, yeah, 2045. The things that I don't like is we have to wait for something to happen, like an inch or something before they can actually make they can action like, that's not the way I push. 

Speaker 2  (27:52)
Or let me let me try 32 if her, which we have fallen back to 24. I said backup plan, please. Okay, out of capacity, all right, so anything else we wanna put into this picture any other dependency or anything? 

Speaker 1  (28:12)
I'm just a comment right this indexers, they will need to have indirect access. Yes, I hate that they need to connect 244 or 5 specific new arrests on the building side, to be able to perform authentication and be able to present the data so as the north that needs to be part of the design as well. 

Speaker 2  (28:33)
Okay, so these QR R's will point to proof point site, or are they some other 

Speaker 1  (28:39)
Hi. 3 of them are proof point one of them is it goes to AWS 

Speaker 2  (28:45)
To realize we have a multitude. 

Speaker 3  (28:48)
Which is still, technically part of their SaaS solution. However, it's just an endpoint within their SaaS solution, so it's technically part of a proof of stuff. 

Speaker 4  (28:57)
Yeah, they're hosted on AWS like that's where they are. Yeah, so it's 

Speaker 2  (29:02)
So it's basically covered by this box here right? 

Speaker 1  (29:07)
Sure, but I don't know if you have to make that observation somewhere that they will need to have that connection out to the internet. 

Speaker 4  (29:15)
As long as it's just 

Speaker 2  (29:17)
It already shows this one. The right is the connection around. So It can be like several urls connecting to and the urls should be covered underneath one, right? 

Speaker 2  (29:29)
This small code, eventually part of that saw solution which we can say is still part of that, you know, mall code, the problem is like if you like specifically separate url, then it's more problematic to show that malcody belongs to whether it was assessed and so on. So In my mind, you don't want to go down the drove. 

Speaker 1  (29:51)
Fair enough for enough, I just wanted to mention all right 

Speaker 2  (29:55)
If you're running into issues, we can address it, but I would still try to handle it. Somebody part of the proof point sauce here. Sorry, anything else? 

Speaker 1  (30:08)
I think we forgot to talk about the blob storage and we are supposed to have a conversation today with cloud security Josh Stein, trying to figure out what are the challenges or why, you know, some of the patterns cloud to cloud is now being allowing how we can actually get an Inception, because we need to think about the long-term options based on the conversation, then we'll have something else with value, most likely either towards the end on the day or tomorrow, or maybe Friday. And then at that point we'll have an answer for you. 

Speaker 1  (30:39)
So just wanting to throw that out. 

Speaker 4  (30:42)
Yep, so Howard just did a link back to the beginning. Do you want to wait for that so that this pit can reflect the blob which we don't know how long it will take or no okay. Okay. 

Speaker 4  (30:53)
So it's not recommendation of it but 

Speaker 1  (30:55)
That's great information, exactly. 

Speaker 4  (30:58)
This pit looks good done for the surfer side. 

Speaker 1  (31:06)
So I was good. All right, I think we had time, guys. Thank you for the updates, appreciate it. 

Speaker 2  (31:12)
Oh, yeah, so when do you okay quick question like what is the timeline? When do you wanna proceed to pardon this just wanna know how much time I have to get these and approved. 

Speaker 1  (31:24)
Yesterday, maybe okay. 

Speaker 2  (31:30)
He's in a probable, okay, got it. 

Speaker 1  (31:32)
Thank you, Peter, appreciate her, and I'll cancel the media concluding correction. 

Speaker 2  (31:37)
How did we discuss But the deployment of the service EDP or the manual bill or the cotpip. We discussed this, or did we have already argue? Involved to review this. 

Speaker 1  (31:53)
I don't think there was an traction on the ticket. So maybe we still need that all I call to talk about this positive specific items. Exactly. 

Speaker 2  (32:04)
Alright, so I figured we'll get some arrival and bring it or send him your way to review list. So I wouldn't need is some kind of email that I you know, this is suitable for EDP we are proceeding with EDP or we don't have time to do EDP or proceeding with monoaubiel, but they want us to do this assessment. Okay, good goal. 

Speaker 1  (32:29)
Yeah, if you want to come in that email and I can provide some background and see what's required and yeah, I'm going with that. 

Speaker 2  (32:36)
All right, come on check on that. I think I already requested last time. It's just I haven't followed up on that. 

Speaker 1  (32:43)
Sounds good. Thank you guys. 
