
Speaker 1  (00:01)
So I think last time Peter, you shared something or Chad, I'm not sure, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (00:07)
Yeah, it was primarily being great, so basically this is kind of proposal for the production rate for the alcohol dp site. I don't have the other ones yet, but I think we got stuck on this Azure. Use Azure files or the italic to be connected directly from SARS hosting. 

Speaker 2  (00:32)
So If we make any progress on that, should you have any updates on that? 

Speaker 3  (00:41)
I don't know, I think there's some tipco calls that are being arranged to see what can be done there. 

Speaker 2  (00:48)
So anybody prompting open theme, has looked into that 

Speaker 4  (00:54)
So again, you're a bit a question, Peter, I was sorry. 

Speaker 2  (00:57)
Howard yeah, okay. So great, so last time basically, we construct when we review this design that technical, it's not possible. You correct from SARS hosting to data lake in interior Chad mentioned that somebody you guys looked into possibility to transfer this data via tip code. 

Speaker 2  (01:21)
And all of this, I think, had to be reviewed with proof point vendor right? So that we had chance to look in the alternate ways of delivering these reports, or whatever we are saving on the 

Speaker 5  (01:33)
Absolutely there, I think, HIV. Yes, we, we've done this yesterday, just said, and like, was sorry, I'm late, guys, I was just wanting to come to this meeting to ask if everybody was good with a 2:30 PM time. For I think it was tomorrow. 

Speaker 5  (01:56)
I need to check that again because somehow I was looking at today. Yeah I don't know. Yes, so we tapped the tip code. 

Speaker 5  (02:06)
It's a pattern that they're using. Already, they can do from Amazon, either that's a push or a pull to a td edge or a blob, and they can do that, but We'll find us so I had some items I wanted to share with us. So we're still working on that. 

Speaker 5  (02:26)
But That's a possibility we went through those options with the ST archive, and they think it can work, so we just need to Sneed up another session with them to make sure it, you know what they have, there has been done before, and we can replicate that easily. 

Speaker 4  (02:45)
Yeah, and just do a little bit more, Peter, maybe that component we need to put it in a maybe we'll need to get back to you next week. Because there's also a decision that needs to be made. On the basis side which is, you know, our mbs and vbs, there is a cost associated with this, so we're not sure if it's worth it to actually pay the amount of money, so we have to present that to our leaders and all the options, what's available whatnot. 

Speaker 4  (03:11)
And decide if we want to go with this or we just hold on and wait until our pipeline is there if that makes sense right there could be another compensation and control. So all that needs to be reviewed, so they said, there's a small chance that we're going to come back and say this is not. Required. 

Speaker 2  (03:29)
Hi, so based on what I'm hitting, I'm not kind of getting yet direct instructions, what we want. So we still have to wait to clarify all these points, right? 

Speaker 5  (03:42)
Yeah, I mean 

Speaker 4  (03:43)
I would say one more, wait, you know how days are they Duffy? 

Speaker 5  (03:47)
I'm trying to drop this in on your truck like so now we've sinked 2 dirty to 3 dirty, and they're available, we need 30 minutes. But in both cases, we have a profile and meeting elsewhere, right? 

Speaker 4  (03:59)
Yeah, but we also need to talk to Roger, right? The options and so forth. 

Speaker 5  (04:03)
I just wanted Clark Eddie, before I go to graduate this, because this is the same one, just to make sure tip go get pick it up and move it across for us, and if that's true, then we can present that to Rajo, you know, knowing that it's going to happen, right? Yeah, okay, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (04:19)
Okay. So yeah, that was to mean that's still, it is my choice to prepare right here for me, proceeding with a dec. 

Speaker 5  (04:26)
So Peter, whatever meeting we're having with tiko. I'm always gonna include you in that so so locomot. 

Speaker 2  (04:34)
Yeah, not promising, but we're trying to go A 

Speaker 5  (04:37)
Okay, good thanks. 

Speaker 2  (04:40)
I that's all I have called today. I haven't created a bit for the other Marcos yet. I haven't had time to work on the death. 

Speaker 4  (04:50)
Okay, okay, hi Bixby 

Speaker 2  (04:53)
Yeah, I know. 

Speaker 4  (04:53)
Yes, I do have a question for metric is just something that could run on windows servers or in the cfi closer again, okay? 

Speaker 2  (05:04)
Yes, but there is a limit right, so it can, but how it works is basically it will create one big file and like the grip file right and put everything they need. So there is like theoretical limit of 7 TB of data and last time you guys mentioned you might have several 100. Terabytes, if I remember correctly. 

Speaker 4  (05:31)
This is a nice candidate that's a ban right now, and just to, you know, be straightforward, we have one television Nas that holds the file. So yes, there's a lot of data in the band but it doesn't mean that we're going to be capturing every single file right? So My question was unrelated to that we 're gonna be setting up something that is pulling Dexter, and in that indexer, I'm gonna be sending certain files, so I wasn't sure if that was supported. 

Speaker 4  (06:06)
But yeah, thank you, sorry. 

Speaker 2  (06:09)
Yeah, so yeah, we can do warmer tray, we can do it on windows, but again theoretically made 7 TB, I don't think they will allow you to go any further than that. The reason is, I think I mentioned it last time right a restored from a venture backup with 7 TB. Takes about two weeks if you need to get any file to just declip the whole thing, so that's why they don't like to go past 7 TB. 

Speaker 4  (06:36)
Yeah, no, no I agree. I agree. Yeah, for that, I would have to fight close there and do something else, yeah, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (06:43)
Yeah, so okay, so you have to slide the options and yeah, most probably I don't think we will find any easy way to encrypt, like, if you talk about a 100 TB, so most productive levels have to go through some bisocion for that to host it on the regular file a regular storage like us or something. 

Speaker 4  (07:06)
Yeah, even sharpen chair bone is classified to hold that information type. Right? I would just need to get it in our landing time. 

Speaker 2  (07:15)
Hey, gaine, I would clarify that we want to start several terabytes. How what are they good to say to that window? 

Speaker 4  (07:25)
Quentin planner, the badcammy still plops storage, right? 

Speaker 2  (07:30)
Yeah, so you will. You will play quite a few Bucks here for that if you want to do that. Yeah, yeah, there shouldn't be any problem with encryption in as you were, but it will be expensive. 

Speaker 2  (07:42)
Yeah? That's where we are. Any other question. 

Speaker 1  (07:47)
Ok, so I'll set up maybe 2 more sessions next week. And the week after is that 

Speaker 2  (07:53)
Make Sanchez point like this, and we'll see whether we can proceed or where we are. 

Speaker 1  (07:58)
Okay, I'll i'll do 2 more and then we'll see where we're at 

Speaker 4  (08:02)
Okay, well, let me ask you if they is my right, do we really need a call or because I think at this point, Peter is just waiting for the confirmation. If we just take up now right, if we get that confirmation, we can just send an email a this is how we want to proceed unless you guys still want to call that altho. 

Speaker 2  (08:19)
However, I would recommend let's put a place all around our calendar right if we have nothing to do this cause we can always tell Myron to cancel it run off yeah, if you guys give me next to 3 days that whatever is the direction I can bring to bed for the next meeting next week. So personally, I am okay. I'm in favor of setting up someplace all the meetings. 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
Okay. Yeah, it's easier. It's easier to cancel than to schedule, right? 

Speaker 1  (08:46)
So I'll schedule them and then yeah, okay, gotcha. All right, so sounds good. I'll set up 2 and you know, if this is resolved. 

Speaker 1  (08:54)
Otherwise, then we can like Peter said, we'll just cancel. Okay. All right, okay, have a good afternoon, okay. 
